<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<folder>
		<path>./Sports</path>
		<name>Sports</name>
		<sortname> Sports</sortname>
		<desc>Sports games (including casino, fishing and racing)</desc>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<developer>Sports</developer>
		<publisher>Folder</publisher>
		<image>./images/sports.png</image>
		<releasedate>19691231T160000</releasedate>
	</folder>
	<folder>
		<path>./Other</path>
		<name>Other</name>
		<sortname> Other</sortname>
		<desc>Other games</desc>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<developer>Other</developer>
		<publisher>Folder</publisher>
		<image>./images/stairs.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19691231T160000</releasedate>
	</folder>
	<game>
		<path>./Penguin Land (SG-1000).zip</path>
		<name>Doki Doki Penguin Land</name>
		<sortname>Doki Doki Penguin Land</sortname>
		<desc>Doki Doki Penguin Land is a 1985 game initially developed by Sega for the SG-1000. It is a platform-based puzzle game, where a penguin must guide an egg down the screen making sure not to break it.

The basic aim of Doki Doki Penguin Land is to guide an egg from the top of the screen to the bottom. To do so means digging downwards, making sure it does not smash in the process. As a puzzle-platformer, everything is affected by gravity, and if the egg falls from a great height, it will smash. Success is achieved by making your way down the playfield carefully.

You control a penguin. 1 jumps, 2 digs. The penguin can push the egg left or right, and can jump on it to make sure it doesn't get stuck against a wall. Digging affects the tile one block left (or right) and one block down away from the penguin's position, meaning it is impossible to dig straight downwards. If the egg gets into a position where it cannot be moved left or right, jumping and landing on it will cause it to smash.

The penguin cannot be damaged, but can be temporarily stunned, the objective being to protect the egg, not necessarily yourself. If the player leaves the screen from the bottom he/she will emerge from the top.</desc>
		<image>./images/Penguin Land (SG-1000)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pony Canyon</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Flicky (SG-1000).zip</path>
		<name>Flicky</name>
		<desc>In the game, the player controls Flicky, a bird who has to save the Chirps (Piopio in Japan) from cats named Tiger (Nyannan) and iguanas named Iggy (Choro). The player has to collect all of the Chirps and guide them through the exit, with a bonus increasing in proportion to the amount of Chirps saved at once.

There is only one button in the game, which both causes Flicky to "jump" and, if he is holding and item, throw it across the screen. Items thrown ate enemies will knock them off the screen temporarily, however they will re-spawn at specified locations until the game is over.

Players start with three lives and can gain more lives by acquiring certain scores, however there is a maximum of five lives that can be retained at once.

There are 48 proper levels ("rounds") in the game. Completing these yields a "congratulations" message, followed by the possibility of playing through the game again at a faster speed. These levels are numbered 49, 50 and so on, and levels which previously did not contain Iggy may contain it. Furthermore, some throwable items are replaced with different ones. Once the game has been completed a second time (passing level 96, the "fast" version of 48), the game repeats again, but there is no speed increase (i.e. level 97 is identical to level 49), and the game simply carries on in this fashion until the player loses all his/her lives.</desc>
		<image>./images/Flicky (SG-1000)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Girl's Garden (SG-1000).zip</path>
		<name>Girl's Garden</name>
		<desc>In order to prevent her boyfriend Minto from going to another little girl named Cocco, Papri must collect ten different flowers and return them to her boyfriend's house. Flowers must be caught in full bloom so that the number of flowers in her possession will increase; catching flowers too early will consider the flowers to be wasted and flowers caught too late will be wilted. Wilted flowers will ruin the bouquet, causing the player to lose half of the flowers.

Bears have a taste for honey and cause the player to lose one of two hearts if one of them attacks the player. However, the honey can be dropped in order to render the bear temporarily harmless to the player. Bees appear as the player's ally, giving her bonus items occasionally and extra honey if the player catches it on a flower.</desc>
		<image>./images/Girl's Garden (SG-1000)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840413T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sega Galaga (SG-1000) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Sega-Galaga</name>
		<sortname>Galaga</sortname>
		<desc>Sega-Galaga is the SG-1000 port of Galaga, and is strangely the only port to receive a name change.

The player pilots a starship and must destroy all the on-screen enemies, similar to Space Invaders and Galaxian. However, the enemies in Galaga have the power to steal your ship to use as reinforcements (meaning the player loses a life). However, if you are able to destroy the enemy who has captured your ship, you are able to pilot both ships at once, doubling your firepower at the expense of being a bigger target.

Though Sega-Galaga is essentially the same game as the arcade original, the limitations of the SG-1000 means the graphics and sound are not quite as advanced. Also the "challenging stages" have been omitted, meaning each stage is identical to the last.</desc>
		<image>./images/Sega Galaga (SG-1000) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Space Invaders (SG-1000).zip</path>
		<name>Space Invaders</name>
		<desc>Space Invaders is a 1979 milestone arcade game developed by Taito. The player controls a gun which can move left or right, and needs to destroy waves of aliens (or "invaders") before they reach the ground. Space Invaders was brought to a variety of home video game consoles and computers, including the SG-1000 in 1985.

Surprisingly the SG-1000 port of the game was one of the most accurate of its time, surpassing the NES and MSX versions which were the console's main competitors. Though it adds more color (the arcade version was simply black and white, with translucent overlays to mimic color), the SG-1000 version retains all the original graphics, whereas other ports (especially for Atari systems) re-drew the invaders due to various graphical restrictions.

The SG-1000 version does not appear to have been released outside of Japan.</desc>
		<image>./images/Space Invaders (SG-1000)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wonder Boy (SG-1000) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Wonder Boy</name>
		<desc>Wonder Boy is a platform game developed by Escape and Sega in 1986 for Sega System 1 and Sega System 2 arcade hardware.

WONDER BOY starts off a long and hazardous journey in pursuit of KING, who has kidnapped his girlfriend, TINA. KING lives in a faraway place, inhabited by monstrous creatures and full of many surprises. On the way, our hero has to collect food to increase his energy. WONDER BOY's ultimate mission is to rescue TINA and prove to one and all that true love always triumphs.

Wonder Boy is a sidescrolling platform game, in which the basic goal is to keep heading to to the right, avoiding obstacles, attacking enemies and jumping across platforms. Though it is not a requirement to do so, the game encourages players to keep moving to the right, as health decreases over time and the screen cannot scroll left. Health, and by extension, time, is added to by collecting fruit. There are numerous items hidden in eggs, including hammers, skateboards and fairies which can assist Tom-Tom in his quest.

One button jumps, another attacks. If the attack button is held, Tom-Tom will run and be able to jump higher, similar to the mechanics in Super Mario Bros..</desc>
		<image>./images/Wonder Boy (SG-1000) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19860501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Escape</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sports/Champion Baseball (SG-1000).zip</path>
		<name>Champion Baseball</name>
		<desc>Champion Baseball is an arcade baseball game developed by ADK. Sega distributed the game worldwide, and produced an SG-1000 port in 1983. Alpha Denshi also made a sequel, only released in arcades.

Champion Baseball is said to have been a hugely successful arcade game in Japan, even receiving its own dedicated parlours in the country (of the sort first seen with Space Invaders in 1978).</desc>
		<image>./Sports/images/Champion Baseball (SG-1000)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ADK</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sports/Champion Billards (SG-1000) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Champion Billiards</name>
		<desc>Champion Billiards is a simplistic billiards game built for the SG-1000. It is the first game in Compile's "Lunar Pool" series. It was not released outside of Japan.

Unlike the other Champion Sports games, Champion Billiards is not an accurate representation of it's sport. Instead, Champion Billiards is a level-based physics game. The goal of each level is to use the red cue ball to sink the other balls.

Trivia: Breaking open the yellow ball can release a yellow Flicky.</desc>
		<image>./Sports/images/Champion Billards (SG-1000) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sports/Championship Golf (SG-1000).zip</path>
		<name>Champion Golf</name>
		<desc>Champion Golf is a golf game for the SG-1000.</desc>
		<image>./Sports/images/Championship Golf (SG-1000)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Logitec</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sports/Champion Pro Wrestling (SG-1000) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Champion Pro Wrestling</name>
		<desc>Champion Pro Wrestling is an SG-1000 game. It was later ported to SG-1000-based arcade hardware and to the MSX. Other Japanese computers received Champion Prowres Special instead.</desc>
		<image>./Sports/images/Champion Pro Wrestling (SG-1000) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pony Canyon</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sports/Champion Soccer (SG-1000).zip</path>
		<name>Champion Soccer</name>
		<desc>Champion Soccer is a simplistic football game built for the SG-1000. Pony Canyon later brought it to the MSX.</desc>
		<image>./Sports/images/Champion Soccer (SG-1000)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pony Canyon</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sports/GP World (SG-1000) [!].zip</path>
		<name>GP World</name>
		<desc>GP World for the SG-1000 and MSX, is a loose conversion of the 1984 LaserDisc-based arcade game, GP World. It was released in 1985 exclusively in Japan.

Gameplay in this "8-bit" version of GP World is similar in concept to the arcade GP World but given the wildly differing hardware, different in execution. Most notably all graphics in the game are generated in real-time by the SG-1000 rather than streamed from a LaserDisc, which in turn leads to more predictable car physics. The concept of racing in four different types of GP is scrapped, replaced instead with a GP that spans the world and three selectable difficulties.

Like the original, the game uses a third person perspective similar to the likes of Turbo (although the camera is positioned behind the steering wheel), and sees the player race in a formula one car, navigating the course and avoiding other drivers. This version is also notable for having a simplistic track editor. It is likely that the SH-400 controller was designed with this game in mind.</desc>
		<image>./Sports/images/GP World (SG-1000) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pony Canyon</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sports/Hang-On 2 (SG-1000).zip</path>
		<name>Hang On II</name>
		<sortname>Hang-On 2</sortname>
		<desc>Hang-On II is an SG-1000 sequel to the critically acclaimed Hang-On.

Despite the name, the game is meant as a direct sequel to the Mark III version of Hang-On, and is virtually identical to that game. The only difference is downgraded graphics and the addition of music from the arcade version. Meanwhile, Super Hang-On is the direct sequel to the arcade game.

It is compatible with the BH-400 bike handle controller, and would be the only SG-1000 game designed for it (though the peripheral is compatible with the Sega Master System and Sega Mega Drive).</desc>
		<image>./Sports/images/Hang-On 2 (SG-1000)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sports/Hyper Sports (SG-1000) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Hyper Sports</name>
		<desc>Hyper Sports is a sports game developed by Konami and released for the SG-1000 in 1985 (following a 1984 MSX launch). The game has the player compete through a number of Olympic events.</desc>
		<image>./Sports/images/Hyper Sports (SG-1000) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sports/Monaco GP (SG-1000).zip</path>
		<name>Monaco GP</name>
		<desc>Monaco GP is a 1979 arcade racing game made by Sega. The game is very simple - all the player needs to do is avoid cars and obstacles on a track. He/she can speed up and slow down and two players may play at the same time.

Monaco GP was Sega's last arcade game to use discrete logic circuits rather than a digital CPU, meaning it cannot be emulated in emulators such as MAME. The player's score and time are also displayed on external LED displays, so it is impossible to re-create the game perfectly.

The game only was ported to the Sega SG-1000 in 1983. The SG-1000 version had a difficulty select of one, two, or three other cars on the road. It was quickly followed by Pro Monaco GP which uses similar hardware, but the series would not reach its peak until 1989's Super Monaco GP. The game was, however, included in the Japanese release of the Sega Saturn compilation Sega Ages Memorial Selection Vol: 2. An updated version of the game was released as part of the Sega Ages 2500 series in Japan also.</desc>
		<image>./Sports/images/Monaco GP (SG-1000)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sports/Zippy Race (SG-1000) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Zippy Race</name>
		<desc>Zippy Race is a top-down racing game developed by Irem and initially released in the arcades in 1983. It was subsequently ported to home platforms, including the SG-1000 later in the same year. Some North American ports of the game are called Motorace USA, though no SG-1000 games were officially released in that region.

The game has the player control a motorbike, avoiding cars and obstacles while making sure it does not run out of fuel. The player travels across the United States of America, hence the localized title of Motorace USA.

The SG-1000 version of the game is one of two SG-1000 releases to see four separate Japanese releases (the other being Monaco GP) - three on cartridge with each of the SG-1000's box designs, and one on Sega Card. Despite this it did not see a release outside of Japan.

The arcade version of this game was re-released on the Sega Saturn as part of Irem Arcade Classics.</desc>
		<image>./Sports/images/Zippy Race (SG-1000) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Bank Panic (SG-1000) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Bank Panic</name>
		<desc>Bank Panic is an arcade shooting game developed by Sanritsu and manufactured by Sega in 1984. It was later ported by Sega to the SG-1000 and Sega Master System. An unlicensed clone called West Bank was released for several home computer systems. The same hardware would also be used for the later Sega/Sanritsu game Combat Hawk.

The player takes on the role of a sheriff in 19th century USA, protecting a bank from armed robbers. There are twelve doors arranged in a circle, with the player in the center, which can be viewed three at a time. Robbers who appear from the doors are to be shot (after they draw their weapons, for a higher score) and customers are to be ignored while they make a deposit. Once deposits have been made from all twelve doors, the level is complete.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Bank Panic (SG-1000) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sanritsu</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Bomb Jack (SG-1000).zip</path>
		<name>Bomb Jack</name>
		<desc>Bomb Jack is an arcade game developed by Tehkan which was later ported to the SG-1000 by Sega in 1985. The aim of the game is to collect all the bombs in the playfield while avoiding monsters. Extra points are awarded for collecting the bombs in a specific order.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Bomb Jack (SG-1000)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tehkan Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Borderline (SG-1000).zip</path>
		<name>Borderline</name>
		<desc>Borderline is a VIC Dual arcade game developed in 1980 by Sega. It is a shoot-'em-up in which the player controls a red jeep who must destroy the enemy refineries.

Borderline was ported to the SG-1000 in 1983, and has also been released as part of the Sega Ages 2500 series in Japan. The second gameplay section was also recycled for the Atari 2600 release of Thunderground, though instead of driving a jeep the player controls a tank.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Borderline (SG-1000)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Chack'n Pop (SG-1000).zip</path>
		<name>Chack'n Pop</name>
		<desc>Chack'n Pop is an arcade game developed by Taito which was subsequently ported to the SG-1000 in 1985. It follows a yellow creature named Chack'n who must traverse across several mazes blowing up monsters.

The SG-1000 version of the game includes extra cutscenes and a training level not seen in the arcade version.

Though Chack'n Pop was not a particularly successful game for Taito, it would go on to inspire the success of Bubble Bobble, which shares many of the same characters and devotes a stage to Chack'n Pop. Chack'n has also cameoed in numerous Taito games since, including Bubble Bobble, Fairyland Story, Parasol Stars, Puzzle Bobble (and sequels), Bubble Symphony, Bubble Memories and Arkanoid DS.

Curiously this SG-1000 version uses the katakana script for writing Chack'n Pop as opposed to the hiragana script used in almost every other version.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Chack'n Pop (SG-1000)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Choplifter (SG-1000) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Choplifter</name>
		<desc>Choplifter is a 1982 Apple II game developed by Dan Gorlin and published by Brøderbund. In the game you pilot a helicopter and must rescue people from prisoner of war camps.

Sega were responsible for an arcade remake on both the Sega System 1 and Sega System 2 hardware in 1985. This version was ported to a variety of platforms, including the SG-1000 in 1985 and the Sega Master System in 1986.

Though Choplifter II was a Nintendo Game Boy exclusive, Choplifter III was ported to the Sega Game Gear.

One of Sega's own games, Air Rescue may have been influenced by Choplifter.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Choplifter (SG-1000) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Dragon Wang (SG-1000) (Ver-A).zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Wang</name>
		<desc>Inspired by the arcade classic Kung-Fu Master, Dragon Wang (ドラゴン・ワン) is an action game for the SG-1000. You play as Wang (Chinese for "King"), a Kung-Fu master (inspired by Jackie Chan or his character, Thomas), and must kick other men across four stages. 

This is the prequel to Kung Fu Kid for the Sega Master System.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Dragon Wang (SG-1000) (Ver-A)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Drol (SG-1000).zip</path>
		<name>Drol</name>
		<desc>Drol is an SG-1000 game released in 1985. Originally developed by Brøderbund for various home computers in the west, it was brought to the SG-1000 by Sega and released exclusively in Japan. You play as a robot who must rescue his children.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Drol (SG-1000)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>BrÃ¸derbund Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Elevator Action (SG-1000) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Elevator Action</name>
		<desc>Elevator Action is an arcade game developed by Taito which was later ported to the SG-1000 exclusively for Japan.

This is one of two Elevator Action games to be released on a Sega system, the other being Elevator Action Returns.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Elevator Action (SG-1000) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Exerion (SG-1000) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Exerion</name>
		<desc>Exerion is a arcade shoot-'em-up released by Jaleco in 1983. It was ported to several systems including the SG-1000.

Exerion is a very basic shoot-'em-up, however its main appeal at the time was its parallax backgrounds, whose positions would change depending on the coordinates of the player's ship. Unfortunately, the effects do not transfer well onto the SG-1000, as the scrolling is choppy.

1 shoots a single shot which you can shoot rapidfire. 2 shoots a double shot which you cannot rapidfire.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Exerion (SG-1000) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Golgo 13 (SG-1000).zip</path>
		<name>GOLGO 13</name>
		<desc>Golgo 13 is a shoot-'em-up game for the SG-1000 based on the Japanese manga of the same name.

The game has you shoot at windows of a passing train. Hitting objects that get in the way will make the bullet rebound and potentially kill you.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Golgo 13 (SG-1000)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Gulkave (SG-1000) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Gulkave</name>
		<desc>Gulkave is an SG-1000 shoot 'em up game developed by Compile and published by Sega in 1986. It is a horizontal shooter, in which the player controls a spaceship that must destroy the 8 fortresses of the Gulbas Empire and several various enemies. Despite the limitations of the console, there are 30 "acts", and each "act" has a different background and there are numerous powerups available, setting it apart from most other SG-1000 shooters at the time.

Pony Canyon released a version for the MSX computer presumably also in 1986, on ROM cartridge. This version still sports a Sega logo and Sega copyright; the primary difference between the SG-1000 and MSX is the sound hardware, so the ports are relatively identical. This version was included in Compile's disk magazine DiscStation #09, released in February 1990 as that issue's "Retro Game".</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Gulkave (SG-1000) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/H.E.R.O. (SG-1000).zip</path>
		<name>H.E.R.O.</name>
		<desc>H.E.R.O. is an action game originally developed and published by Activision. Sega brought it to the SG-1000 in Japan.

The objective of the game is to rescue trapped miners in a volcano. 1 drops a stick of dynamite to blow up barriers and kill enemies. 2 shoots a laser-like thing, which you can use to kill enemies. At the bottom of the screen, there is a Power meter showing you how much energy you have left; energy goes down as time goes on. Simply touch a miner to rescue him and move on to the next level.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/H.E.R.O. (SG-1000)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Hustle Chummy (SG-1000) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Hustle Chumy</name>
		<desc>Hustle Chumy is an SG-1000 and MSX game developed by Compile and released in 1984.

In Hustle Chumy players control a mouse named Chumy who needs to collect apples (and other food) in a sewer, avoiding other critters as he goes. As Chumy eats more food, his speed decreases, but his fireballs are given a longer range. Levels have varying layouts.

There are several types of enemies in the game, most of which can be defeated with fireballs.

    Bats: Bats fly over Chumy.
    Mecha-Dinos: Mecha-Dinos are indestructible, although Chumy can slow them down with fireballs.
    Gators: Gators usually sleep in one spot, but sometimes move slowly around.
    Cats: Cats can jump like Chumy.
    Ninjas: Ninjas need to be hit with three fireballs to be defeated.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Hustle Chummy (SG-1000) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/James Bond 007 (SG-1000) [!].zip</path>
		<name>James Bond 007</name>
		<desc>007 James Bond is a shoot-'em-up game developed and published by Tsukuda Original for the SG-1000. It was ported from Parker Brothers's 1983 game of the same name, which was published for various American computers/consoles.

007 James Bond was the last SG-1000 game to be produced by the company.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/James Bond 007 (SG-1000) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tsukuda Original</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Loderunner (SG-1000) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Lode Runner</name>
		<desc>Lode Runner is a puzzle/action game originally developed by Douglas E. Smith and published by Brøderbund Software in 1983. It made its way to many home computers and video games consoles of the day including the SG-1000. Like the NES port, this version only has 50 levels instead of 150 in the original Apple II version, but is much faster.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Loderunner (SG-1000) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Maechiko's Omikuji (SG-1000) (PD).zip</path>
		<name>Mahjong</name>
		<desc>Mahjong or Sega Mahjong is a mahjong game for the SG-1000.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Maechiko's Omikuji (SG-1000) (PD)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/N-Sub (SG-1000).zip</path>
		<name>N-Sub</name>
		<desc>N-Sub is an arcade game released by Sega in 1980. It is similar to Nintendo's Heli Fire but currently nobody is sure which came first. It is also very similar to Deep Scan, except rather than control a boat firing at submarines, you're a submarine firing at boats (and other submarines). As it was a VIC Dual game, it was often bundled with another game in the arcade.

N-Sub is one of the few VIC Dual games to see a home console port — and one of Compile's first projects. It was brought to the SG-1000 in 1983, though as with all SG-1000 games, it only saw a release in Japan and PAL regions.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/N-Sub (SG-1000)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Ninja Princess (SG-1000).zip</path>
		<name>Ninja Princess</name>
		<desc>Ninja Princess known as Sega Ninja in the west, is a Sega System 1 arcade game by Sega. It is a top-down shooter/action game, in which you play as a princess disguised as a ninja who is attempting to stop the evil tyrant Gyokuro.

The game was ported to the SG-1000 in 1986 exclusively for Japan, with an MSX port following shortly afterwards. It was also brought to the Sega Master System as The Ninja, however The Ninja makes several adjustments to the story and characters, as well as updating the gameplay.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Ninja Princess (SG-1000)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pony Canyon</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Orguss (SG-1000).zip</path>
		<name>Orguss</name>
		<desc>Orguss is a shoot-'em-up game developed and published by Sega for the SG-1000. In the game, the player takes control of a robot which can transform into a starship. It is based on the science fiction anime series Super Dimension Century Orguss.

The player can swap between robot and starship modes freely, though both come with their own set advantages and disadvantages. In robot mode, you are able to destroy ground targets and have greater freedom across the screen at the expense of being a bigger target for enemies. You can shoot rapidfire, but move slower. In starship mode you cannot destroy ground targets, but are less likely to be destroyed thanks to the smaller surface area of the ship. You can move faster, but cannot shoot rapidfire. 1 switches between the two forms and 2 shoots.

Orguss had a spiritual sequel in the form of TransBot, released for the Sega Master System in 1985.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Orguss (SG-1000)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Pacar (SG-1000).zip</path>
		<name>Pacar</name>
		<desc>Pacar is an SG-1000 game initially released in 1983. It is essentially a mix between two Namco games; Pac-Man and Rally X.

It is the sequel to Head-On, which was released a year before Puck-Man. However, Pacar is more-so a clone of Puck-Man than a true Head-On sequel.

The player controls "Pacar", a "mischievous" green car through a maze of roads. The objective of the game is to "delete" all of the small red "dots" scattered around the playfield, building up points for a high score. The joystick allows Pacar to move in the proposed direction, assuming it is possible to do so. Like Pac-Man, Pacar does not stop moving unless it hits a wall, however unlike Pac-Man, it is not possible to rotate 180 degrees on the spot - moving in the opposite direction causes Pacar to reverse, and reversing is significantly slower than driving normally. Ideally the player should plan his or her route to avoid reversing altogether.

1 or 2 allows Pacar to move faster across the board. Driving off the edge of the screen makes Pacar appear at the other side, again similar to Pac-Man.

The game has Pacar avoid two types of enemy, also depicted as cars. Blue cars spawn from the garage at the centre of the screen and wander around the play area, only following Pacar if it is close by. Red cars spawn randomly on the road behind Pacar, and are much more aggressive with their tactics. Red cars also differ in that if Pacar speeds up, they will also increase their speed. If either car crashes into Pacar under normal conditions, the player loses a life.

Under certain conditions the game's equivalent of Pac Man's power pellets appear after deleting smaller dots. These give Pacar "temporary invincibility" turning it purple in the process, and act as the only form of attack against oppoents. While purple, the player is free to crash into as many cars as he or she likes, and is granted extra points in the process (starting at 200 and doubling for each successive hit, i.e. 200, 400, 800, 1600, 3200 etc.). It will also slow down red cars. Though there are typically fewer enemies on-screen in Pacar than Pac-Man, the fact that blue cars spawn from the garage instantly after being deleted means it is possible to achieve much higher point combos.

There are only two maps in Pacar, which cycle endlessly until the player dies. The game claims it is "three dimensional" as some roads in map 1 act as bridges over other roads. Once both maps are completed the player proceeds to the next "round", in which more blue cars are added to the playfield (with the exception of round 4, in which the three "normal" blue cars are replaced with one faster blue car. Round 5 will then add a second faster car and so on).

Extra lives are awarded every 10,000 points.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Pacar (SG-1000)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Pachinko 2 (SG-1000) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Pachinko</name>
		<desc>Pachinko is an SG-1000 game developed and published by Sega in 1983. It is, as the name suggests, a video game version of Pachinko, a popular game in Japan. The game did not see an international release.

Pachinko is an extremely rare game for the SG-1000. Soon after release, it was recalled from sale due to a game-breaking bug (need to verify) and very few copies remain in the hands of collectors. This is probably the very first instance of a recall in Sega's history (?).

As of 2013, a recent auction of the game on Yahoo Japan was won for ¥113,500, but it has been known to sell upwards from ¥200,000.

The bug was fixed and the game was re-released a few weeks later as a "sequel", Pachinko II, which is much more common.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Pachinko 2 (SG-1000) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Pitfall II (SG-1000) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Pitfall II: The Lost Caverns</name>
		<sortname>Pitfall 1985: The Lost Caverns</sortname>
		<desc>Pitfall II: The Lost Caverns is the sequel to Pitfall and was released for a variety of systems during the mid-1980s including the SG-1000 in 1985. It was also ported to Sega System 1 arcade hardware by Sega. Gameplay is similar to the original game, but the levels are more maze-like.

Sega's version of Pitfall II was tweaked significantly from its western counterparts released for the Atari 2600, ColecoVision etc. The gameplay is largely the same, but there are many additions. These include a Lives system, mine-carts, balloons, and a final Demon boss. The increased specifications of System 1 hardware means the arcade version is much more detailed and allows the player to see more of the maze at one time. The SG-1000 version is directly inspired by the arcade game, and though cannot match the same level of graphical quality, it is arguably the nicest looking home port of the game.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Pitfall II (SG-1000) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Pop Flamer (SG-1000) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Pop Flamer</name>
		<desc>Pop Flamer is an arcade game developed by Jaleco in 1982, and was brought to the SG-1000 in 1983 by Sega. In the game, the player controls a mouse armed with a flamethrower who must pop balloons while avoiding enemies.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Pop Flamer (SG-1000) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Rock N' Bolt (SG-1000) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Rock n' Bolt</name>
		<desc>Rock n' Bolt is a puzzle game developed by Activision, released for a number of home computers and consoles including the SG-1000 in 1985. It follows Louie the constructor who must bolt down moving platforms in their correct location within a set time limit.

The SG-1000 port is arguably a better choice over its Commodore 64, MSX and ColecoVision counterparts. This is because it is able to give the game a soundtrack without sacrificing the quality of the graphics. Unfortunately the SG-1000 version was only released in Japan.

Interestingly Rock n' Bolt's cover depicts what appears to be an earlier version of the game, sporting green pieces on a blue background (rather than blue on black) and a more western-looking Louie.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Rock N' Bolt (SG-1000) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Safari Hunt (SG-1000) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Safari Hunting</name>
		<desc>Tranquillizer Gun is a 1980 arcade game developed by Sega for VIC Dual hardware. It has the player control a hunter, who must make his way around a maze, shooting animals and dragging their bodies back to his truck.

The game was brought to the SG-1000 as Safari Hunting by a then-just founded Compile with slightly updated graphics. It was also included as a minigame within Dynamite Cop.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Safari Hunt (SG-1000) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sports/Safari Race (SG-1000).zip</path>
		<name>Safari Race</name>
		<desc>Safari Race is a racing game for the SG-1000, developed and published by Sega in 1984. The player must drive through various "sections", avoiding wildlife and other cars while making sure not to run out of fuel.

The game is notable for using licensed cars, potentially the first video game to do so. The player controls a Lancia Stratos HF, and according to the box art, some of the rival cars are Audi Quattros. The Lancia Stratos would receive greater video game recognition in Sega's later creation Sega Rally Championship.</desc>
		<image>./Sports/images/Safari Race (SG-1000)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Video Flipper (SG-1000).zip</path>
		<name>Sega Flipper</name>
		<desc>Sega Flipper is a pinball game released for the SG-1000 in 1983. In New Zealand it is known as Video Flipper.

It was one of the first pinball video games to be released, being released one year earlier than attempts from Jaleco and Nintendo but four years after Atari's Video Pinball. Unlike Video Pinball, however, Sega Flipper makes use of color.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Video Flipper (SG-1000)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Sinbad Mystery (SG-1000).zip</path>
		<name>Sindbad Mystery</name>
		<desc>Sindbad Mystery is an arcade game developed by Sega for Sega G80 (raster) hardware in 1983. It was ported to the SG-1000 in the same year. It follows a boy named Sindbad who must avoid monsters while piecing together a treasure map, similar to Pac-Man. He can also use a digging mechanic to trap enemies, similar to Heiankyo Alien and Space Panic.

The game was re-released as part of the Sega Saturn game, Sega Ages Memorial Selection Vol. 2 in 1997.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Sinbad Mystery (SG-1000)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Soukoban (SG-1000) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Sokoban</name>
		<desc>Sokoban is a puzzle game developed by Thinking Rabbit. Sega ported it to the SG-1000 in 1985. Neither version left Japan.

Sokoban is the basis for Shove It! ...The Warehouse Game, released for the Sega Mega Drive.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Soukoban (SG-1000) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Thinking Rabbit</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Star Force (SG-1000) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Star Force</name>
		<desc>Star Force is a 1984 arcade vertical shoot-'em-up developed by Tehkan (now Tecmo), which was later brought to the SG-1000 in 1985.

The SG-1000 version of the game was released on both cartridge an on Sega Card.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Star Force (SG-1000) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tehkan Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Star Jacker (SG-1000) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Star Jacker</name>
		<desc>Star Jacker is a shoot 'em up video game released for Sega System 1 arcade hardware in 1983. Unlike most shoot 'em ups, the player initially controls three space ships, losing one each time the player dies. This means on the first life you will have three times the amount of firepower than on your last.

Like Xevious there are two types of weapon - forward lasers for flying enemies and bombs for bases.

Star Jacker was ported to the SG-1000 in the same year. Due to the limitations of the console there are fewer variations in backgrounds and the graphics are far simpler overall. The player in this version starts with four ships rather than three, however.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Star Jacker (SG-1000) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830715T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Super Tank (SG-1000) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Super Tank</name>
		<desc>Super Tank is a shoot-'em-up game for the SG-1000. The player drives a tank and is tasked with shooting at and destroying enemy units and structures.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Super Tank (SG-1000) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Terebi Oekaki (SG-1000) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Terebi Oekaki</name>
		<desc>Terebi Oekaki is the game packaged with the Sega Graphic Board for the SG-1000. It is a simple paint program.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Terebi Oekaki (SG-1000) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Black Onyx, The (SG-1000) [!].zip</path>
		<name>The Black Onyx</name>
		<sortname>Black Onyx</sortname>
		<desc>The Black Onyx is a role-playing game developed by Bullet Proof Software. It was released, among other consoles and computers, for the SG-1000 in 1987. It was the last SG-1000 game to be released in card form, and the last to be published by Sega, but it is currently unknown as to whether it was the last SG-1000 game. MSX and PC-8801 versions had been released in 1983 and 1984, respectively, meaning this version is unusually late.

The game was followed by The Black Onyx II: Search For The Fire Crystal, which saw its original MSX release in 1984.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Black Onyx, The (SG-1000) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bullet-Proof Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Yamato (SG-1000) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Yamato</name>
		<desc>Yamato is an arcade game developed by Sega in 1983. It runs on hardware designed by Nichibutsu for their 1980 game Crazy Climber. It was subsequently brought to the SG-1000 later in the year.

In the game the player takes control of the Yamato battleship (which was sunk off Kyuushuu during World War II), firing at enemy ships and planes while avoiding missiles and torpedoes.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Yamato (SG-1000) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Zaxxon (SG-1000).zip</path>
		<name>Zaxxon</name>
		<desc>Zaxxon is an arcade shoot 'em up video game released by Sega. It is named after its groundbreaking use of axonometric projection (though more specifically, it uses isometric projection) and was released for bespoke arcade hardware in 1982.

Zaxxon was the first video game to use an isometric perspective, a graphical style which would see widespread use in the years which followed. It was an early attempt at adding three-dimensional depth to the shoot 'em up genre. The term "isometric perspective" was originally coined by Sega in reference to Zaxxon.[9]

Zaxxon stands as one of Sega's earliest video game successes, and is also notable for being the first arcade game to be advertised on US television, with a commercial being produced by Paramount Pictures for $150,000.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Zaxxon (SG-1000)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pony Canyon</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Congo Bongo (SG-1000).zip</path>
		<name>Congo Bongo</name>
		<desc>Congo Bongo, originally known as Tip Top, is a 1983 arcade platformer game developed by Sega. It is often considered an isometric equivalent to Nintendo's Donkey Kong, as it stars a protagonist chasing after a large ape (in this game, called "Bongo"). However, unlike Donkey Kong, the game is set in a jungle, the graphics are more detailed and there are more enemies and traps.

Congo Bongo runs on similar hardware to Zaxxon, known as the Sega Zaxxon hardware.</desc>
		<image>./images/Congo Bongo (SG-1000)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>5</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20210904T170842</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Castle, The (SG-1000).zip</path>
		<name>The Castle</name>
		<sortname>Castle, The</sortname>
		<desc>The Castle is video game developed by ASCII and released for the SG-1000 in 1986. It is a port of an MSX game of the same name, and is largely identical due to the similar hardware between the two machines. Due to the decline of the SG-1000 and emergence of the Sega Master System, the game was not released in Europe or Australia like many other SG-1000 games.

The Castle was the last SG-1000 game to be released commercially by Sega on a cart, and the only SG-1000 to adopt packaging more akin to Sega Mark III games. The Black Onyx would be the very last SG-1000 game to be released by Sega, but this would be on card.

The game has a fairly standard plot of rescuing a princess from a castle, though the game itself was considered very large for the time. It also contains a map system similar to that of later Metroid and Castlevania games.

The Castle was followed by the MSX/NES game Castle Excellent later in the year. The MSX version was also brought independently to the SG-1000 in Taiwan.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Castle, The (SG-1000)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19860201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ASCII</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
</gameList>
