<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<folder>
		<path>./Sports</path>
		<name>Sports</name>
		<sortname> Sports</sortname>
		<desc>Sports games (including casino, fishing and racing)</desc>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<developer>Sports</developer>
		<publisher>Folder</publisher>
		<image>./images/sports.png</image>
		<releasedate>19691231T160000</releasedate>
	</folder>
	<folder>
		<path>./Other</path>
		<name>Other</name>
		<sortname> Other</sortname>
		<desc>Other games</desc>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<developer>Other</developer>
		<publisher>Folder</publisher>
		<image>./images/stairs.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19691231T160000</releasedate>
	</folder>
	<game>
		<path>./Sports/Decathlon (1983) (Activision).zip</path>
		<name>Decathlon</name>
		<desc>The Activision Decathlon is a sports game written by David Crane for the Atari 2600 and published by Activision in 1983. It was ported to the Atari 8-bit family, Atari 5200, Commodore 64, ColecoVision and MSX platforms. Up to four players compete in the ten different events of a real-life decathlon, either in sequence or individually.

The game became somewhat notorious for the amount of wear or damage inflicted upon console controllers,[citation needed] namely the Atari 2600 version where rapid back-and-forth movement of the joystick propels the athlete down the track.

The game was later reissued simply as Decathlon by the UK budget label Firebird.[1] It was subsequently featured on the PlayStation 2 compilation Activision Anthology.</desc>
		<image>./Sports/images/Decathlon (1983) (Activision)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830502T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20211018T222701</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sports/Motocross Racer (1984) (Xonox).zip</path>
		<name>Motocross Racer</name>
		<desc>Motorcycle racing in three events. Qualify in Desert Scramble, Hill Climb and Beach Sprint. Race against time and avoid obstacles in this fast paced game.</desc>
		<image>./Sports/images/Motocross Racer (1984) (Xonox)-image.png</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840808T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Xonox</developer>
		<publisher>Xonox</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sports/Omega Race (1981-83) (Midway).zip</path>
		<name>Omega Race</name>
		<desc>Omega Race is an arcade game programmed by Ron Haliburton[1] and released in 1981 by Midway. It is the only arcade game with vector graphics Midway created.

Omega Race was ported to the VIC-20 and Commodore 64 in 1982 and sold by Commodore. In 1983, a ColecoVision port was released by Coleco and an Atari 2600 version by CBS Electronics. The 2600 cartridge came bundled with a special 2-button, "booster grip" controller.[2]</desc>
		<image>./Sports/images/Omega Race (1981-83) (Midway)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19831001T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sports/Rocky Super-Action Boxing (1983) (Coleco).zip</path>
		<name>Rocky Super Action Boxing</name>
		<desc>Rocky Super Action Boxing is the first licensed video game based on the popular Rocky film series. The game is based on Rocky III and was designed by Coleco. In the game, the player can play as either Rocky Balboa or Clubber Lang in the game, either against the computer in a one player game, or against each other in a "Head to Head" two player mode. There is also a "Demo" mode if the player wants to watch Rocky and Clubber Lang fight.

Since Rocky Super Action Boxing is one of the later ColecoVision titles released, it includes a pause feature for the game.

Each boxing match consists of, according to the skill level chosen, two, five, ten, or fifteen rounds each lasting one minute each. During gameplay, the player's movement is restricted to three positions or "lanes" vertically, and from each player's side of the ring to the front of their opponent horizontally.

The 4 button controller allows for (independently) offensive hits to the body or head, defensive blocking for the head and body, and ducking.

Points are scored in the game by hitting the opponent's guard (1 point), or with a punch connecting with the opponent's head or body (2 points for either hit).

Victory can be achieved in two ways, either by knockout, or by point count if the fight goes all the way to the end.</desc>
		<image>./Sports/images/Rocky Super-Action Boxing (1983) (Coleco)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Coleco</developer>
		<publisher>Coleco</publisher>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Alphabet Zoo (1984) (Spinnaker).zip</path>
		<name>Alphabet Zoo</name>
		<desc>Alphabet Zoo is a series of ten-minute programmes for young children, produced by Granada Television and was broadcast on ITV for two series in 1983 and 1984. It was presented by singer Ralph McTell and actress Nerys Hughes. Each episode is dedicated to a letter of the alphabet.

The second series was directed by Lorne Magory (Press Gang, Life Force, Emmerdale etc.)

Nearly a decade after Alphabet Zoo came to an end, the format was revived by ITV Carlton on the similarly named series Alphabet Castle which ran from September 1993 to December 1995.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Alphabet Zoo (1984) (Spinnaker)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Spinnaker Software Corporation</publisher>
		<kidgame>true</kidgame>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Antarctic Adventure (1984) (Konami).zip</path>
		<name>Antarctic Adventure</name>
		<desc>All dressed up and no place to go? Not so with Frostbite Freddie! He's on a goodwill mission, visiting as many bases as he can before time runs out! Catch fish and collect flags for bonus points! And be on the lookout for curious seals and holes in the ice! Speed counts! Is time on your side?</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Antarctic Adventure (1984) (Konami)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840803T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Coleco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Aquattack (1984) (Interphase).zip</path>
		<name>Aquattack</name>
		<desc>Aquattack is an action game with four levels which partly have varying gameplay mechanics. In level one and two, the player mans a motor boat which needs to travel a certain distance from left to right. Of course there is a lot of enemy opposition which needs to be avoided. Some enemies can be shot while others are out of reach. Fuel is limited and needs to replenished by collecting refreshments dropped by allied planes. Level three is similar; the player uses a hang glider now. There are different enemies to fight and no fuel to collect. In level four, there is a guarded energy field to cross in order to bring four bombs to the other side. However, only one bomb can be transported at once and there is a time limit.

After beating all four levels, they loop with more difficult enemies and faster playing speed. The player can take nine hits and the overall goal is to earn as many points as possible before the unavoidable final death occurs.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Aquattack (1984) (Interphase)-image.png</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Interphase Technologies Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Interphase Technologies Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Artillery Duel (1983) (Xonox).zip</path>
		<name>Artillery Duel</name>
		<desc>In this two player game each player controls an artillery gun set in a mountain landscape with the goal of destroying the other player. Players take turns firing at each other; on each turn you have a limited amount of time in which the barrel angle and powder level can be set in order to control the direction and distance of the shot. When deciding on your shot, you will need to take the current conditions into account, which includes wind speed/direction and any mountains that may get in your way. Successfully destroying your opponents gun will earn you a point, and the first player to reach the set number of points wins the game. There are multiple skill levels available which set the amount of time you have to make a shot.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Artillery Duel (1983) (Xonox)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830316T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Xonox</developer>
		<publisher>Xonox</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Strategy</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/BC's Quest for Tires (1983) (Sierravision).zip</path>
		<name>B.C.'s Quest for Tires</name>
		<sortname>B.C. 1 Quest for Tires</sortname>
		<desc>Cute Chick is in trouble! She is being held captive by the dinosaur, and it is up to Thor to ride his trusty wheel to the rescue. There are many obstacles in the way which Thor will need to jump and duck, including rocks, trees, rivers, lava pits, cliffs, and of course Fat Broad. When you duck, the character bounces up and down, so don't duck too soon. BC's Quest For Tires is a side scrolling action game resembling Moon Patrol in some ways, featuring characters from the comic strip BC.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/BC's Quest for Tires (1983) (Sierravision)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19831101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sydney Development Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra Online</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/BC's Quest for Tires II - Grog's Revenge (1984) (32k).zip</path>
		<name>B.C. II: Grog's Revenge</name>
		<sortname>B.C. 2 Grog's Revenge</sortname>
		<desc>Thor has completed his Quest for Tires. Now he must discover the Meaning of Life. But it won't be easy. The Meaning of Life is hidden away; somewhere in a long maze of mountains.

Each mountain is covered with clams and Thor needs to gather 100 clams in order to pay the tolls and advance through each mountain. The only way to Peter and the toll bridge is through the "real scary caves". There are lots of clams in the caves but watch out for stalagmites. Keep Thor's headlight sweeping back and forth for maximum clams.

Out of the cave, watch out for Grog, who saves clams from Thor. Thor also has contend with rocks, potholes and pterodactyls (they'll eat his wheel) in his Quest for Clams and the Meaning of Life.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/BC's Quest for Tires II - Grog's Revenge (1984) (32k)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19850401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sydney Development Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra Online</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Bejeweled Demo by Daniel Bienvenu (2001) (PD).zip</path>
		<name>Bejeweled</name>
		<image>./Other/images/Bejeweled Demo by Daniel Bienvenu (2001) (PD)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20020101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>?</developer>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Blockade Runner (1984) (Interphase).zip</path>
		<name>Blockade Runner</name>
		<desc>A 3D shoot 'em up. You have to guide a fleet of four merchant space freighters to Earth with vital supplies. Hostile aliens have sighted you and forced you enter a dangerous asteroid belt. And now, you must try to avoid these asteroids, to destroy the Robot mines and alien space ships and also contend with fuel shortages and prevent the deflector shields from over-heating.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Blockade Runner (1984) (Interphase)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Interphase Technologies Inc.</developer>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Boulder Dash (1984) (Micro Fun).zip</path>
		<name>Boulder Dash</name>
		<desc>The ultimate underground journey, but be forewarned - nothing less than perfection is required! Boulder Dash will challenge your mind and reflexes like no other game. The objective is to search throughout each cave and collect as many jewels in as short a time as possible. Once the indicated amount has been collected, the door to the mysterious escape tunnel is revealed and you go to the next level. Boulders drop predictably enough, but you and Rockford also have to block growing amoebas, transform butterflies, outmaneuver fireflies, and overcome other numerous obstacles.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Boulder Dash (1984) (Micro Fun)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19841201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Micro Fun</developer>
		<genre>Action, Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Brain Strainers (1984) (Carousel).zip</path>
		<name>Brain Strainers</name>
		<desc>Brain Strainers is a collection of two separate games/learning tools.

The first game is "Follow The Leader" where a pattern is repeated using a 4-color circle. By keeping track of either the tones generated or the colors flashing, the player can copy the sequence to continue. Higher difficulties increase speed and allow only tone identification of sequences. Additionally it keeps track of your best number of correct identifications in a row.

The second game is "Clef Climber" where the player is given a tone that corresponds to a certain musical note and must match the note being played. Lower difficulties provide a constant tone to refer to and visual help on the note being used. Higher difficulties provide a single playing of the tone and no visual help.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Brain Strainers (1984) (Carousel)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Coleco</developer>
		<genre>Music</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Buck Rogers - Planet of Zoom (1983) (Sega).zip</path>
		<name>Buck Rogers: Planet of Zoom</name>
		<desc>It's the 25th Century. You are Buck Rogers fighting the battle of Planet Zoom. Skillfully slip through zapping electron posts. Dodge and destroy deadly space hoppers and alien saucers. Your race against death has just begun! Prepare for battle with your most powerful enemy... the Mother Ship! It's never easy when it's do or die. You must hit the Mother Ship with two deadly shots. Anything less will only waste precious time. Aim steady, but hurry ... your time is dangerously low!</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Buck Rogers - Planet of Zoom (1983) (Sega)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840203T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Coleco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sports/Bump 'N' Jump (1982-84) (Data East).zip</path>
		<name>Bump 'n' Jump</name>
		<desc>Bump 'n' Jump, known in Japan as Burnin' Rubber (バーニンラバー Bānin Rabā?), is a 1982 Japanese arcade game created by Data East Corporation, released as both a dedicated board and as part of their DECO Cassette System. The game was published in certain regions by Bally Midway.

In Bump 'n' Jump the goal is to drive from the beginning of a level to the end while bumping enemy vehicles into obstacles and jumping over various large obstacles such as bodies of water.</desc>
		<image>./Sports/images/Bump 'N' Jump (1982-84) (Data East)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840601T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Burgertime (1982-84) (Data East).zip</path>
		<name>BurgerTime</name>
		<desc>Your chef is battling for his life in the fast-paced world of fast food. He scurries up ladders and across planks in a frantic effort to build delicious hamburgers. Horrible hot dogs, evil eggs, and perilous pickles constantly try to surround and trap him. Dust those nasties with a pinch of pepper and stop them in their tracks. Gulp some coffee or gobble some fries and you store some extra pepper. Get through the seventh maze and you are a certified burger-maniac.

Pickles, eggs, and hot dogs relentlessly chase your chef through the maze. Be smart and be quick but most of all, carry plenty of pepper.

Give nasties a ride on a falling bun to score the big points. Watch out though! These nasties never die.</desc>
		<image>./images/Burgertime (1982-84) (Data East)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19831125T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Mattel Electronics</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Campaign '84 (1983) (Sunrise).zip</path>
		<name>Campaign '84</name>
		<desc>Campaign '84 is a game developed by Sunrise Software and released for the ColecoVision in 1983. It is a political simulator in which the player must run for president in the 1984 American presidential elections.

The plot involves the player campaigning in the continental U.S. to become the president of the United States. The player has a limited amount of time to play as well as random events which may come up. The player must focus on many comical issues like reducing Pet Rock unemployment or controlling water guns.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Campaign '84 (1983) (Sunrise)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunrise Software</developer>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Carnival (1982).zip</path>
		<name>Carnival</name>
		<desc>This game captures the fun, excitement, and sounds of an old-time shooting gallery. Blaze away at clay pipes, dancing bears and sitting ducks. But watch out, those aren't ordinary sitting ducks. They come to life when they reach the end of the gallery, and avenge themselves by eating from your limited supply of ammunition. How many can you shoot down?</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Carnival (1982)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19800605T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Coleco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Centipede (1983) (Atarisoft).zip</path>
		<name>Centipede</name>
		<desc>Centipede is a vertically oriented shoot 'em up arcade game produced by Atari, Inc. in 1981. The game was designed by Ed Logg and Dona Bailey. The player defends against centipedes, spiders, scorpions and fleas, completing a round after eliminating the centipede that winds down the playing field.


The player is represented by a small, "somewhat humanoid head"[1] at the bottom of the screen, later depicted as a caped, elf-like character on the Atari 2600, Atari 5200 and Atari 7800 cartridge graphics (though described as being a garden gnome in the trivia section of the cell phone interpretation). The player moves the character about the bottom area of the screen with a trackball and fires laser shots at a centipede advancing from the top of the screen down through a field of mushrooms. Shooting any section of the centipede creates a mushroom; shooting one of the middle segments splits the centipede into two pieces at that point. Each piece then continues independently on its way down the board, with the first section of the rear piece becoming a new head. If the head is destroyed, the section behind it becomes the next head.

The centipede starts at the top of the screen, traveling either left or right. When it hits a mushroom or the edge of the screen, it drops one level and switches direction. Thus, more mushrooms on the screen cause the centipede to descend more rapidly. The player can destroy mushrooms by shooting them, but each takes four hits to destroy.


Centipede-Arcade
If the centipede reaches the bottom of the screen, it moves back and forth within the player area and one-segment "head" centipedes are periodically added. This continues until the player has eliminated both the original centipede and all heads. When all the centipede's segments are destroyed, a new centipede forms at the top of the screen. Every time a centipede is eliminated, however, the next one is one segment shorter and is accompanied by one additional, fast-moving "head" centipede.

The player is also menaced by other creatures besides the centipedes. Fleas drop vertically, leaving additional mushrooms in their path; they appear when fewer than five mushrooms are in the player movement area, though the number required increases with level of difficulty. Spiders move across the player area in a zig-zag fashion and occasionally eat some of the mushrooms. Scorpions move horizontally across the screen and poison every mushroom they touch, but these never appear in the player movement region. A centipede touching a poisoned mushroom hurtles straight down toward the player area, then returns to normal behavior upon reaching it.

A player loses a life when hit by a centipede or another enemy, such as a spider or a flea, after which any poisoned or partially damaged mushrooms revert to normal. Points are awarded for each regenerated mushroom.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Centipede (1983) (Atarisoft)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19831201T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Choplifter (1982-84) (Broderbund).zip</path>
		<name>Choplifter</name>
		<desc>In Choplifter, the player assumes the role of a combat helicopter pilot. The player attempts to save hostages being held in prisoner of war camps in territory ruled by the evil Bungeling Empire. The player must collect the hostages and transport them safely to the nearby friendly base, all the while fighting off hostile tanks and other enemy combatants. According to the backstory, the helicopter parts were smuggled into the country described as "mail sorting equipment."

Although the Iran hostage crisis ended the year before the game was released, Gorlin has stated "the tie-in with current events was something that never really crossed my mind until we published."</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Choplifter (1982-84) (Broderbund)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Coleco</developer>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Chuck Norris - Super Kicks (1983) (Xonox).zip</path>
		<name>Chuck Norris Superkicks</name>
		<desc>You are the world's greatest living karate expert armed with a variety of kicks and punches, and in search of an ancient monastery. You must choose which path to follow. At each branch, you find obstacles and warriors you must conquer. Win the fight and earn a higher degree belt, plus bonus time. Lose and you lose ground and time because you've been stunned. Become a black belt and you enter the monastery, only to encounter the mystical Ninja, masters of camouflage. How far can you get on the path to ultimate victory?</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Chuck Norris - Super Kicks (1983) (Xonox)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19831209T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Xonox</developer>
		<publisher>Xonox</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Super Cobra (1983) (Parker Bros).zip</path>
		<name>Super Cobra</name>
		<sortname>Cobra, Super</sortname>
		<desc>Super Cobra (スーパーコブラ Sūpā Kobura?) is a 1981 arcade game, the sequel to popular horizontally scrolling shooter Scramble, Super Cobra was developed by Konami and manufactured and distributed by Stern in North America. It is similar in concept to its predecessor, but much more difficult.

The game was a success, selling 12,337 video game arcade cabinets in the United States in four months, by October 2, 1981, becoming Stern's third best-selling arcade classic after Berzerk and Scramble. Scramble sold 15,136 cabinets in the US in five months earlier that year, adding up to 27,473 US cabinet sales for both.[1]

Super Cobra was widely ported by Parker Brothers, and there was an Adventure Vision handheld version from Entex.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Super Cobra (1983) (Parker Bros)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Parker Brothers</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/ColecoVision Monitor Test (1982).zip</path>
		<name>ColecoVision Monitor Test</name>
		<desc>ColecoVision Monitor Test was created in 1982 to test the monitor settings for the ColecoVision to Television interface. This game was only a demo.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/ColecoVision Monitor Test (1982)-image.png</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19820101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Coleco</developer>
		<publisher>Coleco</publisher>
		<genre>Sandbox</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Congo Bongo (1984).zip</path>
		<name>Congo Bongo</name>
		<desc>Congo Bongo is an isometric platform arcade game released by Sega in 1983 and on the Colecovision in 1984. The player takes the role of a red-nosed safari hunter who tries to catch an ape named Bongo. The hunter seeks Bongo to exact revenge for an apparent practical joke in which Bongo set fire to the hunter's tent, giving him a literal "hotfoot." The game was named by Peter W. Gorrie who was the CFO of Sega at that time.

The game's ROM contains a message indicating it was likely coded at least in part by the company Ikegami Tsushinki.

Congo Bongo's gameplay is similar that of Donkey Kong and Frogger, but levels are viewed in an isometric perspective, or oblique perspective in some ports. The protagonist has no offensive abilities and must move or jump to avoid enemies and obstacles to complete a level.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Congo Bongo (1984)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Cosmic Avenger (1982) (Universal).zip</path>
		<name>Cosmic Avenger</name>
		<desc>In this futuristic air and sea battle game, you command a space fighter in combat against an alien civilization. Using the control, you direct it over the cities and down through the sea caverns. The alien installations must be destroyed! But the aliens employ ships and submarines that fire missiles and release bombs with unrelenting force! You've got to maintain a close watch on the radar screen, observe their positions and retaliate to stay alive!</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Cosmic Avenger (1982) (Universal)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19810807T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Universal Interactive Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Cosmic Crisis (1983) (Bit Corp).zip</path>
		<name>Cosmic Crisis</name>
		<desc>Feel that secret joy of the demons? As it Is so badly haunted by those energetic demons, it seems that, this time, the world is terribly drawing to the crisis of surviving. In front of you will be the toughest enemies over met and you get to rely on yourself alone. No fighting though, it wouldn't do you any good; the only chance Is the hammer In your hand and the intelligence in your head. Got it? Fine, now start and win a beautiful victory!</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Cosmic Crisis (1983) (Bit Corp)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830504T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bit Corporation</developer>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Cosmo Fighter 2 by Marcel de Kogel (1996-97) (PD).zip</path>
		<name>Cosmo Fighter 2</name>
		<desc>iant spaceship is threatening to attack the planet Xunor and capture its inhabitants. As commander of the mighty Cosmo Fighters, you are given the task of eliminating this evil force and returning peace to the galaxy.

But this mission won’t be an easy one! To reach your goal, you must fight your way through various stages, each filled with advanced enemy fighters, grouping together to prevent you from finishing your mission successfully.</desc>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Super Cross Force (1983) (Spectravideo).zip</path>
		<name>Super Cross Force</name>
		<sortname>Cross Force, Super</sortname>
		<desc>There’s a new menace in the galaxy! It’s the evil Morplus from the planet Tzoris. Morplus are without question the fiercest warriors east of the Libra Super-Galactic Cluster. They arrive in teams of two to four members, and in waves with the more dangerous squadrons arriving later. In the more advanced skill levels, they’re impossible to stop! Both their flight patterns and bombing maneuvers are highly unpredictable. What can you do against odds like these? There’s only one hope: you must catch them in a devastating super cross force. The key is your awesome "Spectron" weapon, which creates a dual holographic laser blast. You can get them coming and going, and if you run low on energy, you can deftly swing your joystick to the left or right to catch the energy packs dropped by your mother ship.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Super Cross Force (1983) (Spectravideo)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19831201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Spectravideo</developer>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Dam Busters, The (1984).zip</path>
		<name>The Dam Busters</name>
		<sortname>Dam Busters, The</sortname>
		<desc>You will relieve the spine chilling experience of this famous raid as you take the place of some of the bravest men in recent history. You will play the role of pilot, navigator, gunner and bomb-aimer in this real-time multiscreen, arcade/strategy game which is an authentic recreation of that fateful flight.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Dam Busters, The (1984)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840419T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sydney Development Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Coleco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Dance Fantasy (1984) (Fisher-Price).zip</path>
		<name>Dance Fantasy</name>
		<desc>There are eight dance steps to choose from and endless ways to put them together. You decide how long your dance is, where the dancers move, and how they dance together. And that creates the freedom children need to stretch their imaginations and create their own special works of art.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Dance Fantasy (1984) (Fisher-Price)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Fisher Price</developer>
		<genre>Music</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Defender (1983) (Atarisoft).zip</path>
		<name>Defender</name>
		<desc>Defender is an arcade video game developed and released by Williams Electronics in February 1981.[1] A shooting game featuring two-dimensional (2D) graphics, the game is set on a fictional planet where the player must defeat waves of invading aliens while protecting astronauts. Development was led by Eugene Jarvis, a pinball programmer at Williams; Defender was Jarvis' first video game project and drew inspiration from Space Invaders and Asteroids. Williams planned to display the game at the Amusement &amp; Music Operators Association (AMOA) trade show, though development delays resulted in the team working on the game up until the show started.

Defender was one of the most important titles of the Golden Age of Video Arcade Games, selling over 55,000 units to become the company's best selling game and one of the highest-grossing arcade games ever. Praise among critics focused on the game's audio-visuals and gameplay. It is frequently listed as one of Jarvis' best contributions to the video game industry, as well as one of the most difficult video games. Defender was ported to numerous platforms, inspired the development of other games, and was followed by sequels and many imitations.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Defender (1983) (Atarisoft)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19831201T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Destructor (1984) (Coleco).zip</path>
		<name>Destructor</name>
		<desc>Your starcruiser lands in the hostile city of Araknid to collect precious Crystals needed desperately on earth. Your equipment: the mighty Ram-car. Use your Ram-car to bump Krystaloids, transforming them into precious Crystals! But watch out for the evil Destructor and deadly Insektoids, protectors of the Krystaloids! Can you collect the invaluable jewel-like Crystals and fly home? 

This is one of the few Colecovision games to make use of the Expansion Module #2, the Steering Wheel Controller.

You steer your armored Ram-car through Araknid's maze searching for Krystaloid insects. Ram them to form Crystals, then push the Crystals to the starcruiser.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Destructor (1984) (Coleco)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Coleco</developer>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Dig Dug (1983) (Atarisoft) (Prototype).zip</path>
		<name>Dig Dug</name>
		<desc>Dig Dug (ディグダグ Digu Dagu?) is an arcade game developed and published by Namco in Japan in 1982. It runs on Namco Galaga hardware, and was later published outside of Japan by Atari, Inc.. A popular game based on a simple concept, it was also released as a video game on many consoles.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Dig Dug (1983) (Atarisoft) (Prototype)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atarisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Coleco</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong (1982).zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong</name>
		<desc>In this engaging game, Donkey Kong the ape has captured Mario's girlfriend, and has taken her to the top of a steel fortress. You've got to get Mario to the top to save her! But - as he runs across the girders and up the ladders, the ape throws barrels at him to prevent his progress. Mario must jump the barrels to get to the top and rescue his girlfriend!</desc>
		<image>./images/Donkey Kong (1982)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830714T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ikegami Tsushinki</developer>
		<publisher>Coleco</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Jr (1982-83).zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Junior</name>
		<desc>Mario has gone mad! He's turned the tables on Donkey Kong and locked him in a cage. It's up to you, as Donkey Kong Jr., to rescue your father by stealing Mario's set of keys. But it won't be easy. You'll have to fight off ape-eating Snapjaws, jump onto moving islands and break through a jungle of vines to get to the keys that will free Donkey Kong. Can you handle the action? Because this off-the-wall monkey business will have you going bananas!</desc>
		<image>./images/Donkey Kong Jr (1982-83)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Dr. Seuss's Fix-Up The Mix-Up Puzzler (1984) (Coleco).zip</path>
		<name>Dr. Seuss' Fix-Up the Mix-Up Puzzler</name>
		<desc>Designed for children ages 4–10, Dr. Seuss' Fix-Up the Mix-Up Puzzler is an electronic sliding puzzle featuring six Dr. Seuss characters: the Cat in the Hat, the Grinch, a Star-Bellied Sneech, the Doorman, and the Woset and Clark. The object of the game is to reassemble scrambled pictures, each of which is composed of three characters.

There are five difficulty levels from which to choose. In the easiest level, kids can mix and match the characters' heads, torsos and feet any way they like. In higher levels of play, there are more puzzle pieces, some of which are upside down, and characters must be assembled in their original left-to-right order. Puzzles range in size from 9 to 25 pieces. The fifth level has a time limit which, when beaten, will give the player bonus points.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Dr. Seuss's Fix-Up The Mix-Up Puzzler (1984) (Coleco)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19841001T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/DragonFire (1984) (Imagic).zip</path>
		<name>Dragonfire</name>
		<desc>The king's treasures have been stolen! As the daring young prince, your goal is to recover them all. The treasures are being kept in various castles, each one guarded by a fire breathing dragon. Each level in the game has two parts; first you will need to cross the castle's drawbridge. You will have to jump and duck the dragons fireballs as well as avoid flying arrows to reach the other side! In the second part you need to collect all of the treasures on the screen and make it to the exit while avoiding the dragon who runs across the bottom of the screen. The dragons on each level have different patterns of movement and firing, and as the levels progress will become faster and trickier.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/DragonFire (1984) (Imagic)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19820101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Imagic</developer>
		<publisher>Imagic</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Escape From The Mind Master (1983) (Starpath) (Prototype).zip</path>
		<name>Escape from the Mindmaster</name>
		<image>./Other/images/Escape From The Mind Master (1983) (Starpath) (Prototype)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Evolution (1983) (Sydney).zip</path>
		<name>Evolution</name>
		<desc>Evolution is an arcade style action game with six levels where you need to evolve from an amoeba to a human. Each level is a different stage in evolution with it's own unique goals. The first level is the amoeba stage where you need to eat all the DNA on the screen while avoiding the spores, microbes, and antibodies that are trying to stop you. The second level is the tadpole stage. The tadpole needs to eat three flies to move on to the next stage while avoiding the very hungry fish. Next is the rodent stage, where you need to eat five blocks of cheese while avoiding the snakes. In level four you need to guide a beaver across alligator infested waters to retrieve sticks and build a dam. The fifth level is the gorilla stage, where your gorilla has to use coconuts to fight off monkeys that are trying to steel its orange stash. And finally is the human stage, where you have to use a laser gun to fight off mutants that are trying to take over the earth.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Evolution (1983) (Sydney)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830504T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sydney Development Corp.</developer>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Fall Guy (1983) (20th Century Fox) (Prototype).zip</path>
		<name>Fall Guy</name>
		<desc>Based on the hit television series staring Lee Majors and Heather Thomas.
In the warehouse screen, when you land on the second floor, go all the way to the LEFT. Then run RIGHT and JUMP.
Now you should be on top of the first crate, so run RIGHT. You should fall through the hole on the right, when you fall
adjust it so that you land on your feet. The last floor you should be able to handle.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Fall Guy (1983) (20th Century Fox) (Prototype)-image.png</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>20th Century Fox</developer>
		<publisher>Coleco</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Fathom (1983) (Imagic).zip</path>
		<name>Fathom</name>
		<desc>Neptina, Neptune's daughter, has been imprisoned at the bottom of the sea by Titans. Your goal is to rescue her by locating the scattered pieces of a magical trident! You will need to take the form of a dolphin and a bird in order to locate the pieces that are hidden in the ocean and clouds. When flying in the air, there are several screens that have clouds flying by. Touch all of the clouds, and the trident piece appears! Other birds which are flying around will cause you to lose energy if you touch them accidentally. Underwater, trident pieces can be found by touching the sea horses. Octopuses, sharks, and a deadly maze of seaweed will get in your way and cause you to lose energy if caught! When you have located all of the trident pieces, the cage holding Neptina can be unlocked, but if you run out of energy first the game will be over.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Fathom (1983) (Imagic)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830502T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Imagic</developer>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Final Test Cartridge (19xx).zip</path>
		<name>Final Test Cartridge</name>
		<desc>Final Test Cartridge was designed as a full system test of the ColecoVision in 1982.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Final Test Cartridge (19xx)-image.png</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19820101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Coleco</developer>
		<publisher>Coleco</publisher>
		<genre>Sandbox</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Flipper Slipper (1983) (Spectravideo).zip</path>
		<name>Flipper Slipper</name>
		<desc>It is a water-themed Breakout-like game, with the unique mechanic of having curved paddles, which can cause the ball to roll off them and bounce off at unconventional angles.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Flipper Slipper (1983) (Spectravideo)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Spectravision</developer>
		<publisher>Spectravision</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fortune Builder (1984) (Circuits and Systems).zip</path>
		<name>Fortune Builder</name>
		<desc>FORTUNE BUILDER has it all! Educational and fun, FORTUNE BUILDER lets you plan, build and run your own community. Race against time to achieve your financial goal in a One-Player Game or compete with another tycoon in a Two-Player Game. Either way.
FORTUNE BUILDER is a challenge. Your community will be laid out on a map of undeveloped land, consisting of a seacoast with beachfront. two mountain ranges, midlands, a river and a lake, with a main highway running north and south. You'll start with a fixed amount of cash, enabling you to buy and build a large variety of proper-ties: hotels, condos, marinas, factories, malls, gas stations and numerous other facilities.
The challenge is to build them where they will draw the most traffic, thereby increasing profits. And all the while, you must keep an eye on bulletins that may affect your efforts, watching for changes in every-thing from consumer trends to the weather. FORTUNE BUILDER teaches problem solving and helps you learn, in a way both fun and realistic, about economics, geography, sociology, investments and the effects of the environment and current events on industry and the marketplace.</desc>
		<image>./images/Fortune Builder (1984) (Circuits and Systems)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Coleco</developer>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Fraction Fever (1983) (Spinnaker).zip</path>
		<name>Fraction Fever</name>
		<desc>In Fraction Fever, the player's goal is to advance floors up to the twentieth with the help of his pogo stick and the Fraction Elevators located on each floor. To find them, the player needs to look for the correct fraction pictures, matching what is shown at the top of the screen, while a radar shows the layout of floors at the bottom. Incorrect fractions can be knocked down for scoring points, but this leaves holes in the floors. When the player doesn't manage to jump over these and falls down far enough or several times, the game will end. There is also a time limit to look out for, if the clock reaches zero the Fraction Elevator of the current floor cannot be reached, and the player has to jump down a floor to be able to try again.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Fraction Fever (1983) (Spinnaker)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830503T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Spinnaker Software Corporation</developer>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<kidgame>true</kidgame>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Frantic Freddy (1983) (Spectravideo).zip</path>
		<name>Frantic Freddy</name>
		<desc>A tall building is on fire, and while all the human inhabitants seem to be safe, their cats are trapped in the flames. It is up to the brave fireman Frantic Freddy to save all the cats, floor by floor.

Frantic Freddy is an arcade action game where Freddy must run back and forth on the ground, dodging falling rubbish while shooting water at flames in the windows of a building. When all fires are extinguished, the game progresses to the next floor, where Freddy can climb between the floors, shooting to the left and right instead of upwards. On these levels, there are two kinds of flames – the red and the purple ones. The purple ones are more aggressive, following Freddy around the screen, and can only be put out once all the red ones are extinguished. The game progresses in this way, alternating between the upwards-shooting levels and the sideways-shooting levels.

On the higher difficulty levels, cats turn up at intervals in the windows, falling down after a while. Freddy must catch the cats, or he will lose a life. Similarly, he loses a life if hit by a fire or falling rubbish.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Frantic Freddy (1983) (Spectravideo)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830505T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Spectravideo</developer>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Frenzy! (1982-83).zip</path>
		<name>Frenzy</name>
		<desc>Frenzy is the sequel to Berzerk and gameplay is similar. You are chased around a maze of rooms by various robots and your player must avoid their lasers and shoot them back to destroy them. There's only so much time the player can stay in a room before a "Robot Attacks" occurs and a smiley face of death moves in on the player. In Frenzy there are also reflective mirrors in place of certain walls which reflects shots back and allow you to ricochet your fire. Also unique to Frenzy are four "device rooms" with a special icon in the center of the room that may be destroyed for bonus points and a special effect within that room.</desc>
		<image>./images/Frenzy! (1982-83)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830504T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Coleco</developer>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Frogger (1982-83) (Parker Bros).zip</path>
		<name>Frogger</name>
		<desc>Frogger (フロッガー) is a 1981 arcade game developed by Konami and licensed for North American distribution by Sega-Gremlin. It is regarded as a classic from the golden age of video arcade games, noted for its novel gameplay and theme. The object of the game is to direct frogs to their homes one by one by crossing a busy road and navigating a river full of hazards. The Frogger coin-op is an early example of a game with more than one CPU, as it used two Z80 processors.[4]

By 2005, Frogger in its various home video game incarnations had sold 20 million copies worldwide, including 5 million in the United States.[5]</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Frogger (1982-83) (Parker Bros)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19831101T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Frogger II - ThreeDeep! (1984) (Parker Bros).zip</path>
		<name>Frogger II: Threeedeep!</name>
		<desc>Frogger II: ThreeeDeep![1] is a console and computer game released in 1984. The game is a sequel to the original Frogger from 1981, and features similar gameplay.

The goal of Frogger II: ThreeeDeep! is to maneuver each frog to a berth at the top of the screen. Once all of the berths are filled the player progresses to the next level. Unlike its predecessor, the game features three consecutive screens for each level rather than one screen per level, with berths at the top of each of the three screens that need to be filled.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Frogger II - ThreeDeep! (1984) (Parker Bros)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19841001T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Frontline (1983) (Taito).zip</path>
		<name>Front Line</name>
		<desc>Front Line is a vertically scrolling action game. Your mission is to infiltrate enemy territory and destroy their fortress. To reach the fortress, you will have to make your way through varied and dangerous terrain. Jungles, deserts, brush, and rocks all slow your progress, plus each area has numerous enemy fighters and tanks trying to stop you. To help get past these obstacles, you are armed with a machine gun and grenades; at some points in the game you may even come across an abandoned tank which you can control to increase your odds of survival. When you reach the end of the level and successfully destroy the fortress, the game will repeat at a higher level of difficulty. Gameplay is for one or two players, and four different skill levels are available.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Frontline (1983) (Taito)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830504T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Coleco</developer>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Galaxian (1983) (Atarisoft).zip</path>
		<name>Galaxian</name>
		<desc>Galaxian (ギャラクシアン Gyarakushian?) is an arcade game that was developed by Namco and released in October 1979. It was published by Namco in Japan and imported to North America by Midway that December. A fixed shooter game in which the player controls a spaceship at the bottom of the screen, and shoots enemies descending in various directions, it was designed to compete with Taito Corporation's successful earlier game Space Invaders (which was released in the previous year, and also imported to the US by Midway Games).

The game was highly popular for Namco upon its release, and has been a focus of competitive gaming ever since. It spawned a successful sequel, Galaga, in 1981, and the lesser known Gaplus and Galaga '88 in 1984 and 1987 respectively, as well as many later ports and adaptations. Along with its immediate sequel, it was one of the most popular games during the golden age of arcade video games.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Galaxian (1983) (Atarisoft)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840501T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Gateway to Apshai (1984) (Epyx).zip</path>
		<name>Gateway to Apshai</name>
		<desc>Gateway to Apshai is a top-down action-RPG. As the descendant of a hero, the player starts with basic stats in 4 areas, Strength, Agility, Luck and Health. and basic equipment, a dagger and leather armor. Then it's time to choose a number between 1 and 99 to generate the dungeon. Once begun, the player must explore the dungeon, hidden until explored and revealed. The player can move in four directions and has standard abilities, each mapped to a different control. There are several different actions available to the player. These include: fighting with the equipped weapon, a LOCATE spell to discover traps in the room, a SEARCH spell to discover hidden doors inside of room which would otherwise look like ordinary walls. Players may also use many of the items and scrolls that can be picked up in the dungeon. The treasure can be picked up which include weaponry (swords, bows and arrows), healing slaves, precious items and magical scrolls. Most items are only good for a single use.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Gateway to Apshai (1984) (Epyx)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Epyx</developer>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gorf (1981-83) (Midway).zip</path>
		<name>Gorf</name>
		<desc>The game itself consists of four levels:
•The first level has you behind a defensive shield, defending against an alien attack. The level is a top-down view, with your ship &amp; shield on one side and the aliens on the other side;

•The second level is similar to the first, only your defensive shield is gone, and the enemies tend to swoop down over the level as opposed to those row formations. Bonus ships also tend to appear in this level;

•The third level is a change, and has you entering hyperspace. Your only goal is to survive to the end of your journey. The viewpoint switches from a top-down view to a behind-the-ship view and in effect you are heading "towards" your destination. Alien vessels flying in circular formation try to stop you;

•The fourth and final level is similar to the first again, with some key differences. You do not fight a wave of enemies, but a single one. A mothership with a glowing weak spot. Hitting the weak spot will instantly destroy it. The mothership also has that same shield that was yours in the first level.</desc>
		<image>./images/Gorf (1981-83) (Midway)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway, Bally</developer>
		<publisher>CBS Electronics</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Gust Buster (1983) (Sunrise).zip</path>
		<name>Gust Buster</name>
		<desc>Navigate your way through videogame's most colorful amusement park without the use of the joystick. Keep an eye on the windsocks since they indicate the force and direction of wind gusts that will blow you around the park.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Gust Buster (1983) (Sunrise)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840817T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunrise Games</developer>
		<publisher>Sunrise Software, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gyruss (1984) (Parker Bros).zip</path>
		<name>Gyruss</name>
		<desc>Gyruss (ジャイラス Jairasu?) is a shoot 'em up arcade game designed by Yoshiki Okamoto and released by Konami in 1983. Gyruss was licensed to Centuri in the United States, and was ported to contemporary home systems.

The gameplay is similar to that of Galaga but presented in a forced 3D perspective, with the player's ship facing 'into' the screen and able to move around the perimeter of an implicit circle. The scrolling starfield of earlier space shooter games is arranged to fit the 3D perspective, with the stars coming into view at the centre of the screen and flying outward, giving the impression of the player's ship moving through space.

Gyruss is the second and last game Yoshiki Okamoto designed for Konami, after Time Pilot. Due to pay disputes, he was fired after the release of this game, and soon joined Capcom, where he would write 1942 and the first Street Fighter game.

The game's background music is an electronic, uptempo arrangement of J. S. Bach's Toccata and Fugue in D minor, BWV 565; this particular track is similar to "Toccata", a rock arrangement by the UK-based instrumentalist group Sky. Gyruss is notable for using stereo sound, which according to the bonus material for Konami Arcade Classics, was achieved by utilizing discrete audio circuits.

Gyruss was released in both upright and cocktail cabinets.[2]</desc>
		<image>./images/Gyruss (1984) (Parker Bros)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840601T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Heist, The (1983) (Micro Fun).zip</path>
		<name>The Heist</name>
		<sortname>Heist, The</sortname>
		<image>./Other/images/Heist, The (1983) (Micro Fun)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840301T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/H.E.R.O. (1984) (Activision).zip</path>
		<name>HERO</name>
		<desc>I had been traveling farther south. Word came from a nearby village of a terrible mine of disaster. Many miners were trapped with no means of escape. The closer I came to the site, the warmer the ground felt beneath my feet. Then, as the villagers assisted with my gear and shouted a chorus of encouragement, I suddenly realized. I was being lowered, not merely into a mineshaft, but - a volcano.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/H.E.R.O. (1984) (Activision)-image.png</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840813T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Illusions (1984) (Nice Ideas).zip</path>
		<name>Illusions</name>
		<desc>Illusions is a surreal ColecoVision video game in which the player maneuvers blobs around the screen, trying to get them to merge, or, alternatively, split apart. At times, lizards may chase the blobs around. The water bucket, when spilled, can cause the lizard to turn into a fish. If the fish remains there too long, however, it turns into a bird. The game was created by Nice Ideas, a division of Mattel that was located midway between Cannes and Nice.</desc>
		<image>./images/Illusions (1984) (Nice Ideas)-image.png</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Coleco</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Its Only Rock 'N' Roll (1984) (Xonox).zip</path>
		<name>It's Only Rock 'N Roll</name>
		<desc>In this brilliant text and graphics game, you start with a guitar, a few bucks and enough raw talent to sit in with the Stones or the Police. Now you've got some big decisions to make as you pick one of three levels and let IT'S ONLY ROCK 'N ROLL take you down a whirlwind road seeking the unbelievable wealth, status and popularity points you'll need to succeed. If you're really good if you can avoid exhausting tours, bad managers. lousy material and too much fun — if you can keep your money, stay happy, and interpret the record charts and newspaper headlines — you'll be the all time reigning KING OF ROCK AND ROLL! Fail and you'll be playing the opening act blues. But whether you end up a superstar or a has-been, ITS ONLY ROCK 'N ROLL AND YOU'LL LIKE IT! LOVE IT! YES YOU WILL!</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Its Only Rock 'N' Roll (1984) (Xonox)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Xonox</developer>
		<genre>Music</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/James Bond 007 (1984) (Parker Bros).zip</path>
		<name>James Bond 007</name>
		<desc>When it comes to fast-paced action and intrigue, nobody does it better than Bond. James Bond.

But you can try when you reenact scenes from four great James Bond movie classics.

007's specially designed vehicle will take you on the ride of your life - over land, in the air, and under the sea! Through it all you must avoid obstacles, avert enemies, and accomplish four different missions!

Raid a sunken ship in For Your Eyes Only. Illuminate the night for an oil rig rescue raid in Diamonds Are Forever. Get Stromberg and his undersea hideaway in The Spy Who Loved Me. Save the Earth from cosmic catastrophe in Moonraker.

Multiple levels and special effects add challenge and excitement. It's the best of bond in one great game!</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/James Bond 007 (1984) (Parker Bros)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840515T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Parker Brothers</developer>
		<publisher>Parker Brothers</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Joust (1983) (Atarisoft) (Prototype).zip</path>
		<name>Joust</name>
		<desc>Joust is an arcade game developed by Williams Electronics and released in 1982. While not the first game to feature two-player cooperative play, Joust was more successful than its predecessors and popularized the concept. The player uses a button and joystick to control a knight riding a flying ostrich. The object is to progress through levels by defeating groups of enemy knights riding buzzards.

John Newcomer led the development team, which included Bill Pfutzenreuter, Jan Hendricks, Python Anghelo, Tim Murphy, and John Kotlarik. Newcomer aimed to create a flying game with cooperative two-player gameplay, but wanted to avoid a space theme, which was popular at the time. Staff worked within the technical limitations of the hardware (originally developed two years earlier for Williams' first game, Defender), excluding concepts and optimizing the visuals.

The game was well received in arcades and by critics, who praised the gameplay. The gameplay mechanics influenced titles by other developers. Joust was followed by a sequel four years later, and was ported to numerous home and portable platforms.

The ColecoVision version of Joust was never released officially by AtariSoft in 1983, game was done but with no sound.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Joust (1983) (Atarisoft) (Prototype)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19831001T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Juke Box (1984) (Spinnaker).zip</path>
		<name>Jukebox</name>
		<desc>JUKEBOX is a musical strategy game that's kind of a cross between a chess match and a dance contest. During the game the jukebox plays lots of terrific songs—songs so good you never want them to stop. But to keep the music playing. you've got to create gold records. Use your dancing shoes to jump from square to square. creating hit records as you go. The more gold records you get, the more coins you earn. Use the coins to keep the music bopping and the game from stowing. And not only is JUKEBOX fun to play. it's also a challenging learning game. By studying the size and configuration of records. players develop strategies to avoid being trapped. Memory and concentration skills are tested as players plan their moves from square to square. And by recognizing patterns. players sharpen their prediction skills. All together. JUKEBOX is an exciting challenge with plenty of fun for young and old alike.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Juke Box (1984) (Spinnaker)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840502T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Spinnaker Software Corporation</developer>
		<genre>Music</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Jumpman Junior (1984) (Epyx).zip</path>
		<name>Jumpman Junior</name>
		<desc>The ALIENATORS are back! And they have overrun the Jupiter Command Substation. It's up to Jumpman Junior with his speed and jumping ability, to defuse the bombs planted throughout the twelve levels.

Your strategy is important, analyze each screen before you begin, but don't take too long, the more quickly you clear the screen the more bonus points you get. Maneuver up and down the ladders, ropes, and dumbwaiters. Watch out for the electrocution traps, moving walls, hellstones and the ever present enemy bullets. If you think you can handle all that, be prepared for the hurricane winds that blow you off course every time you jump. Jumpman Junior, the cartridge sequel to Jumpman, has twelve exciting screens waiting for you. Can you master them all?</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Jumpman Junior (1984) (Epyx)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19841201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Epyx</developer>
		<publisher>Epyx, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Jungle Hunt (1983) (Atarisoft).zip</path>
		<name>Jungle Hunt</name>
		<desc>JUNGLE HUNT! Now you can play the arcade hit in your own home. The graphics and gameplay are so realistic, you'll think you're on your own video safari! You'll find yourself hanging by your fingertips from slippery ropes, fighting off tooth crocodiles, and dodging huge bouncing boulders. Hurry up and rescure your sweetie from the hungry cannibals - it's almost dinnertime!</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Jungle Hunt (1983) (Atarisoft)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atarisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Atarisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Ken Uston's Blackjack-Poker (1983).zip</path>
		<name>Ken Uston's Blackjack/Poker</name>
		<desc>Feeling Lucky? Pull up a chair and play a few hands of Blackjack or Poker. Minimum bet is $1 and maximum is $499 at the BlackJack table, whereas over on the 5-Card Stud Poker table the sky is the limit. Up to 4 people can play simultaneously, or if you're a little shy you can always go one-on-one with the dealer. Speaking of which, don't forget to give Max, your dealer, a nice tip, or you never know what kind of cards he'll deal out in your next hand.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Ken Uston's Blackjack-Poker (1983)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19831202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Coleco</developer>
		<publisher>Coleco</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Keystone Kapers (1983-84) (Activision).zip</path>
		<name>Keystone Kapers</name>
		<desc>Keystone Kapers is a video game published by Activision for the Atari 2600 in 1983, and later ported to the Atari 5200, Atari 8-bit family, ColecoVision, and MSX. Inspired by Mack Sennett's slapstick Keystone Cops series of silent films, the object of the game is for Officer Keystone Kelly (the player) to catch Harry Hooligan before he can escape from a department store.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Keystone Kapers (1983-84) (Activision)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840601T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Lady Bug (1982) (Universal).zip</path>
		<name>Lady Bug</name>
		<desc>Lady Bug is an insect-themed maze chase arcade game produced by Universal Entertainment Corporation and released in 1981. Its gameplay is similar to Pac-Man, with the primary addition to the formula being gates that change the layout of the maze when used. The arcade original was relatively obscure, but the game found wider recognition and success as a launch title for the ColecoVision console.

The goal of Lady Bug is to eat all "flowers", hearts and letters in the maze while avoiding other insects. The player is represented by a red, yellow, and green character resembling a ladybug while the enemy insects' appearance varies by level. The border of the maze acts as timer, with each circuit signaling the release of an enemy insect from the central area, up to (generally) a maximum of four. The speed of the circuit increases on stages 2 and 5.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Lady Bug (1982) (Universal)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19920601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Universal Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Universal Interactive Inc.</publisher>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Linking Logic (1984) (Fisher-Price).zip</path>
		<name>Linking Logic</name>
		<desc>LINKING LOGIC challenges children to improve their logical reasoning and pluming skills. These skills play a key role in developing a child's ability to approach and solve problems. A child learns to identify different ways to approach a problem. plan actions to be taken. and evaluate the outcome of a solution. In LINKING LOGIC, your child places -tools- along a path to guide Ruddy or Betty down through five floors of a building. Along the way, your child helps the character collect the patterned tiles that are missing from the bottom floor.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Linking Logic (1984) (Fisher-Price)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Fisher Price</developer>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Logic Levels (1984) (Fisher-Price).zip</path>
		<name>Logic Levels</name>
		<image>./Other/images/Logic Levels (1984) (Fisher-Price)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Looping (1983) (Venture Line).zip</path>
		<name>Looping</name>
		<desc>Looping is an arcade action game for one or two players. Your goal is to guide a plane from the runway to a docking station. To do this, there are several screens you need to get past. In the first area, you need to destroy a rocket which will open the gate to the next area. Enemy balloons and city terrain all get in your way! Once you've opened the gate and flown through, you will enter a maze made of pipes. There are no enemies trying to destroy you here, but be careful not to crash into the walls! Bonus points can be earned by staying in the maze for longer periods of time or by flying faster. Once you near the end of the pipe maze, the docking station will be in sight. There will now be several twinkle monsters, green drops, and bouncing balls in the way, all of which destroy your plane on contact. If you successfully reach the goal, the game will repeat at a more difficult skill level.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Looping (1983) (Venture Line)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830504T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Coleco</developer>
		<genre>Flight Simulator</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/M.A.S.H. (1983) (20th Century Fox) (Prototype).zip</path>
		<name>M*A*S*H</name>
		<desc>M.A.S.H. is loosely based off of the hit TV show of the same name. It is actually two separate games that can be played four different ways. In each game you play Hawkeye and play against Trapper who is either player 2 or the computer. The object of either game is to get 1,000 points first.

The first game is a Choplifter style game where you must maneuver your helicopter through the jungles of Korea picking up the wounded until your chopper is full and then return them safely to base. You will have to compete with Trapper in collecting the limited number of wounded while navigating through the trees and past tanks who are trying to shoot your copter down.

In the second game you're in the operating room and must remove the bullets from your fallen comrades without further injuring him, much like the board game Operation.

Style one is Welcome to Korea which features both styles of game switching back and forth. Style two is Operating Room which is just the Operation challenge. Style three is Chopper Challenge is just the Choplifter style game. Style four is Heavy Flak which is just like style three but with many more injured to rescue and more tanks to avoid.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/M.A.S.H. (1983) (20th Century Fox) (Prototype)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>20th Century Fox</developer>
		<publisher>Coleco</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Memory Manor (1984) (Fisher-Price).zip</path>
		<name>Memory Manor</name>
		<desc>Wee Willie is a window washer at an apartment who wants to keep his customers happy. Some of the customers welcome him and want their windows washed while others are worrisome about his wet work and would not want him washing their windows. There's only so much water for Willie to wield in his bucket, so he must only waste it on the welcoming window wash customers. It's also raining so Willie will have to remember who lives where.

Memory Manor is a memory matching game played from a side-view perspective. Players take control of Wee Willie who can move left and right, climb ladders and choose to wash a window he is in front of. The game relies on memory, after a brief glimpse of the people in the manor the windows fog up, hiding the occupants. The player must remember which windows contain happy customers and wash their windows. Willie has a limited water supply and so must not waste washing on anyone who doesn't want their windows washed. The game is over if Willie uses up all of his water.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Memory Manor (1984) (Fisher-Price)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Fisher Price</developer>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Meteoric Shower (1983) (Bit Corp).zip</path>
		<name>Meteoric Shower</name>
		<desc>Meteoric Shower is essentially a clone of Space Invaders, Galaxian and Galaga, but it introduces several new concepts: Your ship can move in all four directions, it flips upside down when moving down, and enemies can attack from both above and beneath your ship.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Meteoric Shower (1983) (Bit Corp)-image.png</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bit Corporation</developer>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Miner 2049er (1983) (Micro Fun).zip</path>
		<name>Miner 2049er</name>
		<desc>As Bounty Bob, the player's goal is to inspect every section of each mine in search of the evil Yukon Yohan while avoiding the various radioactive creatures that inhabit the mine. As Bounty Bob walks over a section of flooring, it fills with color. To complete the level, every section of flooring must be colored. There are ten mines in total (eleven in the ColecoVision port). Each level is timed and must be completed before the player runs out of oxygen.
Along the way, Bob encounters many objects left behind by past miners. By collecting these, bonus points are achieved and the radioactive creatures smile and turn green. While in this state, Bob can collect them and earn extra points.
Various obstacles in each mine aid and hinder Bob's progress. Ladders allow him to climb up or down to the next platform, Matter transporters teleport him to other matter transporters in that mine, chutes slide Bob off a platform (often against his will), and pulverizers crush Bob if he gets in their way.
Most levels contain some custom element, which varies from level to level. Pressing the space bar for several seconds skips a level. On the Atari 800, the player can key in the phone number on the title screen, followed by a level number to skip to that level.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Miner 2049er (1983) (Micro Fun)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830801T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Monkey Academy (1984) (Konami).zip</path>
		<name>Monkey Academy</name>
		<desc>This platform game is about solving arithmetic problems. In the equation one number is missing, you 'll have to find the right number. This game is aimed at young children to help them learn arithmetic problem solving or playing with numbers.

Some monkeys are minding their own business when they see a number missing from their arithmetic problem. Who took it? Another monkey, a crab? And where could it be? The only way to find that out is to go looking for it.

Guide your monkey across the screen and up and down platform levels. Watch out for the crab! If its claws bite you, you lose a monkey. Jump up and pull down shades to find the missing number. When you find it, catch the number bar. Then send it up to your helper monkey. Find three missing numbers and earn bonus points!</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Monkey Academy (1984) (Konami)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Coleco</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Montezuma's Revenge (1984) (Parker Bros).zip</path>
		<name>Montezuma's Revenge</name>
		<desc>Wherever there's mind-twisting mystery, hair-raising adventure, and non-stop action - PANAMA JOE is sure to be there. And in MONTEZUMA'S REVENGE, he's got more than he bargained for as you help him through 100 danger-filled chambers in Aztec emperor's fortress. The stakes? Priceless treasure. And lots of it. But finding necessary keys, torches, swords, and amulets is no small feat as PANAMA JOE tries to avoid deadly snakes, menacing spiders, and bouncing skulls. But then disappearing floors, bridges, and laser walls are no picnic either! It's up to you to lead this undaunted adventurer through the labyrinth of chambers in an attempt to solve the riddle of the fortress and escape with the loot!</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Montezuma's Revenge (1984) (Parker Bros)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Parker Brothers</developer>
		<publisher>Parker Brothers</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Moonsweeper (1983) (Imagic).zip</path>
		<name>Moonsweeper</name>
		<desc>In Moonsweeper your goal is to rescue miners from the moons in Star Quadrant Jupiter. You begin your mission in space where you must avoid deadly aurora flares, photon torches and space bullets from the sun in this quadrant. From time to time you will see a moon pass by, and by flying near it you can descend to the surface. As you sweep along the surface, you will see stranded miners which need to be rescued by flying over them. Also on the moons surface are various obstacles which must be avoided or destroyed, such as towers and lunar satellites as well as alien surface destroyers. Should you survive and rescue six miners (the maximum your ship can carry), then you may take off from the surface by using the accelerator rings. There are several different types of moons found in this quadrant, each with a different level of difficulty. To help out, your ship is equipped with photon torpedoes and shields (though you will lose points while using the shield).</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Moonsweeper (1983) (Imagic)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830504T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Imagic</developer>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mousetrap (1982) (Exidy).zip</path>
		<name>Mouse Trap</name>
		<desc>Mouse Trap is a 1981 arcade game released by Exidy. The game design is similar to Pac-Man, replacing Pac-Man with a mouse, the dots with cheese, the ghosts with cats, and the power pills with bones. The unique element of Mouse Trap is that color-coded doors in the maze can be toggled by pressing a button of the same color. The game was ported by Coleco as a ColecoVision launch title in 1982.

The player uses a  joystick to maneuver a mouse throughout a maze and eat pieces of cheese scattered along the paths. Six cats patrol the maze and chase the player, with two present at the outset and four more being released one at a time. The maze has three sets of color-coded doors, which the player can open or close by pressing the corresponding buttons in order to block the cats' approach. The player can also escape the cats by entering the "IN" box at the center of the screen, which will teleport the mouse to one of the four corners at random. Contact between the mouse and a cat costs the player one life.</desc>
		<image>./images/Mousetrap (1982) (Exidy)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19820601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Exidy, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Exidy, Inc.</publisher>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Mr. Do! (1983) (Universal).zip</path>
		<name>Mr. Do!</name>
		<desc>You control Mr. Do has he tries to harvest all of the cherries on the screen. However, there are numerous bad guys out to get him! Mr. Do can defend himself from the badguys in two ways: first he can push the apples located throughout the playfield on top of the enemies and crush them. Secondly, Mr. Do is armed with a power ball. This can be thrown to destroy an enemy. Mr. Do has only one power ball, though, so he will need to wait for it to return to him before it can be used again. From time to time an alpha monster will appear on the screen bearing one of the letters in EXTRA. If you use the power ball to destroy an alpha monster you earn that letter; when you've earned the complete word EXTRA you receive an extra life. When you successfully collect all of the cherries, you will move on to the next, more difficult level.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Mr. Do! (1983) (Universal)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Universal Entertainment Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Coleco</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Mr. Do's Castle (1983) (Parker Bros).zip</path>
		<name>Mr. Do's Castle</name>
		<desc>The object of Mr. Do's Castle is to score as many points as possible by collecting cherries and defeating unicorn-like monsters. The game takes place in a castle filled with platforms and ladders, some of which can be flipped from one platform to another. The player controls Mr. Do as he collects cherries by using a hammer to knock out blocks that contain them from the various platforms. Empty holes left by the knocked-out blocks serve as traps for the monsters - if a monster falls into a hole, the player can then defeat it by causing a block above the monster to fall on top of it. If the player takes too long to complete a level, the monsters transform into faster, more difficult forms that occasionally multiply. The game advances to the next level when all cherries on the level have been collected or all enemies have been defeated. The player loses a life if Mr. Do is caught by a monster, and the game ends when the player runs out of lives. The game is an example of the trap-em-up genre, which also includes games like Heiankyo Alien, Lode Runner, Boomer's Adventure in Asmik World, and Space Panic.

As in Mr. Do!, the player can earn an extra life by collecting all of the letters from the word "EXTRA". Regular monsters can be changed into monsters bearing the EXTRA letters by collecting all three keys distributed around the playfield and then picking up a magic shield from the top floor. Monsters in this state are easier to defeat than normal; a simple hammer strike will do the job. After a brief interval, they change back into their normal forms. The game also offers a bonus credit for collecting a rare diamond that appears on the playfield at random intervals.

The cherry blocks are absent from Mr. Do Vs. Unicorns and early revisions of Mr. Do's Castle. Instead, blocks that are not keys or skulls at the start of a stage will be fill blocks (those left behind when unicorns fall into holes and are left alone for a time). Because of this, there are only three ways to complete a level in this version, versus the four ways to complete levels in Mr. Do's Castle. In addition, in these early revisions, the fill blocks change colors every two stages.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Mr. Do's Castle (1983) (Parker Bros)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19841001T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Oil's Well (1984) (Sierravision).zip</path>
		<name>Oils Well</name>
		<desc>The player attempts to manage an oil drilling operation and collect oil, while evading subterranean creatures. The player can advance through eight different levels, using four directional control buttons to move the drill head, and pressing a button to quickly retract it.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Oil's Well (1984) (Sierravision)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840301T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sports/One on One Basketball (1984) (Micro Fun).zip</path>
		<name>One-on-One Basketball</name>
		<desc>Control either Julius Erving or Larry Bird in front of a single basket, in a game of one on one. The user can select to play either to a certain score or for a certain amount of time. When on offense, the player can rotate to keep away from his rival, take a shot from a distance or move in to the basket for special up-close slam-dunks. When on defense, you can try to take your rival's ball or jump up to block a shot. Particularly good set-ups get a slow-motion replay. You can even smash the glass on the backboard, which will send an irate janitor onto the court to clean up the mess.</desc>
		<image>./Sports/images/One on One Basketball (1984) (Micro Fun)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Chris Oberth</developer>
		<publisher>Micro Fun</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Pac-Man (1983) (Atarisoft) (Prototype).zip</path>
		<name>Pac-Man</name>
		<desc>Pac-Man was a prototype game developed in 1982 for the ColecoVision System.  This game was only a prototype.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Pac-Man (1983) (Atarisoft) (Prototype)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atarisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Atarisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Pepper II (1983) (Exidy).zip</path>
		<name>Pepper II</name>
		<desc>Pepper II is an arcade game programmed by Exidy and published in 1982, and, despite its name, there was no predecessor named Pepper or Pepper I.[1][2] Its gameplay is similar to the game Amidar by Konami and Stern.

The game featured Gounod's "Funeral March of a Marionette" when gameplay started.

Gameplay[edit]
There are four mazes per level in Pepper II. Each maze has exits leading to 3 other mazes. All four mazes must be filled to advance to the next level. To fill in a maze, the player maneuvers "Pepper" around different segments of the maze. As Pepper travels, he leaves a "zipper". Once he encloses or "zips" a segment, it fills in and points are awarded. If Pepper backtracks on an uncompleted segment, it unzips.

The character "Pepper" is an angel. There are two types of enemies that must be avoided: "Roaming Eyes" and the " Whippersnapper" who unzips all uncompleted, zipped segments by moving over them. Pepper's one defense is to enclose an area containing a pitchfork "energizer", which turns him into a devil for approximately four seconds. At that time he can go after all Roaming Eyes for points. At the same time, the Whippersnapper freezes. There are four pitchforks in the corners of every maze. A deluxe energizer is located in the center of each maze. This energizer alternates between being a pitchfork and a halo symbol. If Pepper encloses the middle area when the energizer is a halo, the Whippersnapper will disappear from the maze.

Points are made for enclosing a segment, consuming a pair of roaming eyes when energized by the pitchfork (similar to Pac-Man), obtaining prizes, completing a maze, and completing 4 mazes. A bonus turn is awarded at 40,000, 50,000, 70,000 or 90,000 points, depending on the dip switch settings.

Each maze also contains a prize in one of the segments. The player must enclose the area it appears in to gain the prize and points, and then the prize is shown beneath the maze.

Pepper II was ported to the ColecoVision home system.[1]</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Pepper II (1983) (Exidy)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830501T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pitfall II - Lost Caverns (1983-84) (Activision).zip</path>
		<name>Pitfall II: Lost Caverns</name>
		<sortname>Pitfall 2 Lost Caverns</sortname>
		<desc>David Crane's classic platfomer returns in this groundbreaking sequel -- one of the first free-roaming platformer games -- expanding on the original with a complete world of interconnecting caverns full of dangerous traps and terrifying enemies. Face the terrors to rescue your lost daughter and her pet, while collecting treasures from deep within the temple.</desc>
		<image>./images/Pitfall II - Lost Caverns (1983-84) (Activision)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19841201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Pitstop (1983) (Epyx).zip</path>
		<name>Pitstop</name>
		<desc>Pitstop is a 1983 racing video game developed and published by Epyx for the Atari 8-bit family, ColecoVision, Coleco Adam, and Commodore 64. Pitstop was noted for its implementation of a pit stop, a concept not featured in many other racing video games at the time.

Pitstop is played from a first-person perspective, placing the player in the driver's seat of a race car. The game features three difficulty modes and three gameplay modes: Single, Mini-Circuit, and Grand Circuit. In Single, the player can choose from one of six tracks and learn how to play the game. In the game's Circuit modes, the player races against other drivers and earns a certain amount of points and money depending on the place finished in each race. The Mini-Circuit features only three tracks, while the Grand Circuit features all six.

Color-based damage is shown on the player's car whenever it hits another vehicle or a wall on the track, both of which wear out the tires. The player also has a fuel meter that gradually depletes during each race. If the player's vehicle displays a red color from taking too much damage, or if it is running low on fuel, it must make a pit stop. Unlike other racing video games, the pit crew is fully controlled by the player, who must refuel the vehicle and replace its worn-out tires. Up to four players can play by taking alternating turns.

he Coleco version utilizes the ColecoVision's Expansion Module #2 steering wheel/pedal peripheral. The Coleco version features lighter colors and billboards alongside the road rather than trees.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Pitstop (1983) (Epyx)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Epyx</developer>
		<publisher>Epyx, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Popeye (1983) (Parker Bros).zip</path>
		<name>Popeye</name>
		<desc>Climb aboard and join Popeye as you race him through a crazy maze in pursuit of Olive Oyl's falling hearts. The more hearts you help him catch, the higher your score. Of course, it won't be easy with Brutus and the Sea Hag around! Lead Popeye to his spinach in time and it's curtains for this pesky pair. If not - it's into the briny deep for this sailor!</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Popeye (1983) (Parker Bros)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19831005T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Parker Brothers</developer>
		<publisher>Parker Brothers</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Porky's (1983) (20th Century Fox) (Prototype).zip</path>
		<name>Porky's</name>
		<desc>Porky's was a prototype game designed for the ColecoVision in 1983.

Revenge is sweet... and you're out to get it. You've been "had" at Porky's, and you're out to blow it away. The action's hot and heavy and it's up to you to keep Pee Wee on his toes. If he succumbs to distraction, it's the pits! It's more fun than a greased pig... it's a blast!</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Porky's (1983) (20th Century Fox) (Prototype)-image.png</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>20th Century Fox</developer>
		<publisher>Coleco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Power Lords - Quest for Volcan (1983) (Prototype).zip</path>
		<name>Power Lords - Quest for Volcan</name>
		<desc>As superhero Adam Power, you’re the pilot of a space sled on patrol around the explosive Volcan Rock, and what better cover for the bad guys? An enormous laser-eyed space serpent is coiled around the mountain, and you have to take it down single-handedly. Once See the videoyou’ve baked the snake, you land your sled on the surface and have a shootout with Gryptogg, Raygoth and Arkus. Once you’ve beaten them back, you can explore the underground caverns, collecting their instruments of evil and exchanging fire with them again. When you escape from their maze, you advance to the next level and begin the fight anew. (North American Philips / Probe 2000, 1983 – unreleased)

This Colecovision adaptation of the Odyssey2 game (now there’s a phrase you’re never going to see again), based on a less-than-blockbuster-successful series of comics and action figures, adds more depth to the game than the dear old Odyssey ever could’ve managed. But it’s hard to tell how much depth, as the game was never completed.

The “snake” screen, though it’s much more impressive visually than its counterpart on the Odyssey2, is just plain boring. The O2 edition of Power Lords also forced you to dodge earthbound meteors and an “artificial black hole” within the volcano that could drag you to your doom if you got on a horizontal line of sight with it when it opened. On the Colecovision, all you have to contend with are enemy vehicles and a slow-moving snake. It takes more time than effort to clear this screen, and it’s ultimately a bit boring.

The other screens, which aren’t even hinted at in the Odyssey2 version of the game, are also a bit tedious – enemy A.I. and combat programming obviously weren’t finished when the game was abandoned. You can exchange fire with your interestingly-animated opponents, but sometimes they just stop firing and disappear. Convenient, sure, but not terribly exciting.

“Probe 2000” was an imprint – akin to Atari’s “Atarisoft” division – opened by North American Philips to release games for hardware other than the Odyssey2, which was by now firmly into its twilight. The only game actually released by Probe 2000 was War Room, programmed by Bob “RoSHa” Harris (who created Killer Bees on the O2). Probe 2000’s next release would’ve been either Power Lords or the impressive RPG Lord Of The Dungeon (which was left in limbo because its battery-backed-up cartridge, capable of saving the player’s position, was an idea that just wouldn’t be practical until the NES era).  The intellectual property rights to Pink Panther had been snagged by N.A.P. for the Odyssey2 and other systems, but the only version of that game that has ever surfaced has been an incredibly rare Atari 2600 prototype. N.A.P. ultimately got out of the game business, leaving both the Odyssey2 and Probe 2000 behind.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Power Lords - Quest for Volcan (1983) (Prototype)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NAP Consumer Electronics Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>NAP Consumer Electronics Corp.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Q-bert (1983) (Parker Bros).zip</path>
		<name>Q*bert</name>
		<desc>Q*bert is an isometric platform game with puzzle elements where the player controls the titular protagonist from a third-person perspective. Q*bert starts each game at the top of a pyramid of cubes, and moves by jumping diagonally from cube to cube. Landing on a cube causes it to change color, and changing every cube to the target color allows the player to progress to the next stage.</desc>
		<image>./images/Q-bert (1983) (Parker Bros)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Parker Brothers</developer>
		<publisher>Parker Brothers</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Q-bert II (1984) (Parker Bros).zip</path>
		<name>Q*bert's Qubes</name>
		<desc>Q*Bert's Qubes is the sequel to the game Q*Bert and features similar gameplay, but is now in three dimensions. Once again your goal is to change multicolored blocks to a target color, but now you must make sure all three visible sides of the blocks match the target color. You control Q*Bert on the playfield of blocks; Q*Bert changes the colors by jumping to a block which will cause it to rotate in the direction of his jump. Unlike the original game, you don't need to change the colors of the whole playfield, but rather need to form straight line(s) of the target colors, and when you do you can move on to the next round. Of course, to make this task more challenging are a variety of creatures (including a giant rat!) that chase you around the playfield. Each creature is a different color, and if it lands on a block where the top face is the same color then the creature falls off of the playfield, but if Q*Bert gets caught by a creature then a life is lost! As the game progresses, more creatures chase Q*Bert and additional colors are added to the playfield making it tougher to find the target color. There are no longer any discs on the sides of the playfield to carry you to safety, so make sure you don't jump off the edge! To help out, a green ball may appear from time to time; if you catch this, all the enemies become frozen temporarily.</desc>
		<image>./images/Q-bert II (1984) (Parker Bros)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840502T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Parker Brothers</developer>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Robin Hood (1984) (Xonox).zip</path>
		<name>Robin Hood</name>
		<desc>You are Robin Hood in Medieval England and you are trying to enter the Sheriff of Nottingham's castle. Inside the castle, lovely Maid Marian is being held captive by the evil Sheriff, and the Sheriff's gold is locked away in a vault.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Robin Hood (1984) (Xonox)-image.png</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840906T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Xonox</developer>
		<publisher>Xonox</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Roc 'N Rope (1983-84) (Konami).zip</path>
		<name>Roc 'N Rope</name>
		<desc>Roc'n Rope (ロックンロープ?)[1] is a 1983 arcade game developed and published by Konami (published by Kosuka/Interlogic in some markets). The player, a flashlight- and harpoon gun- equipped archaeologist, had to ascend a series of rocky platforms in a Lost World scenario to reach a Phoenix bird, the object of his quest. Along the way he had to avoid ferocious man-sized dinosaurs and belligerent red-haired cavemen against whom he had no direct means of offense. The only ways to defeat the opponents were either temporary (dazing them with the flashlight) or indirect (waiting for them to be suspended on a harpoon rope to make them fall down), an element which added a certain amount of trickiness to the game, unusual for its time. Bonus items to collect along the way included fallen phoenix feathers and phoenix eggs, which granted the player invulnerability from the prehistoric denizens for a short period of time.

Roc'n Rope was ported to the Atari 2600 and ColecoVision. The ColecoVision version was more faithful to the original, while the Atari port was rudimentary at best.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Roc 'N Rope (1983-84) (Konami)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840301T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Rock 'N' Bolt (1984) (Telegames).zip</path>
		<name>Rock 'N Bolt</name>
		<desc>Rock n' Bolt is a puzzle video game developed in 1985 by Action Graphics and published by Activision.

Objective[edit]
The objective of the game is to lock platforms into place according to a supplied map. There are three levels of difficulty; the second and third level have time limits.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Rock 'N' Bolt (1984) (Telegames)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19850201T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Rolloverture (1983) (Sunrise).zip</path>
		<name>Rolloverture</name>
		<desc>The hall is at a hush The maestro takes the baton and readies the orchestra. But wait! All the notes have been scrambled and you must help the maestro scurry madly around the orchestra pit directing the notes back to their proper order Climb ladders, throw levers, reverse the conveyor belt, and step on rollovers to guide the music ball to the correct notemaker slot. Proper placement rewards you with the overture, but incorrect placement results in a speed increase and greater difficulty. A variety of melodies and random scrambling of the notes guarantees to keep your interest, while you painlessly learn about music.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Rolloverture (1983) (Sunrise)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830504T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunrise Software</developer>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Sammy Lightfoot (1983) (Sierravision).zip</path>
		<name>Sammy Lightfoot</name>
		<desc>Go through three levels jumping over obstacles that get in your way. Use trampolines and swings to get to hard-to-reach places and avoid hazards or falling down gaps. Get to the top of the screen in order to proceed to the next level. Once three levels are completed, the game restarts with increased difficulty. Before you start the game, you can access the options screen which lets you customize the screen to include another player, turn off the sound or the scene music, or let either player start at any particular level.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Sammy Lightfoot (1983) (Sierravision)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830505T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sierra On-Line</developer>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Sector Alpha (1983) (Spectravideo).zip</path>
		<name>Sector Alpha</name>
		<desc>SECTOR ALPHA is a three-dimensional arcade-type search and destroy game. Robot penetrator space craft are invading from three directions and you must face and destroy them in each direction of the playing field.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Sector Alpha (1983) (Spectravideo)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Spectravision</developer>
		<publisher>Spectravision</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Sewer Sam (1984) (Interphase).zip</path>
		<name>Sewer Sam</name>
		<desc>It's a lovely day and Sam is waiting in Central Park to meet his girlfriend Sally. He sees her and walks to her. He only has eyes for her and before he realizes it he finds himself in the New York sewer system.

Three Russian submarines have been located in the New York sewer system and they have blocked off the system. Sam's only way out of the sewer system is to destroy the Russian submarines. Luckily, Sam carries his revolver. Sam can't go back... once he's gone through the City Sewer Department seals the tunnel. Luckily, Sam carries his revolver.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Sewer Sam (1984) (Interphase)-image.png</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840308T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Interphase Technologies Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Interphase Technologies Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sports/Skiing (1986) (Telegames).zip</path>
		<name>Skiing</name>
		<desc>The object of the SKIING'. game is to successfully negotiate the course in the feast amount of time.</desc>
		<image>./Sports/images/Skiing (1986) (Telegames)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Telegames, Inc.</developer>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20211019T073958</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Slither (1983) (Century II).zip</path>
		<name>Slither</name>
		<desc>Slither is similar in nature to the hit arcade game Centipede by Atari. You control your snake as it slither's around the screen. Where this game differs greatly from Centipede is that you can shoot in 4 different directions at the same time to take out the baddies trying to hunt you down. The bad snakes hunting you down will appear from various angles on the screen, often several at a time. The game was bundled with Coleco's Roller Controller and can't be played without it.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Slither (1983) (Century II)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830503T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Coleco</developer>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Slurpy (1984) (Xonox).zip</path>
		<name>Slurpy</name>
		<desc>You control a strange green blob of a creature with a long trunk sticking out the front, moving it around in a one-screen, non-scrolling, open cave. In every level, your goal is to eat ten floating seeds. Meanwhile, of course, the game does its best to prevent you from doing so, by throwing a multitude of different monsters against you. Fortunately nearly every monster in the game can be eaten as well. If an enemy touches Slurpy, you can kiss one of your precious lives goodbye; but woe to the enemy that strays in front of Slurpy's trunk and is caught by his amazing suction power!</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Slurpy (1984) (Xonox)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840920T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Emag</developer>
		<publisher>Xonox</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Smurf - Paint 'n Play Workshop (1983).zip</path>
		<name>Smurf Paint 'n' Play Workshop</name>
		<desc>Choose any one of four background scenes and start to add clip-art objects, furniture and free form design. The four scenes are:
-Outside a mushroom house
-Inside a mushroom house
-The River crossing
-Gargamel's Castle

Create any number of decorated scenarios and then use either controller to change into one of four characters: Smurf, Papa Smurf, Smurfette or Gargamel and play around in the graphic you have created. Characters are able to move left, right, up, down... jump and drop.
There is no method of saving your work, so it all disappears when the power goes off.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Smurf - Paint 'n Play Workshop (1983)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840502T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Coleco</developer>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Smurf - Rescue in Gargamel's Castle (1982).zip</path>
		<name>Smurf: Rescue in Gargamel's Castle</name>
		<desc>You control the actions of the SMURF! He must jump over and duck under natural obstacles and avoid the dangerous animals while trying to rescue the Smurfette! She has been captured by Gargamel and only he can save her! Can you get him to the castle in time?</desc>
		<image>./images/Smurf - Rescue in Gargamel's Castle (1982)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19821125T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Coleco</developer>
		<publisher>Coleco</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Space Fury (1983) (Sega).zip</path>
		<name>Space Fury</name>
		<desc>Space Fury (J:スペースフューリー) is a multi-directional shooter arcade game created by Sega and released on June 17, 1981. The game was an early example of color vector graphics and it also featured speech synthesis.[1]</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Space Fury (1983) (Sega)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830301T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Ms. Space Fury (Digital Press) (2001).zip</path>
		<name>Ms. Space Fury</name>
		<sortname>Space Fury, Ms.</sortname>
		<desc>This years’ Classic Gaming Expo and the 10th Anniversary of Digital Press happen to coincide. Obviously, DP wanted to do something special to mark the occasion. What better way than to release an original game for a classic system? Several game developers were contacted, but the job went to Daniel Bienvenu, who had written a few homebrews for ColecoVision (BUSTin Out, Dac-Man). Joe Santulli came up with the title and concept and provided support. A lot of people pitched in to help. Daniel brought in Sylvain (‘Sly DC’) De Chantal to design most of the levels and assist with the graphics. Marcel de Kogel wrote the emulator the game was compiled and tested on. As the project neared completion, Dave Giarrusso designed the artwork for the label and the instruction manual (as well as the full page advertisement shown in the last issue of DP as well as the CGE2K1 show program). Even veteran homebrew author John Dondzila lent his expertise on coding and debugging the program. Most of the communication and brainstorming was done via the Internet through email and instant messenger—something the designers of old didn’t have at their disposal.

Finally, when the game was complete there were ten levels. After the game was downloaded to a ROM, it was discovered that it wouldn’t load an the actual console! After nearly giving coordinator Santulli a heart attack, John Dondzila was consulted and solved the problem. During his testing there were issues that had to be addressed such as heavy flickering and fatal errors. These were eventually worked out, and Santulli survived from near-coronary condition. Ironically when the bugs were fixed it freed up a lot of storage, so an additional ten levels were eventually added. There was not much time left but Santulli, with the aid of fellow CGE organizer and DP guy John Hardie managed to do the soldering and construction of 40 cartridges in time for a Classic Gaming Expo release.

When the scheduled release time arrived at the show a long queue had formed. The games sold out within ten minutes. Even the promotional posters (with Dave G’s artwork) were taken. Most Expo-goers managed to at least play the demo that was set up. Their comments were consistently positive.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Ms. Space Fury (Digital Press) (2001)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>20010101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Press</developer>
		<publisher>Digital Press Publishing</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Space Invaders Collection Pack Demo (2002) (PD).zip</path>
		<name>Space Invaders Collection</name>
		<image>./Other/images/Space Invaders Collection Pack Demo (2002) (PD)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20030101T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Space Panic (1983) (Universal).zip</path>
		<name>Space Panic</name>
		<desc>A game remarkably similar to Lode Runner, you play an astronaut with limited oxygen (time) chased around by various space aliens. Your only method of dealing with these multicolored threats from space is to dig a hole, lure it into a hole and then manually fill up the hole with the alien in it. Dropping aliens on top of other aliens earns you extra points and eliminates both. Levels get progressively harder and enemies grow faster.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Space Panic (1983) (Universal)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830504T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Coleco</developer>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Spectron (1983) (Spectravideo).zip</path>
		<name>Spectron</name>
		<desc>The planetary clust Shalix is plagued by an intergalactic dust cloud that blocked out their sun. Now the Shalix have built a fleet to colonize new worlds. Unfortunately they set their eyes on Spectron, the player's home world. It's up to the player to repel the invading forces from Shalix.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Spectron (1983) (Spectravideo)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830502T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Spectravideo</developer>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spy Hunter (1983-84) (Midway).zip</path>
		<name>Spy Hunter</name>
		<desc>Spy Hunter is a 1983 arcade game developed and released by Bally Midway.[1]

The game draws inspiration from the James Bond films and was originally supposed to carry the James Bond license. The object of the game is to drive down roads in the technologically advanced "Interceptor" car and destroy various enemy vehicles with a variety of onboard weapons. Spy Hunter was produced in both sit-down and standard upright versions with the latter being more common.[1] The game's controls consist of a steering wheel in the form of a futuristic aircraft-style yoke with several special-purpose buttons, a two-position stick shift (offering 'low' and 'high' gears), and a pedal used for acceleration.

Spy Hunter was also ported to various home computers and video game systems. The game was followed by a pinball spin-off, a sequel that added two-player split-screen play and a successor series of games bearing the Spy Hunter name.</desc>
		<image>./images/Spy Hunter (1983-84) (Midway)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Coleco</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Racing, Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Squish 'Em Sam! (1983) (Interphase).zip</path>
		<name>Squish 'Em Featuring Sam</name>
		<desc>Squish'em Featuring Sam lets you assume the role of the title character, a man obsessed with climbing to the top of a 48-story building to obtain a suitcase full of money. As you guide Sam up the side of the building, Creeping Creatures that crawl along the ledges will get in your way. You can jump over them or squish them flat. After avoiding or stomping on a creature, you should climb on up to the next floor. A squished, temporarily harmless creature will soon turn white and resume crawling. White creatures can be jumped over, but not squished.

In addition to encountering creatures, you must keep on the lookout for falling objects. Bricks, hammers, tires, motors, dynamite, fire hydrants, television sets and sinks can bonk you on the head and knock you off the building. At some point along the way, you can pick up a prize that will give you a bonus life. You begin the game with four lives and can earn up to 128 in reserve. 

Sam is a climbing man, but he's also verbose. When he squishes a creature he says "SQUISH'EM!" If he gets clocked by a creature or is conked on the head by a falling object, he lets out a "WHOOPS!" If he manages to snag a prize, he'll say "WOW!" After scaling the building and collecting his monetary reward, he gleefully shouts "MONEY, MONEY, MONEY!"</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Squish 'Em Sam! (1983) (Interphase)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Interphase Technologies Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Interphase Technologies Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Star Fortress by John Dondzila (1997) (PD).zip</path>
		<name>Star Fortress</name>
		<image>./Other/images/Star Fortress by John Dondzila (1997) (PD)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19980101T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Star Trek - Strategic Operations Simulator (1984) (Sega).zip</path>
		<name>Star Trek: Strategic Operations Simulator</name>
		<desc>You are the Captain of the Enterprise as you pilot it through a series of combat simulations against Klingon battlecruisers, Antimatter Pods, and the Nomad Probe.    The top of the screen displays a top down tactical display, while the bottom half is the "main screen" view from the Bridge of the Enterprise.




Klingon Ships are after your starbases that you can use to refuel and repair at.  Defeat them before your bases are destroyed and the Enterprise is destroyed as well.




Most of your focus is on the tactical display, and the main screen is frequently forgotten during intense combat.  As the Enterprise takes damage, systems go offline.  Shields take damage first, than photon torpedoes, then warp engines, and then game over.  The balance of keeping the Enterprise in good fighting trim by avoiding damage and docking at starbases, vs. the bonus received from "unused" starbases at then end of each level is a nice tradeoff as your score goes up.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Star Trek - Strategic Operations Simulator (1984) (Sega)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19841201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Coleco</developer>
		<publisher>Coleco</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Star Wars - The Arcade Game (1984) (Parker Bros).zip</path>
		<name>Star Wars: The Arcade Game</name>
		<desc>It's the challenging action of Star Wars: The Arcade Game.
Here in an exciting home video game featuring 3 different screens !
You're at the controls of Luke's X-Wing Fighter, heading straight for the Death Star.
Your mission: to destroy it before the Empire seeks its revenge on the Rebel base.
Lock your sights on attacking Tie Fighters and blast them with your Proton Torpedoes.
Race along the Death Stat's surface, firing on giant towers.
Finally, dive full throttle into the Death Star's equatorial trench.
You'll need splitt-second timing to avoid all the obstacles as you streak through the trench in search of the main reactor.
Hit it and you've blown the Death Star out of existence !.
Good luck and may the force be with you.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Star Wars - The Arcade Game (1984) (Parker Bros)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>Parker Brothers</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter, Flight Simulator</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Steamroller (1984) (Activision) (Prototype).zip</path>
		<name>Steamroller</name>
		<image>./images/Steamroller (1984) (Activision) (Prototype)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>20000729T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Strategy, Racing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Subroc (1983) (Sega).zip</path>
		<name>SubRoc</name>
		<desc>SubRoc 3-D is a shooter, where you look through a periscope and shoot at both sea and air-targets. The arcade version features 3-D effects.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Subroc (1983) (Sega)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830503T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Coleco</developer>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Tapper (1984) (Midway).zip</path>
		<name>Tapper </name>
		<desc>Tapper is an action game where you're a beer tapper (barman) and have to serve beer to demanding customers. There are four customers, each has its own lane lengthier than the previous one, whom you have to keep at bay. If they reach the end of the lane without receiving their beer, you're a goner; if you miss one and accidentally spill beer needlessly you lose a life and should one of them throw you back the mug and you fail to catch it, you lose a life as well.</desc>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bally Midway Mfg.</developer>
		<publisher>Coleco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tarzan (1984) (Coleco).zip</path>
		<name>Tarzan</name>
		<desc>Both CV buttons are used, one to punch, one to jump. Using the control knob, you can run around the jungle floor, climb up trees, swim in the river, swing from vines, and by hitting one of the numeric buttons, you can let out Tarzan's famous yell. As you cross the jungle, you'll come across captured apes that can be released by punching their cages. As previously mentioned, at the end of each round, you'll come to the temple screen. There are several levels to the temple with a caged ape each. Travel down, free each ape, then head back to the top, there the idol resides. Dodge the idol's fire, hit one of the numeric buttons to let out Tarzan's yell, and the idol will crumble. This ends the round and you start again with increased difficulty.</desc>
		<image>./images/Tarzan (1984) (Coleco)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840509T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Coleco</developer>
		<publisher>Coleco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Telly Turtle (1984) (Carousel).zip</path>
		<name>Telly Turtle</name>
		<desc>Telly Turtle is basically a port of the LOGO programming language with the main character being a turtle. The keypad buttons of the Colecovision are used to issue commands from a selection presented on-screen and eventually, programs can be formed to move Telly Turtle around the screen in a series of directions. Music and Sound Effects are also added into the mix to broaden the programming experience.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Telly Turtle (1984) (Carousel)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840503T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Coleco</developer>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Threshold (1983) (Sierravision).zip</path>
		<name>Threshold</name>
		<desc>Threshold is a simple shoot'em up game. You are in control of a spaceship at the bottom of the screen and have to shoot several formations of enemies at the top of the screen.
To make things more difficult you have limited time in form of a fuel tank which will get refilled after you cleared a number of waves. Besides that, your spacecraft is equipped with a laser that tends to overheat. Every shot makes the heat bar of the laser increase a bit. Once it reached its maximum you can't fire anymore and are forced to wait until it cools down while slowly running out of fuel.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Threshold (1983) (Sierravision)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830504T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sierra On-Line</developer>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Time Pilot (1983) (Konami).zip</path>
		<name>Time Pilot</name>
		<desc>Time Pilot (夕イム・パイ口ツ卜) is a multi-directional scrolling shooter and free-roaming aerial combat arcade game designed by Yoshiki Okamoto, released by Konami in 1982, and distributed in the United States by Centuri. Debuting in the golden age of video arcade games, it is a time travel themed game that allowed the player's plane to freely move across open air space that can scroll indefinitely in all directions.[3][4][5] The Killer List of Videogames included Time Pilot in its list of top 100 arcade games of all time.[6</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Time Pilot (1983) (Konami)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830801T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Tomarc the Barbarian (1984) (Xonox).zip</path>
		<name>Tomarc the Barbarian</name>
		<desc>In Tomarc the Barbarian Senta is being held captive in a magical cage, and Tomarc needs to rescue her! In this action game you will control both Tomarc and Senta simultaneously. Tomarc is lost in a series of caves somewhere searching for his magic sword, and then must locate Senta to set her free. Deadly rats and other dangers must be avoided as you run and jump around the caves. Meanwhile, Senta must defend herself from giant bats and other creatures while trapped in the cage; although she can't move, she is capable of firing magic at enemies to destroy them.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Tomarc the Barbarian (1984) (Xonox)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840410T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Xonox</developer>
		<publisher>Xonox</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Tunnels &amp; Trolls Demo (1983) (Adam).zip</path>
		<name>Tunnels &amp; Trolls</name>
		<desc>Tunnels &amp; Trolls is the second ever fantasy role playing game published. A fantasy role playing game is a game where a leader, usually known as the gamemaster, has created an adventure for a group of friends, and the friends play the game and try to solve the problem or rescue the princess or kill the dragon or whatever. Ken St Andre read and tried to understand That Other Fantasy RPG, and decided that he could invent one that was easier to understand and so T&amp;T was born, over 30 years ago. The game has gone through several editions since then, but it remains popular and is played all over the world. A group of five of us created the latest version: the Deluxe Tunnels &amp; Trolls.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Tunnels &amp; Trolls Demo (1983) (Adam)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Flying Buffalo</developer>
		<publisher>Flying Buffalo, inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Turbo (1982) (Sega).zip</path>
		<name>Turbo</name>
		<desc>Turbo by Sega included with Expansion Module #2. 
You're in control of a high performance race car. Use the steering wheel, accelerator foot pedal, and gearshift to drive to victory! The course includes city streest, tunnels, bridges, and coutry roads. Shift into high gear--accelerate--change lanes! Negotiate twisting curves, pass other cars, avoid spin outs, oil slicks, and other hazards to make it into the winner's circle!</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Turbo (1982) (Sega)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19820101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Tutankham (1983) (Parker Bros).zip</path>
		<name>Tutankham</name>
		<desc>Tutankham (ッ夕ンカ一ン) is a 1982 arcade game developed by Konami and released by Stern in the US. The game was originally titled Tutankhamen, but it was discovered that the full name could not fit on the arcade cabinet, so the title was shortened.[citation needed]

Tutankham is one of six games chosen to appear in the LIFE magazine photo-session conducted at Twin Galaxies on November 7, 1982, featuring video game record holders of the 1982-era, gathered for a group photograph. The Tutankham champion in the photo is Mark Robichek of Mountain View, California.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Tutankham (1983) (Parker Bros)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840201T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Up 'N Down (1984) (Sega).zip</path>
		<name>Up'n Down</name>
		<desc>Fun In The Fast Lane

Drive your Baja Buggy over treacherous miles of deadly roads. Watch out! The course is crawling with opponents who want to make this the last race you run. Beware of killer pick-up trucks, boulders, and swarms of other motoring menaces.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Up 'N Down (1984) (Sega)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840203T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Coleco</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Venture (1982) (Exidy).zip</path>
		<name>Venture</name>
		<desc>Venture is an action game in which you control Winky, the heroic adventurer. Your goal is to collect as many treasures as you can which are scattered throughout numerous dungeons. In each dungeon, there are several chambers which each contain a treasure. Armed only with your crossbow, you need to get past the varied creatures which guard the chamber, snag the treasure, and make it out again. When you collect the treasure from each of the chambers in a dungeon, you can then move on to the next, more difficult dungeon</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Venture (1982) (Exidy)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19820406T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Exidy, Inc.</developer>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Victory (1983).zip</path>
		<name>Victory</name>
		<desc>In Victory, use your Coleco Roller Controller to rotate your ship as the space around you scrolls by, smack your fire button to take out anything that moves and snag a power-up or two along the way to aid in your quest. Similar in style to Asteroids, but with a moving background.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Victory (1983)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830502T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Coleco</developer>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Video Hustler (1984) (Konami) (Prototype).zip</path>
		<name>Video Hustler</name>
		<desc>Video Hustler was a prototype game developed by Konami for the ColecoVision system in 1984. This game was only a prototype.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Video Hustler (1984) (Konami) (Prototype)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Coleco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/War Room (1983) (Probe 2000).zip</path>
		<name>War Room</name>
		<image>./Other/images/War Room (1983) (Probe 2000)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Action, Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./War Games (1983-84).zip</path>
		<name>WarGames</name>
		<desc>Greetings, Professor Falken. Shall we play a game?

This strategic game is based on the popular 1983 movie of the same name, starring Matthew Broderick. It might remind people of Missile Command but the action is slower and spread over six screens which represent different areas of the U.S.A. Enemy missiles, planes, and subs will attack and you must direct your own forces, which include missiles, planes, subs, and satellites, to intercept them. Each type of defense has strengths and weaknesses (missiles are fast but limited in range, planes are slower but have unlimited range). Satellites are a better all-around defense but are only available every so often. Some weapons aren't available in certain areas, and some enemies are resistant to certain weapons, so you must alter your strategy accordingly.</desc>
		<image>./images/War Games (1983-84)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Coleco</developer>
		<publisher>Coleco</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Wing War (1983) (Imagic).zip</path>
		<name>Wing War</name>
		<desc>Wing War is an action game where you control a dragon. Beginning in your underground cave, your goal is to capture a sparkling diamond. To do this, you will first need to unlock the secret passage by bringing a fire, water and air crystal back to your cave. Crystals can be found by exploring the various locations available, usually you will need to destroy one of the many enemies so they turn into a crystal. Fire and water crystals can not be in the cave alone at the same time, an air crystal must be placed between them; so you will need to bring back the crystals in the order fire, air, water or water, air, fire. Once you've done this a super crystal is formed unlocking the secret passage so you can try to get the diamond! Your dragon has a limited amount of energy; being hit by enemies will cause the energy to deplete, and the game ends when all of your dragons have lost all their energy.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Wing War (1983) (Imagic)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830503T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Imagic</developer>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Wizard of Id's Wizmath (1984) (Sierravision).zip</path>
		<name>The Wizard of Id's Wiz Math</name>
		<sortname>Wizard of ID's Math</sortname>
		<desc>Spook needs to escape from the King of Id's dungeons. He slips out but Turnkey is in pursuit. He needs to solve math problems to open the way to his escape.

Wizard of Id's WizMath is an educational game to teach mathematics. Using your joystick, you must move blocks into place so they complete a correct math problem and answer. If you push against a block, you will send it flying until it hits a wall or another block. You can also face a block and hold down the button. While keeping the button down, you can then slide the block as needed. There is a sixty second time limit and you are being pursued by Turnkey. Early levels require only one math problem to exit but later levels require two or more.

Early in the game, you can select a floor on an elevator. The higher the floor, the more difficult the math problems. The game also asks your age. The older you say you are, the higher a floor it tries to start you on, although you can select a lower floor.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Wizard of Id's Wizmath (1984) (Sierravision)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sierra On-Line</developer>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Word Feud (1984) (Xonox).zip</path>
		<name>Word Feud</name>
		<desc>Victory doesn't always belong to the fastest player in WORD FEUD. It's not enough to quickly find a likely word match in the maze and move your window over it. You must also be sure that it is the right word and that means finding the other copy! Remember — even if you think you've found the right word. it might not he the one you want because in each round there is always decoy word there to confuse you The decoy word can even he the same word as the one hidden, but with different colors!</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Word Feud (1984) (Xonox)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Xonox</developer>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Yolk's on You, The (1983) (20th Century Fox) (Prototype).zip</path>
		<name>The Yolk's on You</name>
		<sortname>Yolk's on You</sortname>
		<desc>The Yolk's on You was a prototype game developed by 20th Century Fox for the ColecoVision system in 1983. This game was only a prototype.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Yolk's on You, The (1983) (20th Century Fox) (Prototype)-image.png</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>20th Century Fox</developer>
		<publisher>20th Century Fox</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zaxxon (1982) (Sega).zip</path>
		<name>Zaxxon</name>
		<desc>This fantastic 3-dimensional space battle game puts you in control of a futuristic spaceship! Your ship zooms over an alien asteroid, and dives down to attack the enemy's installations. Your ship must avoid hazardous walls, enemy fire, and other unforeseen dangers! Can you survive and score?</desc>
		<image>./images/Zaxxon (1982) (Sega)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19820601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Zenji (1984) (Activision).zip</path>
		<name>Zenji</name>
		<desc>Zenji is an action/strategy game where you control a rolling face throughout a maze. Each section of the maze can be rotated by the face. The goal is to turn the entire maze green by connecting each section of the maze to the source at the center of the screen. After all sections of the maze have been connected, you can move on to the next, more challenging level. In addition to having a time limit to complete your task, you need to avoid the flames and sparks which wander about the maze. From time to time a number will appear in a maze section and count down from 9 to 0. If you touch the number before it disappears, bonus points are earned. As the levels progress, the mazes become larger, trickier and more flames will appear.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Zenji (1984) (Activision)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19841001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Amazing Bumpman (1986) (Telegames).zip</path>
		<name>Amazing Bumpman</name>
		<sortname>Bumpman, Amazing</sortname>
		<desc>Amazing Bumpman is an Action game, developed by VSS and published by Telegames, Inc., which was released in 1984.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Amazing Bumpman (1986) (Telegames)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>VSS, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Telegames, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cabbage Patch Kids - Adventure in the Park (1983).zip</path>
		<name>Cabbage Patch Kids: Adventures in the Park</name>
		<sortname>Cabbage Patch Kids Adventures in the Park</sortname>
		<desc>It's exercise time! Anna Lee, one of the Cabbage Patch Kids, is warming up for a day of athletic adventures in the park--and she's taking you along! So stretch your muscles and get ready for a workout. This adventure is no picnic!

As you stroll through the park, you'll encounter obstacles they never told you about in the Cabbage Patch. You'll leap onto floating lily pads, jump over cabbages and bouncing balls, and hop over puddles so deep they could float a 
ship. And that's the easy part! By the time you get back to the Park entrance, you'll know just what kind of physical shape you're really in. Are you ready for the workout?</desc>
		<image>./images/Cabbage Patch Kids - Adventure in the Park (1983)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19841201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Cabbage Patch Kids Picture Show (1984).zip</path>
		<name>Cabbage Patch Kids: Picture Show</name>
		<sortname>Cabbage Patch Kids Picture Show</sortname>
		<desc>Gameplay is identical to that of Smurf Paint &amp; Play Workshop, in that players can draw and create their own scenes, or choose from any one of four background scenes and start to add clip-art objects, furniture and free form design.

Create any number of decorated scenarios and then use either controller to change into one of four Cabbage Patch Kids characters and play around in the graphic you have created. Characters are able to move left, right, up, down... jump and drop.

Though you can record your animations and play them back, there is no method of saving your work, so it all disappears when the power goes off.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Cabbage Patch Kids Picture Show (1984)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Coleco</developer>
		<genre>Life Simulation</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Super DK! Junior (1983) (Prototype).zip</path>
		<name>Super DK! Junior</name>
		<sortname>Donkey Kong Junior Super</sortname>
		<desc>Super DK! Junior was a prototype game developed by Nintendo for the ColecoVision system in 1983. This game was only a prototype.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Super DK! Junior (1983) (Prototype)-image.png</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Super DK! (1983) (Prototype).zip</path>
		<name>Super DK!</name>
		<sortname>Donkey Kong Super</sortname>
		<desc>Super DK! was a prototype game developed by Nintendo for the ColecoVision system in 1982. This game was only a prototype.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Super DK! (1983) (Prototype)-image.png</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19820101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Dukes of Hazzard, The (1984) (Warner Bros).zip</path>
		<name>The Dukes of Hazzard</name>
		<sortname>Dukes of Hazzard 1, The</sortname>
		<desc>Driving around in the car known as the "General Lee", you must avoid all sorts of obstacles in an attempt to catch up to Jeremiah Stinge. Beware though as Boss Hog and his police force are trying to chase you. The Duke boys are as usual on the side of right in this scenario and it's Jeremiah who has orchestrated things to put them on the wrong side of the law.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Dukes of Hazzard, The (1984) (Warner Bros)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840502T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Coleco</developer>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/2010 - The Graphic Action Game (1984) (Coleco).zip</path>
		<name>2010: The Graphic Action Game</name>
		<desc>2010: The Graphic Action Game is a puzzle/maze game with elements from 2010: Odyssey Two where the player must save the Discovery from crashing onto the surface of Jupiter's volcanic moon, Io. The player must choose one of about five circuits to work on in one of the ship's critical systems: Engine, Power, Communications, Life Support, and the HAL 9000. Successful power routing of a circuit makes each system slowly come on-line. It takes three powered circuits for minimum function, but four provides more leeway for success. On-Line engines and power can be activated for an orbital boost, but too long a burn will damage circuit components. HAL 9000 can power undamaged circuits you assign to him, although at a much slower pace than the player. Communications allow a powered HAL 9000 to inform you of success/failure at powering a circuit assigned to him. Life Support gives more protection against EMPs damaging powered circuits, which require repair and repowering.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/2010 - The Graphic Action Game (1984) (Coleco)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20211114T152845</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sports/Super Action Baseball (1983) (Coleco).zip</path>
		<name>Super Action Baseball</name>
		<sortname>Action Baseball</sortname>
		<desc>Colecovision's only baseball game and first of the Super Action series, Super Action Baseball was specially designed to work with the Super Action controllers.
Batting is done with an angled view wherein you see your batter in the bottom-left of the screen and the pitcher at center-right. The top part of the screen is reserved for keeping an eye on the bases. As the ball approaches, your player attempts to hit the ball with his bat to send it flying. A successful hit will result in your player having to run around the bases. Running is done with the "wheel" on the top of the Super Action Controllers. Stealing is also possible.

Fielding is simple, using the Super Action controllers, players have 4 buttons to correspond to each base. Thus the ball can be thrown at any of the bases instantly.
Box art is fan made.</desc>
		<image>./Sports/images/Super Action Baseball (1983) (Coleco)-image.png</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19830601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Coleco</developer>
		<publisher>Coleco</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20211114T152508</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Adam's Musicbox Demo (1987) (Coleco).zip</path>
		<name>Adam's Musicbox Demo</name>
		<desc>Adam's Musicbox Demo was created as an interface to test and demonstrate various sounds from the ColecoVision system in 1987.  This game was only a demo.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Adam's Musicbox Demo (1987) (Coleco)-image.png</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Coleco</developer>
		<publisher>Coleco</publisher>
		<genre>Sandbox</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220109T102904</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sports/Super Action Football (1984) (Coleco).zip</path>
		<name>Super Action Football</name>
		<sortname>Action Football</sortname>
		<desc>Another game in the Super Action series that makes use of Coleco's Super Action Controllers. Play against the computer or go head-to-head with a friend over 4 quarters of football action. Step back and throw the long bomb to your wide receiver dancing in the end zone, kick the field goal, or lay down a bone-crunching tackle as you control one of 3 offensive or 3 defensive players. What victory dance will you do as you dive across the goal line in the final seconds of the game?</desc>
		<image>./Sports/images/Super Action Football (1984) (Coleco)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Coleco</developer>
		<publisher>Coleco</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220109T102716</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sports/Super Action Soccer (1984) (Coleco).zip</path>
		<name>Super Action Football</name>
		<sortname>Action Soccer</sortname>
		<desc>Super Action Soccer gives you the chance to be the most accomplished star player of any team that ever was. You will be the goal-keeper diving to make incredible saves, the full back with fierce last minute tackles, the mid-field "general" directing shrewd passes and the centre forward scoring great goals. You will be involved all the time in the most exciting moments of the game. You will score the winning goal!

Team Pixelboy released Super Action Soccer for the North American audience.</desc>
		<image>./Sports/images/Super Action Soccer (1984) (Coleco)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19840501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Coleco</developer>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220109T102808</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Other/Alcazar - The Forgotten Fortress (1985) (Activision).zip</path>
		<name>Alcazar: The Forgotten Fortress</name>
		<desc>In this adventure game you control an explorer who's on his way to fortress Alcazar. To reach Alcazar you are travelling through a countryside of fortresses and you need to collect several items that you can find along the way. Once you enter the Alcazar fortress you have to search for the crown.

The strategy map gives you an overview of the countryside, it's fortresses and your location in it. What perils lurk in these mysterious castles? Which path is quick and safe? The Alcazar castle is three stories high, all other castles have only two stories. To enter a castle you just have to follow the path. Each castle has it's own sought-after objects and these objects are always guarded by the castles main demon. Objects to look for are for example: a rope, a gun, raw meat, water or a raft. Collect them and use them properly to master the legendary Alcazar fortress.</desc>
		<image>./Other/images/Alcazar - The Forgotten Fortress (1985) (Activision)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220115T211147</lastplayed>
	</game>
</gameList>
