<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game id="317" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/10-Yard Fight (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>10-Yard Fight</name>
		<desc>The game is viewed in a top-down perspective and is vertical scrolling. The player does not select plays for either offense or defense. On offense, the player simply receives the ball upon the snap and either attempt to run with the quarterback, toss the ball to one of two running backs, or throw the ball to the one long distance receiver - basically the option offense. On defense, the player chooses one of two players to control, and the computer manipulates the others. The ball can also be punted or a field goal can be attempted.</desc>
		<image>./images/10-Yard Fight (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19851018T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="27281" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Space Invaders.zip</path>
		<name>Space Invaders</name>
		<desc>Attention all Earthlings! Relentless alien hordes have been identified near you. Prevent the dangerous Space Invaders from landing on your territory. Use your cannon to defend against waves of descending alien invaders. Don't let them hit the ground or it's all over for you and the Earth! Destroy them and score points!</desc>
		<image>./images/Space Invaders-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19850417T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tose Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Taito Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1615" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/ALL PRO BASKETBALL (2).zip</path>
		<name>All-Pro Basketball</name>
		<desc>The crowd is roaring and the pressure is on...

You're just a basket away from victory. There are only seconds remaining in the game, and you've got the ball. But you're facing a tough zone defense that's bent on keeping you from scoring.

What do you do? Pass the ball? Try to drive for a lay-up and risk a foul? Or just put everything on the line and take a shot from where you stand? Whatever your decision, it'd better be quick. Because the ref has his hand on the whistle, and the clock is running...</desc>
		<image>./images/ALL PRO BASKETBALL (2)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19891201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aicom</developer>
		<publisher>Vic Tokai</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1027" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Al Unser Jr. Turbo Racing (U) [!] (2).zip</path>
		<name>Al Unser Jr. Turbo Racing</name>
		<desc>Get ready for racing action like you've never experienced it. Because Al Unser Jr.'s Turbo Racing is so much more than just a game you drive. It's a game you design, a game where everything - from the pit crew to the power boost, from the suspension to the speed, right down to the color of the racing machine itself - is in your control.
An entire racing season on the world's 16 toughest tracks lies ahead. Each demands its own strategy; Al Jr. will give you advice before every race. In the pusuit of the season's championship, you can set up and modify your own car, or climb behind the wheel of Little Al's maxxed-out machine.
Great graphics. Astounding action. If you're into racing, Al Unser Jr.'s Turbo Racing puts you into it like no other game around!</desc>
		<image>./images/Al Unser Jr. Turbo Racing (U) [!] (2)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Data East Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1027" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Al Unser Jr. Turbo Racing (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Al Unser Jr. Turbo Racing</name>
		<desc>Get ready for racing action like you've never experienced it. Because Al Unser Jr.'s Turbo Racing is so much more than just a game you drive. It's a game you design, a game where everything - from the pit crew to the power boost, from the suspension to the speed, right down to the color of the racing machine itself - is in your control.
An entire racing season on the world's 16 toughest tracks lies ahead. Each demands its own strategy; Al Jr. will give you advice before every race. In the pusuit of the season's championship, you can set up and modify your own car, or climb behind the wheel of Little Al's maxxed-out machine.
Great graphics. Astounding action. If you're into racing, Al Unser Jr.'s Turbo Racing puts you into it like no other game around!</desc>
		<image>./images/Al Unser Jr. Turbo Racing (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Data East Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1615" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/All-Pro Basketball (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>All-Pro Basketball</name>
		<desc>The crowd is roaring and the pressure is on...

You're just a basket away from victory. There are only seconds remaining in the game, and you've got the ball. But you're facing a tough zone defense that's bent on keeping you from scoring.

What do you do? Pass the ball? Try to drive for a lay-up and risk a foul? Or just put everything on the line and take a shot from where you stand? Whatever your decision, it'd better be quick. Because the ref has his hand on the whistle, and the clock is running...</desc>
		<image>./images/All-Pro Basketball (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19891201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aicom</developer>
		<publisher>Vic Tokai</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="6375" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/American Gladiators (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>American Gladiators</name>
		<desc>American Gladiators is licensed from the popular TV show of the same name. It features a series of events testing players' strength, speed and skill against a trained team of ten 'Gladiators', five male and five female. The female characters are Ice, Gold, Lace, Blaze and Zap, most of them know by their bodybuilding achievements. Main male characters are Turbo, Nitro (he featured several US National TV commercials), Gemini, Thunder and Laser (Mr. Montana on 1986).</desc>
		<image>./images/American Gladiators (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Incredible Technologies, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>GameTek, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1619" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Arch Rivals - A Basketbrawl! (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Arch Rivals: A Basketbrawl!</name>
		<desc>The full-court action between the Arch Rivals is really hot tonight. Here's Mohawk, taking it to the hoop... POW! He just got nailed in the alley with a right cross! FOUL! FOUL! FOUL!
What?! No Foul? That's right. No Fouls. This is basketball where breaking the rules is part of the rules! If you can't block a shot - knock your opponent's block off. If you can't steal the ball - steal his shorts! But don't think these tactics are enough to win. Arch Rivals still requires real B-ball skills like passing, shooting, ball handling, slam dunks, and 3 point shots.
Based on the arcade smash hit, Arch Rivals brings all of its hard-hitting "in your face" action into your home. Whether you're going for a fast break, dodging food on the court, or crashing the boards 'til they shatter, Arch Rivals isn't just basketball... it's a basketbrawl!</desc>
		<image>./images/Arch Rivals - A Basketbrawl! (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Midway Games</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1031" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/BASE WARS (2).zip</path>
		<name>Base Wars</name>
		<desc>While maintaining basic baseball elements of pitching, batting, fielding, and base running, Base Wars adds a fighting element to the game featuring four robot classes; a traditional cyborg that looks more like an android, a tank, a flybot, and lastly a motorcycle. A player's robots can be upgraded with new and advanced weaponry and repaired with money earned for game wins during tournaments.</desc>
		<image>./images/BASE WARS (2)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Ultra Games</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1627" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Bad News Baseball (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Bad News Baseball</name>
		<desc>Looking for a baseball game that will challenge your skills and tickle your funnybone? You've finally found it. Bad News Baseball is the new cartoon-style, outrageously funny baseball game only from Tecmo. It's fast-paced and jam-packed full of new animated cinema displays and exciting action. And now Bad News Baseball has boys and girls teams! Play against the computer, play with a buddy, or use the spectator mode, but you had better get ready to laugh. Featuring 12 boys teams and 12 girls teams, 11 different pitches and Tecmo's famous instant close-ups, all you need is a hotdog and you're ready to play.</desc>
		<image>./images/Bad News Baseball (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1629" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Bandai Golf - Challenge Pebble Beach (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Bandai Golf: Challenge Pebble Beach</name>
		<desc>One or Two players can play a round on this video course modeled after the real Pebble Beach. Each player can select their own handicap. Every one of the 18 holes has familiar golf hazards - bunkers, slopes, and water hazards. You'll also have to contend with some of Mother Nature's hazards like changing wind conditions and Pebble Beach's most difficult obstacle - the ocean.

Once you tee off you'll have all kinds of decisions to make. Check your score card to see how you're doing. The card tells you the distance in yards and par for each hole. The computer gives you a bird's-eye view and cross-sectional view of each hole, as well as close-ups of the green. You select the right club for each shot. Control your shot to get the power, distance, and hook or slice you want on the ball. After you've made your shot the computer tells you what kind of lie you have as well as the remaining distance to the hole.</desc>
		<image>./images/Bandai Golf - Challenge Pebble Beach (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19890215T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tose Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game id="335" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Baseball (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Baseball</name>
		<desc>Baseball is a simple baseball video game made by Nintendo in 1983 for the Nintendo Family Computer, making it one of the first games released for the Famicom. It was later one of the NES's 18 launch titles when it was released in 1985 in the United States. As in real baseball, the object of the game is to score the most runs. Up to two players are supported. Each player can select from one of six teams. Although there is no difference between them other than uniform color, they are meant to represent the six members of the Japanese Central League.</desc>
		<image>./images/Baseball (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19851018T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1634" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Baseball Simulator 1.000 (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Baseball Simulator 1.000</name>
		<desc>Baseball Simulator 1.000 (Choujin Ultra Baseball in Japan) is a baseball game released on the NES, where a player can either control a normal baseball team or an ultra baseball team with super hitting and pitching plays to boost their chances of winning.</desc>
		<image>./images/Baseball Simulator 1.000 (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Culture Brain Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Culture Brain Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1635" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Baseball Stars (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Baseball Stars</name>
		<desc>Baseball Stars, released in Japan as Baseball Star Mezase Sankan ?, is a baseball video game developed by SNK. It was released for the NES in 1989. It became a major hit in many countries worldwide, particularly in the United States, Canada, and Puerto Rico. Baseball Stars was a critical success, often referred to as the best baseball game on the NES platform (and possibly of all-time); as such it became a franchise series for SNK, spawning five sequels, and its "create player" and "create team" functions have become standard features in sports games.</desc>
		<image>./images/Baseball Stars (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19890701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="7816" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Baseball Stars II (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Baseball Stars II</name>
		<desc>Baseball Stars 2 is a 2-player baseball arcade game released by SNK in 1992 for the Neo-Geo console.  A less cartoony console version was released for the NES by Romstar the same year.  Baseball Stars 2 for the Nintendo Entertainment System was distributed by Romstar in 1992.  Changes made from the original Baseball Stars, released by SNK in 1989: Female players are no longer included in any form.  Two additional batting stances. These additional stances are never used for players on custom teams. They will only appear on the pre-made teams' players.  Enhanced pitch control.  Ability to shift field formations when playing defense.  Ability to view your team roster and ratings while in-game.  Sidearm-style pitchers are never generated on custom teams. They can only be hired.  Easier bunting controls; bunts are now retractable. (Hold Down+A to bunt instead of stopping the swing partway through.)  Ability to see lead-offs while pitching/batting.  Six pitchers and four bench players instead of five each.  New music and home run animations. These include the "Power connect" graphic for a two-run home run, an animated graphic of the batter rounding the bases and pumping his fist for a 3-run home run or grand slam, and a similar (yet very rare) graphic including a Yorkshire terrier following the batter for a come-from-behind (usually game-ending) home run in a dramatic situation.  Can no longer name custom teams or rename players on custom teams.  You can still upgrade player using the same 15-point system introduced in the original Baseball Stars. However, the random points you get to disperse to various skills each time you purchase a player upgrade changed from between 1 and 6 to between 1 and 5.  Player upgrades overall are much more expensive while the money received during play has remained about the same. This makes it much more time-consuming to upgrade players to maximum.  You can still fire players and hire players. However, due to the fact you cannot change the names of hired players your hired player will always be named generic names given by the game (examples 'STAR 5', 'ROOK 2', etc.). This can also lead to multiple players sharing the same name throughout the custom teams, even conceivably multiple players on the same team with the same name.  Players can still create leagues of up to 125 games (6 teams playing each other 25 times) and view statistics such as League Standings and Top 10 in Average, Home Runs, Runs Batted In, Earned Run Average, Wins and Saves. (A peculiar glitch occurs when viewing league leaders. The last pitcher listed on any user-created team in "View Team" does not appear in any of the Top 10 leaderboards.)</desc>
		<image>./images/Baseball Stars II (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eikichi Kawasaki and team</developer>
		<publisher>Romstar Incorporated</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1032" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Bases Loaded (U) (PRG2) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Bases Loaded</name>
		<desc>The game allows the player to control one of 12 teams in either a single game or a full season. For single games, there is also a two-player option.
Bases Loaded featured a unique television-style depiction of the pitcher-batter matchup, as well as strong play control and a relatively high degree of realism, which made it one of the most popular baseball games of the early NES.
One unique feature of the game is that the pitcher can provoke a batter to charge the mound. Each team has only one batter (usually the team's best hitter) who can be provoked in this manner, however; it is up to the player to discover who it is.
At the time Bases Loaded was released, few video games were licensed by major league sports. Therefore, the league depicted in Bases Loaded is a fictitious league of twelve teams</desc>
		<image>./images/Bases Loaded (U) (PRG2) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19870626T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1033" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Bases Loaded 3 (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Bases Loaded 3</name>
		<desc>The game is the third installment of the Bases Loaded series. The series spanned three generations of consoles and eight total installments. The original Bases Loaded title was a arcade game that Jaleco ported to the NES. Only the original Bases Loaded was an acrade game; the rest of the series were exclusive to their particular consoles. There are four video games in the Bases Loaded NES series, Bases Loaded II: Second Season, Bases Loaded 3 and Bases Loaded 4. There was also a Game Boy version of Bases Loaded. The series continued onto the SNES platform with Super Bases Loaded, Super Bases Loaded 2, and Super Bases Loaded 3. The final entry to the series was Bases Loaded '96: Double Header, released for the fifth generation consoles Sega Saturn and PlayStation.</desc>
		<image>./images/Bases Loaded 3 (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tose Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1636" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Bases Loaded 4 (U) [!p].zip</path>
		<name>Bases Loaded 4</name>
		<desc>Bases Loaded 4 was Jaleco's last 8-bit entry in the long-running baseball series. The game featured slightly more elaborate animations than its predecessor, and much larger fielders. Removed was the goal to play a flawless game; instead the game featured more traditional modes, including exhibition games and full season play.

Geared more toward faced-paced arcade gameplay than simulation, Bases Loaded 4 was not licensed by Major League Baseball or the Major League Baseball Players' Association. Therefore, it did not feature real American (or Japanese, for that matter) teams or players.</desc>
		<image>./images/Bases Loaded 4 (U) [!p]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tose Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="336" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Bases Loaded II (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Bases Loaded II: Second Season</name>
		<desc>The game is the second installment of the Bases Loaded series. The series spanned three generations of consoles and eight total installments. The original Bases Loaded title was an arcade game that Jalelco ported to the NES. Only the original Bases Loaded was an acrade game; the rest of the series were exclusive to their particular consoles. There are four video games in the Bases Loaded NES series, Bases Loaded II: Second Season, Bases Loaded 3 and Bases Loaded 4. There was also a Game Boy version of Bases Loaded. The series continued onto the SNES platform with Super Bases Loaded, Super Bases Loaded 2, and Super Bases Loaded 3. The final entry to the series was Bases Loaded '96: Double Header, released for the fifth generation consoles Sega Saturn and PlayStation.</desc>
		<image>./images/Bases Loaded II (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tose Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1649" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Bill Elliott's NASCAR Challenge (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Bill Elliott's NASCAR Challenge</name>
		<desc>Bill Elliott's NASCAR Challenge is a simulation of the NASCAR Winston Cup circuit, and thus operates like a racing game.  The gameplay action was always through an in-car perspective.  Players could chose to run single races at each track or run for the season championship.  The race distance was chosen by the player, which ranged from 10 miles to the realistic distance of 500 miles for the superspeedway races.  In the MS-DOS version, the championship consisted of a visit to each of the eight tracks.  In the NES and Game Boy versions, the season championship consisted of each of the four tracks run twice, for a total of eight races.  Championship points were awarded consistent to the real-life Winston Cup of the time.  Both the MS-DOS and Nintendo versions allowed the player to setup the car, with effects to be seen.  Both of those versions also allowed the player to choose whether they would race with the effect of damage on their car or not.  However, a large enough collision with another racecar on the track always would result in the player going out of the race in an out-of-control crash.</desc>
		<image>./images/Bill Elliott's NASCAR Challenge (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Distinctive Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1650" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Black Bass USA, The (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>The Black Bass</name>
		<desc>The rumor is true that they will open the International Anglers Fishing Tournament with a selected 200 professional anglers at your NES. The shadow of the fish appears from the depths of the lake. This is a real simulation game between man and fish. THE BLACK BASS makes a fantasy dream competition come true. THE BLACK BASS will jump up and try to hide at the bottom of the trees in the four different lakes. Now the Tournament is ready to start!

The objective is for the player to catch as many black bass as possible from sunrise to sunset. The player may select a beginner's game or ranking game. A ranking game requires a password. From here, a player may select a location on the lake to start at and begin fishing. Simply tossing a lure out with the desired power will start the process. A fish can be lured in by moving the lure around and if it bites, then the player can try reeling it in. Too much constant reeling leads to the line breaking and the loss of both the fish and the lure.

Between casting rounds, the player can make certain selections. Among the selections available is the option to change the type and or color of lure being used.</desc>
		<image>./images/Black Bass USA, The (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19890901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Another</developer>
		<publisher>Hot-B Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="7822" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Bo Jackson Baseball (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Bo Jackson Baseball</name>
		<desc>It is based on Bo Jackson's baseball career.  An option allows the player to play anywhere from five to nine innings.  Nintendo Power gave this game a 2.8 out of 5 in their September 1991 review while Electronic Gaming Monthly issued a 4.25 out of 10 review in their October 1991 issue of their magazine.  Players can either play in exhibition mode or playoff mode. Either one or two players can participate.  In addition to those options, a CPU vs CPU mode and a CPU vs CPU quick mode are available in order to quicken up a tournament; the purpose is to see the stats of that particular match and quickly end tournaments.  The game uses city names but not the team names because of not having any proper licensing with Major League Baseball.  However, the players are purely fictional and they cannot be edited.  Some of the player names are parodies of real life baseball players (such as Baltimore's "Kenrip" being a not-so-subtle parody of Cal Ripken).  There is even a cheat code that allows players to play as an all-Bo Jackson baseball team.</desc>
		<image>./images/Bo Jackson Baseball (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Beam Software</developer>
		<publisher>Data East Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1661" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Caesars Palace (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Caesars Palace</name>
		<desc>This game allows you to play in the Caesars Palace casino.  You wander around the casino and play video poker, roulette, blackjack, the Big Six money wheel or 3 types of slot machines.  You bet and win chips and then exchange them for money whenever you like.  The interaction is done via a cursor, everything is viewed from first-person perspective.  You come to the casino in a taxi - will you be able to leave it in your own limousine?</desc>
		<image>./images/Caesars Palace (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19921201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Realtime Associates, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin Interactive Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1662" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/California Games (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>California Games</name>
		<desc>Get ready for the gnarliest, most radically awesome sports events under the sun! They're six of California's hottest games. Geared for daredevils - and guaranteed to get your adrenaline pumping! First, pick your sponsor. Then tackle the heavy competition in surfing, rollerskating, BMX bike racing and more. Take risks to score high, 'cause wimps wipe out! Trophies are awarded for single events and overall competition! So grab your gear and go for it. You'll be up to your jams in awesome action. And you just might walk away with first prize!</desc>
		<image>./images/California Games (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19890601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Milton Bradley Co.</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1661" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/CAESAR.zip</path>
		<name>Caesars Palace</name>
		<desc>This game allows you to play in the Caesars Palace casino.  You wander around the casino and play video poker, roulette, blackjack, the Big Six money wheel or 3 types of slot machines.  You bet and win chips and then exchange them for money whenever you like.  The interaction is done via a cursor, everything is viewed from first-person perspective.  You come to the casino in a taxi - will you be able to leave it in your own limousine?</desc>
		<image>./images/CAESAR-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19921201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Realtime Associates, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin Interactive Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1662" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/CALI.zip</path>
		<name>California Games</name>
		<desc>Get ready for the gnarliest, most radically awesome sports events under the sun! They're six of California's hottest games. Geared for daredevils - and guaranteed to get your adrenaline pumping! First, pick your sponsor. Then tackle the heavy competition in surfing, rollerskating, BMX bike racing and more. Take risks to score high, 'cause wimps wipe out! Trophies are awarded for single events and overall competition! So grab your gear and go for it. You'll be up to your jams in awesome action. And you just might walk away with first prize!</desc>
		<image>./images/CALI-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19890601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Milton Bradley Co.</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1246" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Championship Bowling (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Championship Bowling</name>
		<desc>The object of the game is the same as a regular game of bowling; score the highest to win.  The game utilizes factors such as left or right-handedness, spin, power and weight of the ball which can affect the outcome of a throw.</desc>
		<image>./images/Championship Bowling (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19891201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Athena Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Athena Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1669" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Championship Pool (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Championship Pool</name>
		<desc>The game is a straight-forward, virtual version of pool and includes several games: eight-ball, nine-ball, three-ball, ten-ball, fifteen-ball, straight pool (14.1 continuous), rotation, equal offense and speed pool. The player may play against the computer or up to seven other players using the same console using the "Party Pool" (multiplayer) option.  Other gameplay modes include "Tournament" (single-player, computer opponents), "Freestyle" (players make up own game rules) and "Challenge" (single-player, shot practice).</desc>
		<image>./images/Championship Pool (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bitmasters,Â Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Mindscape, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1927" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Dance Aerobics (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Dance Aerobics</name>
		<desc>Dance Aerobics is a chance to get fit by following the movements of an aerobics instructor.

Players use side B of the Power Pad accessory (a floor mat with 12 pads in a 4 by 3 grid) to follow the movements of an aerobics instructor. To succeed the player must press the pads with their feet and hands at the same time as the on screen aerobics instructor. Any missed movements are recorded on a mistake counter and 10 missed movements will fail the level. The routines (a set of repeated movements) start slow and simple with a bit of no-penalty practise time however as the player gets better the routines get more complex with less practices time. Each level has a set number of routines that increase with each level from 4 at the start to a total of 32 on the final level (level 7). At the successful completion of each level the player will get a pass stamp which they can enter later to skip that level.</desc>
		<image>./images/Dance Aerobics (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19890301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TRY</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game id="1294" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Goal! (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Goal!</name>
		<desc>The game has four modes: World Cup, Tournament, Shoot Competition, and Vs. Mode. The object of the game is the same as in real football; one team must score more goals than the other to win.</desc>
		<image>./images/Goal! (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19881222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tose Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1841" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Goal! Two (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Goal! Two</name>
		<desc>Get ready for the ultimate rematch! It's too real! Too fast! Too good to be anything less than the best soccer game ever created for the NES! It's GOAL! TWO, the long-awaited sequel to the original title that set the standard for world class soccer simulation. It's living proof that you can never get too much of a great thing!</desc>
		<image>./images/Goal! Two (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19921101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tose Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1844" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Gold Medal Challenge '92 (U) [!p].zip</path>
		<name>Capcom's Gold Medal Challenge '92</name>
		<desc>Catch the spirit of world-class competition with Capcom's Gold Medal Challenge '92! Train and compete with up to seven friends in 18 pulse-pounding events. Now's the time to really pump up and get physical! Out muscle your friends in Weightlifting and leave them in the dust in the 100 Meter Dash. Make a huge splash in the swim meets and leave everyone else in your wake. Earn a perfect 10 in the Vault and watch as the crowd goes wild! With Capcom's Gold Medal Challenge '92, all the thrills and excitement of world-class competition are right at your fingertips!</desc>
		<image>./images/Gold Medal Challenge '92 (U) [!p]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920605T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game id="350" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Golf (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Golf</name>
		<desc>Nintendo GOLF lets you choose your clubs, change your stance, control your swings - even select the angle of impact! You'll view the hole from both close up and far away, judge the changing conditions of the green, and measure the wind velocity. But watch out! When the wind changes, so does the flight of your ball. With Nintendo's state-of-the-art graphics and realistic game play, you'll really believe you're on the fairways. So play Nintendo GOLF, because there's not a video golf game on par with it anywhere!</desc>
		<image>./images/Golf (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19840501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="8488" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Golf Grand Slam (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Golf Grand Slam</name>
		<desc>Now, in Golf Grand Slam, you'll face all the conditions you would on a real golf course! Learn more about using each of the 14 golf clubs, how to choose a strike point on the ball, and setting up putts - all while you're contending with wind resistance, sloping greens, complex faiways and more. Two training modes have been specifically designed to help you sharpen your golf techniques. Then, after you've mastered those, you can take on the Golf Grand Slam Top 30 Pros in a tournament that will push you to the limit! So if you're ready to enjoy golf and improve your game without leaving home, let's go!</desc>
		<image>./images/Golf Grand Slam (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910131T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tose Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1866" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Jimmy Connor's Tennis (U) [!p].zip</path>
		<name>Jimmy Connors Tennis</name>
		<desc>Jimmy Connors, ranked number one for 159 weeks, holder of eight Grand Slam titles and a record 109 singles titles - more than any other player in history - is the GREATEST tennis champion ever! Now YOU'RE Jimmy Connors battling your way to the number one spot. Enjoy a choice of three court surfaces: grass, hard and clay; three skill levels - beginner, intermediate, advanced; tournament or training mode; play singles matches with one or two players.</desc>
		<image>./images/Jimmy Connor's Tennis (U) [!p]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19931101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NMS Software</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1867" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/John Elway's Quarterback (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>John Elway's Quarterback</name>
		<desc>John Elway's QUARTERBACK is the home video game you've been waiting for. So real you can see the game like a quarterback does, from the line of scrimmage. You call the plays, you throw the passes, run the ball, and make the tackles. It's third down and a long four long yards to the first down that will stop the clock. No time-outs left. The weak side linebacker is lined up inside his defensive end. They're coming! You check-off the play at the line of scrimmage and call for a quick pass to the tight end. He breaks it for a T.D.! Named for the quarterback who twice won the AFC Player of the Year Award, this is the game made for every kid who ever wanted to play the game as well as John Elway!</desc>
		<image>./images/John Elway's Quarterback (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19890301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Tradewest, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="2838" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Jordan Vs Bird - One On One (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Jordan Vs Bird: One on One</name>
		<desc>Michael Jordan of the Chicago Bulls and Larry Bird of the Boston Celtics were the only two players in the game, which allowed the player to participate in a one-on-one basketball game. Mini-games included a slam dunk contest (utilizing Jordan) and a three-point contest (utilizing Bird). Mega placed the game at #7 in their list of the 10 Worst Mega Drive Games of All Time.</desc>
		<image>./images/Jordan Vs Bird - One On One (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19890803T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Milton Bradley Co.</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1897" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Major League Baseball (U) (PRG1) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Major League Baseball</name>
		<desc>Sure you've always wanted to be a professional ball player but have you ever thought about managing? Well, here's your chance to prove yourself both on and off the field.</desc>
		<image>./images/Major League Baseball (U) (PRG1) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19880401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>LJN</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1964" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/NES Play Action Football (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>NES Play Action Football</name>
		<desc>Nintendo takes its game to the gridiron with NES Play Action Football. While Nintendo did not get the NFL license for this one, it did secure the license of the NFL Player's Association, so the 8 teams to choose from (all named after the appropriate NFL cities) are all stocked up with real pro players from the 1989 season. You can even substitute second-stringers for the "skill" positions (QB, RB, WR, TE, and FS/SS) when your starters get tired.</desc>
		<image>./images/NES Play Action Football (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game id="1964" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/NES Play Action FootBall (2).zip</path>
		<name>NES Play Action Football</name>
		<desc>Nintendo takes its game to the gridiron with NES Play Action Football. While Nintendo did not get the NFL license for this one, it did secure the license of the NFL Player's Association, so the 8 teams to choose from (all named after the appropriate NFL cities) are all stocked up with real pro players from the 1989 season. You can even substitute second-stringers for the "skill" positions (QB, RB, WR, TE, and FS/SS) when your starters get tired.</desc>
		<image>./images/NES Play Action FootBall (2)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game id="1963" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/NES Open Tournament Golf (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>NES Open Tournament Golf</name>
		<desc>Whether you're an aspiring amateur or a professional-class golfer, NES Open Tournament Golf puts you right in the thick of a world-class golf tournament. Select your club, check the wind and the lay of the turf, and then drive your way toward winnings worth over one million dollars! Pick from three tough courses: one in the US, one in Japan, and one in the UK. Practice your strokes, then compete against a friend. For the ultimate challenge, tee off against 36 computerized golfers and compete for top ranking. It's all here in NES Open Tournament Golf! So warm up on 18 holes and move up to tournament play. The better the golfer, the bigger the prize. Give it your best shot and go for the big money!</desc>
		<image>./images/NES Open Tournament Golf (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910916T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1965" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/NFL Football (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>NFL Football</name>
		<desc>It's very simple... the NFL is football and this is the only officially licensed NFL game for the NES... the closest thing to "real" professional football that you can play without a helmet and shoulder pads. You can select any of the American and National Conference teams, and if you're good enough, you can take them all the way to the Super Bowl! Team rosters are broken down into positions and individually rated according to skills, with position upgrade packages, player ability handicapping, actual NFL Offensive and Defensive Playbook alignments with audibles and even variable wind direction and strength. You not only coach from the sidelines, you also control all the movements of the players on the field. Run, pass, catch, kick, punt, jump, tackle, block and dive... Refs even call penalties. No matter what kind of fan you are, whether you know the rulebook inside-out or just watch an occasional game on TV... this is the one football game you've got to have!</desc>
		<image>./images/NFL Football (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19890901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LJN</developer>
		<publisher>LJN</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1966" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Nigel Mansell's World Championship Challenge (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Nigel Mansell's World Championship Racing</name>
		<desc>Become a Grand Prix legend in a race for the title of World Champion! The most exciting race driver in the world has teamed up with the greatest racing game producers to bring you the definitive Grand Prix experience. Race the full 1992 season in the superb Canon Williams Renault F1 car. Real-time coaching from Nigel Mansell himself! Experiment with the cars set up to achieve maximum performance for each of the 16 race circuits. Fast and furious race action with actual Renault F1 engine sound FX and superbly detailed graphics. The realism of the racetrack... The power and the glory!</desc>
		<image>./images/Nigel Mansell's World Championship Challenge (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19931001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gremlin Graphics</developer>
		<publisher>GameTek, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
	</game>
	<game id="1976" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Nintendo World Championships 1990 (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Nintendo World Championships 1990</name>
		<desc>Nintendo World Championships 1990 is a Compilation game, developed and published by Nintendo, which was released in 1990.</desc>
		<image>./images/Nintendo World Championships 1990 (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game id="1321" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Nintendo World Cup (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Nintendo World Cup</name>
		<desc>The eyes of the world are upon you. National pride is at stake. Only seconds left and the crowd rises in anticipation of the greatest upset in soccer history. The horn sounds and you've won it all! The coveted world cup trophy is yours! Pick your team and plan your game strategy. Use advanced super moves like the Bicycle Kick or the Super Header. Choose from 13 teams, representing countries from around the world. Defeat your opponents and you're on your way to the prestigious world cup final. Bring the excitement of international soccer home with Nintendo World Cup!</desc>
		<image>./images/Nintendo World Cup (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19901201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Technos Japan Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game id="2794" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/OFFROAD.zip</path>
		<name>Ivan "Ironman" Stewart's Super Off Road</name>
		<desc>Grab the wheel and hit the gas! For the first time ever, race up to 4 players simultaneously with Ivan "Ironman" Stewart's Super Off-Road. Based on the #1 arcade game, this all-out dirt-grinding race is now available for the NES. Watch out for the mud holes, jumps and other obstacles on the 8 different Stadium tracks. From match-offs to spin-outs, Super Off-Road is as close to genuine short-course racing as you can get!</desc>
		<image>./images/OFFROAD-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Tradewest, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game id="2016" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/PUNCH OUT.zip</path>
		<name>Punch-Out!!</name>
		<desc>Punch-Out!! It's 13 tough matches in the minor, major and world circuits that lead to the final challenge - the World Video Boxing Association title fight. The ultimate bout against the newest WVBA Champ - Mr. Dream! Practice your hook and take a quick jab. Try to stay light on your feet as you dance left, then right, dodging punches while you throw your own. Boxers from around the world like Piston Honda, Glass Joe and Super Macho Man are all trying to knock you out of the ring. You've trained for months for this moment. There's the bell. Shake hands and come out boxing!</desc>
		<image>./images/PUNCH OUT-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="2015" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Pro Sport Hockey (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Pro Sport Hockey</name>
		<desc>Pro Sport Hockey is an Ice Hockey game, developed by TOSE and published by Jaleco Entertainment, which was released in 1993.</desc>
		<image>./images/Pro Sport Hockey (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930306T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tose Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game id="1320" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Pro Wrestling (U) (PRG1) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Pro Wrestling</name>
		<desc>It's a reverse bulldog, a double nogin-knocker, a leap off the top turnbuckle - it's pure pandemonium! Welcome to the world of Nintendo Pro Wrestling, where you take on six of the meanest, baddest, most rotten guys around. With names like The Amazon, Giant Panther and Kin Korn Karn. You'll begin the match by choosing a wrestler and an opponent - either the computer or a friend. Then with a flick of the wrist you'll perform drop-kicks, body-slams, head-locks and dozens of other bone-crunching moves designed to annihilate your opponent. But be warned. Each wrestler has his own arsenal of back-breaking moves. Which means you'll have to think fast and move even faster to pin your opponent, hold him for a three-count, and become champion of Nintendo Pro Wrestling!</desc>
		<image>./images/Pro Wrestling (U) (PRG1) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19861021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TRY</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="2026" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/R.B.I. Baseball (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>R.B.I. Baseball</name>
		<desc>No other baseball game gets you closer to playing in the big time than R.B.I. Baseball. Because every one of the ten teams in R.B.I. Baseball contains the rosters and player stats officially licensed from the MLB Players Association. Like real baseball, these skills and stats affect the outcome of every play. Like a real manager, you'll need to make good use of this vital information - and wise strategy decisions - if you want a winning record. R.B.I. Baseball is so intensely realistic, we've added amusing animation and a touch of humor to keep the action light-hearted and fun. You can play against the computer in a nine game season or compete against a friend in your own best-of-seven series. Stop playing with no-names and step up to the plate with real superstars in R.B.I. Baseball!</desc>
		<image>./images/R.B.I. Baseball (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19861210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Tengen</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1404" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/R.B.I. Baseball 2 (Unl) [!].zip</path>
		<name>R.B.I. Baseball 2</name>
		<desc>R.B.I. Baseball first set the standard as the only baseball game for play on the NES to use real players and their stats. R.B.I. Baseball 2 raises the standard to a new level: You get all 26 pro teams, each with a roster of 24 real players. Every player comes with his actual 1989 stats. There's instant replay, as well as new and improved animation, graphics, music and sound effects to make the game come alive. As the manager, you get the designated-hitter rule, switch-hitting, and your own lineup of starters and subs. It's so great, it's approved by the Major League Baseball Players Association!</desc>
		<image>./images/R.B.I. Baseball 2 (Unl) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19871222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tengen</developer>
		<publisher>Tengen</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game id="2027" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/R.B.I. Baseball 3 (Unl) [!].zip</path>
		<name>R.B.I. Baseball 3</name>
		<desc>R.B.I. Baseball 3 is a Baseball Sim game, developed and published by Tengen, which was released in 1991.</desc>
		<image>./images/R.B.I. Baseball 3 (Unl) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19881220T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tengen</developer>
		<publisher>Tengen</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game id="8525" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Roger Clemens' MVP Baseball (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Roger Clemens' MVP Baseball</name>
		<desc>Join one of the most dominant pitchers in baseball history for Roger Clemens' MVP Baseball. While the game does not come with the license of Major League Baseball or the MLBPA, there are still 26 similar teams with rosters resembling those of their actual MLB counterparts, including 1991 statistics. Though player names could not be used, the fictional ones make it apparent who each player represents. For instance, you can strike out one of Oakland's Bash brothers (M. Bash or J. Bash) with Texas' R. Nolan or hit a home run with Detroit's C. Fieldman off of Chicago's M. Gaddox. 

The gameplay of Roger Clemens differs from that of most NES baseball games. Though the batting scenes may resemble those typified by R.B.I. Baseball and Major League Baseball, the view switches to what one might see from the outfield stands once the ball is hit. This results in different controls from most baseball games as well.

A player can challenge a friend or the computer, and one-player games may be exhibition or part of a 33-game season, complete with playoffs once the season is complete. In order to help make your season a successful one, Roger Clemens himself is there to offer advice.</desc>
		<image>./images/Roger Clemens' MVP Baseball (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19911001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
		<publisher>LJN</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game id="2030" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Racket Attack (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Racket Attack</name>
		<desc>This is no amateur hour. This one's for keeps. The national finals. Will you play tough enough to hear the umpire call "point, set, match!" A million eyes bore into you from the stands. Moments to start... RACKET ATTACK has made you a pro, the toughest, most awesome champ ever to hit center court. You've a power serve and a ferocious backhand. You're fearsome at the net and in the backcourt. On clay or grass you attack. But your opponent knows your game. And he's ready. Screams go up as you step to the base line. It's 100 degrees. Your service. You launch it like a rocket. Ace... Let... Fault! The umpires' call reminds you to hang tough and be consistent. 15 love... 30 love... 40 love... MATCH POINT. Sweating, you grip your racket. The crowd hushes. Can you deliver an ace? Bear down. Psych up. Get tough!</desc>
		<image>./images/Racket Attack (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19880415T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tose Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game id="2032" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Rad Racket - Deluxe Tennis II (Unl) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Rad Racket: Deluxe Tennis II</name>
		<desc>Six of the best international players have gathered to compete for a fortune in cash, plus the prestige that comes with winning the RAD RACKET trophy. The competition is fierce. You've fought long and hard to get this far. You're gonna have to keep on winning tomake it to the top. Play singles or team up with a friend and play doubles. Either way you will experience the thrill of victory or the agony of defeat as you face off in a test for the best.</desc>
		<image>./images/Rad Racket - Deluxe Tennis II (Unl) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Idea-Tek</developer>
		<publisher>American Video Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game id="8525" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Roger Clemens MVP Baseball (2).zip</path>
		<name>Roger Clemens' MVP Baseball</name>
		<desc>Join one of the most dominant pitchers in baseball history for Roger Clemens' MVP Baseball. While the game does not come with the license of Major League Baseball or the MLBPA, there are still 26 similar teams with rosters resembling those of their actual MLB counterparts, including 1991 statistics. Though player names could not be used, the fictional ones make it apparent who each player represents. For instance, you can strike out one of Oakland's Bash brothers (M. Bash or J. Bash) with Texas' R. Nolan or hit a home run with Detroit's C. Fieldman off of Chicago's M. Gaddox. 

The gameplay of Roger Clemens differs from that of most NES baseball games. Though the batting scenes may resemble those typified by R.B.I. Baseball and Major League Baseball, the view switches to what one might see from the outfield stands once the ball is hit. This results in different controls from most baseball games as well.

A player can challenge a friend or the computer, and one-player games may be exhibition or part of a 33-game season, complete with playoffs once the season is complete. In order to help make your season a successful one, Roger Clemens himself is there to offer advice.</desc>
		<image>./images/Roger Clemens MVP Baseball (2)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19911001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
		<publisher>LJN</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game id="2056" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Roundball - 2-on-2 Challenge (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Roundball: 2 on 2 Challenge</name>
		<desc>Playground basketball goes big time with Roundball: 2-on-2 Challenge. Just imagine half-court, two-on-two (or one-on-one) basketball in an arena setting, complete with a scoreboard and an excited crowd. Your view of the playing area is all encompassing from the half-court line at the bottom of the screen to the basket itself as you near the top. Choose from the players available to customize your own team as you pass, block, steal, dunk, and shoot three-pointers on your way to victory. You can even shoot free throws should the other team foul you. If you think you're good enough, play Tournament Mode and take home the Roundball championship.</desc>
		<image>./images/Roundball - 2-on-2 Challenge (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Park Place Productions</developer>
		<publisher>Mindscape, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game id="2098" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Soccer (JU) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Soccer</name>
		<desc>The objective is to kick the ball into the opponent's goal. The game features cheerleaders and the ability to choose between 15, 30, and 45-minutes halves. Pressing B passes the ball, while A shoots at the opponent's goal.

There are seven teams represented in the game:
BRA -  Brazil
ESP -  Spain
FRA -  France
FRG -  West Germany
GBR -  England
JPN -  Japan
USA -  United States</desc>
		<image>./images/Soccer (JU) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19850409T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="2123" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Super Sprint (Unl) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Super Sprint</name>
		<desc>Super Sprint is a racing game for one or two players. Gameplay is from an overhead view of the racetrack. The racetracks start simple and gradually get more complicated, and may also feature obstacles ranging from traffic cones to tornadoes. Occasionally wrenches will appear in the roadway, and when collected they can be used after a race to power up your car with better tires, better acceleration or a higher top speed.</desc>
		<image>./images/Super Sprint (Unl) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>Tengen</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1457" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Super Dodge Ball (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Super Dodge Ball</name>
		<desc>This ain't elementary school and it sure as heck ain't gym class.  This is Super Dodge Ball.  Control your team of six players to pummel the opposing team into submission using only the ball and your team's unique skills.  Each player has his own special attacks and each team has their own unique attributes.</desc>
		<image>./images/Super Dodge Ball (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19890601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Technos</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Imagesoft</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42048" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Softball Tengoku (J) [T+Eng1.1_Toma].zip</path>
		<name>Softball Tengoku</name>
		<desc>With 60 characters with different abilities and appearance, this is softball unlike you ever experienced before. Batter, pitch, catch, get the team you create to the big leagues.

With different stages and unique abilities, no match is ever the same!</desc>
		<image>./images/Softball Tengoku (J) [T+Eng1.1_Toma]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19891027T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tose Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Tonkin House</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1904" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/T&amp;C 2 - Thrilla's Surfari (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Town &amp; Country Surf Designs II: Thrilla's Surfari</name>
		<desc>Whoa, Thrilla Gorilla! Bag your boards and lay back tall for the raddest, weirdest surf and skate action ever! Wazula, an evil Kahuna, has stolen your babe and taken her to Africa. No curbs and quarter-pipes here, just the ultimate skate challenge of gnarly jungles and bakin' deserts! It's hardcore surfin' down killer volcanoes and mammoth waterfalls... ever catch a wave riding a shark? Wazula's got some smooth moves of his own, like a two-headed flying Rhino, a saw-toothed Great White, and a way-tough Lava Monster big as a volcano. So get rippin' through the scorpions, slashin' through the rapids, and trash that Wazula doofus! But don't choke, Thrilla... or your babe's toast.</desc>
		<image>./images/T&amp;C 2 - Thrilla's Surfari (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
		<publisher>LJN</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1461" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/T&amp;C Surf Design (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Town &amp; Country Surf Designs: Wood &amp; Water Rage</name>
		<desc>O.K. dudes, the time has come to really get radical.  You and the rest of "Da Boys", T&amp;C's famous group of skate and surf crazies, can kick out and pull off some awesome maneuvers together.  Whether you're jammin' the ramps, jumping the cracks, riding the rails or just laying back tall, the skate action is hotter than hot!</desc>
		<image>./images/T&amp;C Surf Design (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19880201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LJN</developer>
		<publisher>LJN</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1383" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/TECMObowl.zip</path>
		<name>Tecmo Bowl</name>
		<desc>TECMO BOWL! You've trained for it in the arcade. Now, strap on your helmet and go for it! Choose your team and select plays for your own game plan. From the snap, total control of every pass, block, run, and tackle is in your hands. Tecmo Bowl! The game of guts and glory!</desc>
		<image>./images/TECMObowl-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19890201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1383" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Tecmo Bowl (U) (PRG1) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Tecmo Bowl</name>
		<desc>TECMO BOWL! You've trained for it in the arcade. Now, strap on your helmet and go for it! Choose your team and select plays for your own game plan. From the snap, total control of every pass, block, run, and tackle is in your hands. Tecmo Bowl! The game of guts and glory!</desc>
		<image>./images/Tecmo Bowl (U) (PRG1) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19890201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1421" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Tag Team Wrestling (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Tag Team Wrestling</name>
		<desc>You are challenged to match the awesome skill of your opponents...to gain the Title in World Super Championship of Tag Team Wrestling. Teamwork and stamina are the keys, as you and your partner battle your way through the Title Matches on your quest for the Belt.

Attack your opponents with Body Slams, Drop Kicks, Backbreakers, Flying Head Butts, or even throwing them out of the ring! To win, it's a pin for a count of three.

Nothing can match the super excitement as the crowd cheers over this mania on the mat. Prepare yourself for Tag Team Wrestling! Data East brings you arcade realism at home!</desc>
		<image>./images/Tag Team Wrestling (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19861001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Technos Japan Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Data East Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="2130" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Tecmo Baseball (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Tecmo Baseball</name>
		<desc>Gameplay is similar to the many other baseball released for the NES. The camera angle when batting or pitching is from behind the pitcher. The pitcher can pitch the ball high and low, as well as curve it. Tecmo Baseball includes digitized voices for the umpire.</desc>
		<image>./images/Tecmo Baseball (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game id="2131" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Tecmo Cup - Soccer Game (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Tecmo Cup Soccer Game</name>
		<desc>Tecmo Cup is a soccer simulator combined with RPG elements. As the game progress, Robin and his teammates will get better. The matches themselves consist of numerous choices what to do at each moment. If you are attacking, you have options to pass, shoot or to dribble. And when you are defending, you can either tackle, cut pass/shoot, or mark the opposition player with ball.</desc>
		<image>./images/Tecmo Cup - Soccer Game (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game id="2132" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Tecmo NBA Basketball (U) (PRG0) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Tecmo NBA Basketball</name>
		<desc>This basketball game is very similar to Tecmo Super NBA Basketball with the main difference being their rosters. The game has 27 NBA teams with a roster of 324 Players. Each player has a rating for his shooting ability, stamina, jumping power, running speed, stealing ability, and blocking ability. The game allows for pre-season and season modes. In the season modes the game tracks team &amp; player statistics throughout the season.</desc>
		<image>./images/Tecmo NBA Basketball (U) (PRG0) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19921101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game id="1905" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Tecmo Super Bowl (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Tecmo Super Bowl</name>
		<desc>The teams, the players, and the halftime shows are ready for the ultimate football season, and you're in control. From the first pre-season game to the playoffs, it's your call, your skill, and your team. Can you get to and win the Super Bowl? Tecmo Super Bowl is the only football game to feature onside kicks, blocked passes and kicks, fumbles, pitchout to the running back, player injuries, time-outs, and much, much more! For 1 or 2 players. All 28 NFL teams! Four running plays, four passing plays. Team stats and data. Create your own Pro Bowl. Coach Mode, where you call the plays!</desc>
		<image>./images/Tecmo Super Bowl (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19911201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1422" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Tecmo World Wrestling (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Tecmo World Wrestling</name>
		<desc>It's your call from the opening bell to the final pin. Select your wrestler and take on any challenge. Every bodyslam, every cobra twist and piledriver brings you closer to victory. Will you be the one receiving the Tecmo World Wrestling Championship Belt?</desc>
		<image>./images/Tecmo World Wrestling (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="11771" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Top Players' Tennis - Featuring Chris Evert &amp; Ivan Lendl (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Top Players' Tennis</name>
		<desc>Top Players Tennis is a Tennis game, developed by Home Data and published by Asmik Corporation of America, which was released in 1990.
In single-player mode, the player may compete in the four Grand Slams: the Australian Open, the French Open, Wimbledon, and the US Open. To compete in the Grand Slams, the player must first win the qualifying tournament, the Asmik Open.
With a multiplayer console accessory such as the NES Satellite or NES Four Score, Top Players' Tennis accommodates up to four simultaneous players. Singles, doubles, or mixed doubles are all available for play.</desc>
		<image>./images/Top Players' Tennis - Featuring Chris Evert &amp; Ivan Lendl (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Home Data</developer>
		<publisher>Asmik Corp. of America</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game id="2148" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Touch Down Fever (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Touchdown Fever</name>
		<desc>Touchdown Fever is an arcade football game from SNK. Go head-to-head against the computer or a human opponent, or team up with another human player vs. the computer. Choose five, ten, or fifteen minute quarters for either league match (single game) or tournament play.</desc>
		<image>./images/Touch Down Fever (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game id="325" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Track &amp; Field (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Track &amp; Field</name>
		<desc>This ain't no 20-minute workout. It's the ultimate in head-to-head competition, in 8 grueling events. 100 meter dash. Long jump. Hurdles. Javelin. Skeet shooting. Triple jump. Archery. And the high jump. No timeouts, no breathers, no water boys. Just you and your own exhaustion. So get psyched. Pick your level of competition and the opening event. Then block out the roar of the crowd and take a deep breath. Because it's not whether you win or lose. It's whether you survive!</desc>
		<image>./images/Track &amp; Field (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19870420T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="324" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Track &amp; Field 2 (U) (PRG1) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Track &amp; Field II</name>
		<desc>The greatest athletes from around the world have gathered for the grandest sporting spectacle since the golden age of Greece. This pressure-packed competition is as fierce as a starved lion. Surviving is a matter of sweat and concentration in Taekwondo, pole vaulting, canoeing, skeet shooting, hammer throwing, high diving, archery, hurdles, gymnastics, hang gliding, pistol firing, arm wrestling, fencing, triple jumping and swimming... Whew! Wears you out just to read them all. The odds in Vegas say you don't have enough strength, stamina or skill, but you know better. And as long as you win, you're the crowd favorite. But lose, and you might as well turn in your jockstrap and joystick.</desc>
		<image>./images/Track &amp; Field 2 (U) (PRG1) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19890601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1458" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/VBALL.zip</path>
		<name>Super Spike V'Ball</name>
		<desc>Warm up with a few exercise games then face contenders in the American Circuit. For the ultimate challenge play against the best in the World Cup. Jump and block opponent's spikes, dive to dig a cross court spike, or set one up for a smash that only the best player can return. Kabooom! Your Super Spike blasts your opponent off his feet! "X" marks the spot so you can track the ball. Pick players with speed, strong defense, or killer offense. Your quick reflexes and competitive spirit complete the team. Play against the computer, by yourself or challenge a friend. With the NES Satellite or the NES Four Score any combination of one to four can play - even two vs. two! Now you can play on sand courts from Daytona to Los Angeles. Face off international teams in Hawaii or challenge the hot Navy team aboard an aircraft carrier. Watch the sand fly! Hear the applause. Soak up the rays! It's Super Spike V'Ball for World Class fun!</desc>
		<image>./images/VBALL-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Technos Japan Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game id="2165" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Venice Beach Volleyball (Unl) [!p].zip</path>
		<name>Venice Beach Volleyball</name>
		<desc>Venice Beach Volleyball is no doubt the coolest video game under the hot summer sun. Check it out! We took miles of clear blue sky, warm sand, along with millions of gnarly 8-foot waves, mixed in dudes, babes, and one ton of pure fun, then crammed the whole thing with the maximum amount of challenge and excitement allowable by federal law. Here you have it, the most excellent beach volleyball game ever! Locals say kicking the butt of a computer controlled team is never easy without a lot of practice. You haven't seen anything until you challenge a friend head to head in competitive double player action mode. Way rad beach volleyball action, blazing 8-bit graphics and killer tunes. That's what VENICE BEACH VOLLEYBALL is all about!</desc>
		<image>./images/Venice Beach Volleyball (Unl) [!p]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Idea-Tek</developer>
		<publisher>American Video Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game id="2168" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Volleyball (UE) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Volleyball</name>
		<desc>Volleyball is an action game for one or two players. Choose a country to represent, choose a mens or womens team, then head to the court to begin! You can serve, set the ball for a teammate, spike, lob, or dive to save the game.</desc>
		<image>./images/Volleyball (UE) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game id="1321" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/WORLDCUP.zip</path>
		<name>Nintendo World Cup</name>
		<desc>The eyes of the world are upon you. National pride is at stake. Only seconds left and the crowd rises in anticipation of the greatest upset in soccer history. The horn sounds and you've won it all! The coveted world cup trophy is yours! Pick your team and plan your game strategy. Use advanced super moves like the Bicycle Kick or the Super Header. Choose from 13 teams, representing countries from around the world. Defeat your opponents and you're on your way to the prestigious world cup final. Bring the excitement of international soccer home with Nintendo World Cup!</desc>
		<image>./images/WORLDCUP-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19901201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Technos Japan Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game id="10252" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/WWF King of the Ring (U).zip</path>
		<name>WWF King of the Ring</name>
		<desc>It's the event that everyone is talking about --- The King of the Ring --- and now it's time to prove you're the best!  It's a brutal, no time out elimination tournament for the wrestling crown!

»  All-New King of the Ring Tournament?
»  10 of the hottest superstars
»  Create your own wrestler with customizes strength, speed, and more
»  Grueling One-on-One and tag team bouts

If you've got the guts...take the challenge.

If you've got the skill...TAKE THE CROWN!!</desc>
		<image>./images/WWF King of the Ring (U)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19931101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eastridge Technology</developer>
		<publisher>LJN</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1391" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/WCW World Championship Wrestling (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>WCW: World Championship Wrestling</name>
		<desc>Challenge the world's greatest wrestlers in the grappling action game that puts you in the toughest competition of all!  Choose which wrestler you want to be or make up your own tag team from top NWA stars including:  "Nature Boy" Ric Flair, Sting, "Total Package" Lex Luger, Ricky "The Dragon" Steamboat, Road Warriors "Hawk" and "Animal," and "Dogface Gremlin" Rick Steiner.  Become your favorite wrestler as you battle it out in the ring!

»  Twelve top stars of the NWA
»  Pair up your own tag team with any two wrestlers
»  1 or 2 player
»  Wrestlers are thrown over the ropes and continue fighting out of the ring
»  On-screen statistics of each wrestler
»  Exciting animated graphics and realistic sound effects</desc>
		<image>./images/WCW World Championship Wrestling (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nihon Bussan Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>FCI</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="10252" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/WWF King of the Ring (U) [!p].zip</path>
		<name>WWF King of the Ring</name>
		<desc>It's the event that everyone is talking about --- The King of the Ring --- and now it's time to prove you're the best!  It's a brutal, no time out elimination tournament for the wrestling crown!

»  All-New King of the Ring Tournament?
»  10 of the hottest superstars
»  Create your own wrestler with customizes strength, speed, and more
»  Grueling One-on-One and tag team bouts

If you've got the guts...take the challenge.

If you've got the skill...TAKE THE CROWN!!</desc>
		<image>./images/WWF King of the Ring (U) [!p]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19931101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eastridge Technology</developer>
		<publisher>LJN</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1604" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/WWF WrestleMania - Steel Cage Challenge (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>WWF WrestleMania: Steel Cage Challenge</name>
		<desc>Accept the toughest challenge in all of wrestling: the WWF® Wrestlemania® Steel Cage Challenge®! You control every action-packed move and manoeuvre - Clothesline, Elbowdrops, Bodyslams, Dropkicks. When you're ready for the ultimate wrestling challenge, the steel cage is ready for you.</desc>
		<image>./images/WWF WrestleMania - Steel Cage Challenge (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
		<publisher>LJN</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1604" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/WWF Steel Cage Challenge (U).zip</path>
		<name>WWF WrestleMania: Steel Cage Challenge</name>
		<desc>Accept the toughest challenge in all of wrestling: the WWF® Wrestlemania® Steel Cage Challenge®! You control every action-packed move and manoeuvre - Clothesline, Elbowdrops, Bodyslams, Dropkicks. When you're ready for the ultimate wrestling challenge, the steel cage is ready for you.</desc>
		<image>./images/WWF Steel Cage Challenge (U)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
		<publisher>LJN</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="2186" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/WWF WrestleMania (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>WWF WrestleMania</name>
		<desc>You`ve always dreamed of being Hulk Hogan or Randy "Macho Man" Savage. Or one of the other WWF Superstars. And now here`s your chance!

Challenge your opponent to a rough and tumble match featuring dropkicks, headlocks, bodyslams and a whole arsenal of bone-crunching wrestling moves!

Or create your own WWF Wrestlemania tournament and compete against your friends or the computer to crown the undisputed WWF Champion!

So put on your wrestling trunks, step into the ring and ready to experience WWF WrestleMania. . . from the inside!</desc>
		<image>./images/WWF WrestleMania (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="2186" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/WWF Wrestlemania (U).zip</path>
		<name>WWF WrestleMania</name>
		<desc>You`ve always dreamed of being Hulk Hogan or Randy "Macho Man" Savage. Or one of the other WWF Superstars. And now here`s your chance!

Challenge your opponent to a rough and tumble match featuring dropkicks, headlocks, bodyslams and a whole arsenal of bone-crunching wrestling moves!

Or create your own WWF Wrestlemania tournament and compete against your friends or the computer to crown the undisputed WWF Champion!

So put on your wrestling trunks, step into the ring and ready to experience WWF WrestleMania. . . from the inside!</desc>
		<image>./images/WWF Wrestlemania (U)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="2187" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/WWF WrestleMania Challenge (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>WWF WrestleMania Challenge</name>
		<desc>Get ready for the greatest in powerhouse action --- both in and out of the ring. Go head-to-head with either of the biggest WWF Superstars.

Can you survive the Atomic Drop, Warrior Wallop, the Hulkster Splash, the Sleeperhold and the Rude Awakening? Fight back with some classic moves of your own --- like Flying Turnbuckle Leaps, Headbutts, Elbow Smashes and more!

Choose Between:
» Singles and tag team matches (even double-teaming!)

» Incredible 3-on-3 Survivor Series® mode

»1 and 2 player head-to-head and team-play action

You can even enter the ring as "yourself" and prove to the world that there's only one true WWF Champion --- you!</desc>
		<image>./images/WWF WrestleMania Challenge (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>LJN</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="2187" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/WWF Wrestlemania Challenge (U).zip</path>
		<name>WWF WrestleMania Challenge</name>
		<desc>Get ready for the greatest in powerhouse action --- both in and out of the ring. Go head-to-head with either of the biggest WWF Superstars.

Can you survive the Atomic Drop, Warrior Wallop, the Hulkster Splash, the Sleeperhold and the Rude Awakening? Fight back with some classic moves of your own --- like Flying Turnbuckle Leaps, Headbutts, Elbow Smashes and more!

Choose Between:
» Singles and tag team matches (even double-teaming!)

» Incredible 3-on-3 Survivor Series® mode

»1 and 2 player head-to-head and team-play action

You can even enter the ring as "yourself" and prove to the world that there's only one true WWF Champion --- you!</desc>
		<image>./images/WWF Wrestlemania Challenge (U)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>LJN</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="2173" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/Wayne Gretzky Hockey (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>Wayne Gretzky Hockey</name>
		<desc>Just like in real hockey, Wayne Gretzky Hockey includes the following features: icing, injuries, passing the puck, off-sides, player changes, six player positions per team, the crease, blue lines, the center line, the center spot and the center circle. Penalties, such as charging, holding, tripping, cross-checking, elbowing, high sticking, hooking, roughing, spearing and slashing, are also part of the action.</desc>
		<image>./images/Wayne Gretzky Hockey (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bethesda Softworks</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game id="2184" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/World Champ (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>World Champ</name>
		<desc>World Champ is a boxing game that has many similarities to Data East's Ring King. You can play a one player "Ranking" mode, where you can build your boxer's stats up while climbing the ladder to eventually challenge for a championship in one of the four weight classes. There is also a two player vs. mode where you and a friend can square off. A tournament mode allows up to 8 players participate in a bracketed tournament.</desc>
		<image>./images/World Champ (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visco Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Romstar Incorporated</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
	</game>
	<game id="21564" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/World Class Track Meet (U) (PRG1) [!].zip</path>
		<name>World Class Track Meet</name>
		<desc>Re-release of Stadium Events, which turns your home into an exciting stadium, dares you to increase your physical ability and better your athletic record. You'll compete against a runner in the Tournament Mode, and in 4 events for a total score in the Olympic Mode. The top 6 winners' names and their scores will appear on the electronic billboard. The top 3 winners will stand on the winners platform!</desc>
		<image>./images/World Class Track Meet (U) (PRG1) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19881001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game id="2185" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/World Games (U) [!].zip</path>
		<name>World Games</name>
		<desc>The events available include:

Weightlifting (Russia)
Slalom skiing (France)
Log rolling (Canada)
Cliff diving (Mexico)
Caber toss (Scotland)
Bull riding (United States)
Barrel jumping (Germany)
Sumo Wrestling (Japan)</desc>
		<image>./images/World Games (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19880301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Milton Bradley</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game id="2186" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/WrestleMania.zip</path>
		<name>WWF WrestleMania</name>
		<desc>You`ve always dreamed of being Hulk Hogan or Randy "Macho Man" Savage. Or one of the other WWF Superstars. And now here`s your chance!

Challenge your opponent to a rough and tumble match featuring dropkicks, headlocks, bodyslams and a whole arsenal of bone-crunching wrestling moves!

Or create your own WWF Wrestlemania tournament and compete against your friends or the computer to crown the undisputed WWF Champion!

So put on your wrestling trunks, step into the ring and ready to experience WWF WrestleMania. . . from the inside!</desc>
		<image>./images/WrestleMania-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="1627" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/badnewsbaseball.zip</path>
		<name>Bad News Baseball</name>
		<desc>Looking for a baseball game that will challenge your skills and tickle your funnybone? You've finally found it. Bad News Baseball is the new cartoon-style, outrageously funny baseball game only from Tecmo. It's fast-paced and jam-packed full of new animated cinema displays and exciting action. And now Bad News Baseball has boys and girls teams! Play against the computer, play with a buddy, or use the spectator mode, but you had better get ready to laugh. Featuring 12 boys teams and 12 girls teams, 11 different pitches and Tecmo's famous instant close-ups, all you need is a hotdog and you're ready to play.</desc>
		<image>./images/badnewsbaseball-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="7816" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sports/baseballstars2.zip</path>
		<name>Baseball Stars II</name>
		<desc>Baseball Stars 2 is a 2-player baseball arcade game released by SNK in 1992 for the Neo-Geo console.  A less cartoony console version was released for the NES by Romstar the same year.  Baseball Stars 2 for the Nintendo Entertainment System was distributed by Romstar in 1992.  Changes made from the original Baseball Stars, released by SNK in 1989: Female players are no longer included in any form.  Two additional batting stances. These additional stances are never used for players on custom teams. They will only appear on the pre-made teams' players.  Enhanced pitch control.  Ability to shift field formations when playing defense.  Ability to view your team roster and ratings while in-game.  Sidearm-style pitchers are never generated on custom teams. They can only be hired.  Easier bunting controls; bunts are now retractable. (Hold Down+A to bunt instead of stopping the swing partway through.)  Ability to see lead-offs while pitching/batting.  Six pitchers and four bench players instead of five each.  New music and home run animations. These include the "Power connect" graphic for a two-run home run, an animated graphic of the batter rounding the bases and pumping his fist for a 3-run home run or grand slam, and a similar (yet very rare) graphic including a Yorkshire terrier following the batter for a come-from-behind (usually game-ending) home run in a dramatic situation.  Can no longer name custom teams or rename players on custom teams.  You can still upgrade player using the same 15-point system introduced in the original Baseball Stars. However, the random points you get to disperse to various skills each time you purchase a player upgrade changed from between 1 and 6 to between 1 and 5.  Player upgrades overall are much more expensive while the money received during play has remained about the same. This makes it much more time-consuming to upgrade players to maximum.  You can still fire players and hire players. However, due to the fact you cannot change the names of hired players your hired player will always be named generic names given by the game (examples 'STAR 5', 'ROOK 2', etc.). This can also lead to multiple players sharing the same name throughout the custom teams, even conceivably multiple players on the same team with the same name.  Players can still create leagues of up to 125 games (6 teams playing each other 25 times) and view statistics such as League Standings and Top 10 in Average, Home Runs, Runs Batted In, Earned Run Average, Wins and Saves. (A peculiar glitch occurs when viewing league leaders. The last pitcher listed on any user-created team in "View Team" does not appear in any of the Top 10 leaderboards.)</desc>
		<image>./images/baseballstars2-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eikichi Kawasaki and team</developer>
		<publisher>Romstar Incorporated</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
</gameList>
